[Script Info]
;          Script generated by Aegisub v2.1.2 RELEASE PREVIEW (SVN r1987, amz)
;          http://www.aegisub.net
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2010-12-12 18:32:49
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: Default2 Aegisub file
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default2,MS UI Gothic,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,10,10,10,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00145CD6,&H804182ED,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,12,134
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00145CD6,&H804182ED,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,12,134
Style: biaoti,DFPGirlW5-B5,45,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,3,30,30,10,136
Style: biaoti1,ＤＦ教科書体W3,45,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,3,30,30,10,128
Style: biaoti2,DFPGirlW5-B5,45,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,3,30,30,10,136
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: OP1,ＤＦ教科書体W3,27,&H009A35FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,7,30,30,10,128
Style: OP2,DFPGirlW5-B5,27,&H009A35FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,3,30,30,10,136
Style: ED1,HGMaruGothicMPRO,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00765932,&H00FFFFFF,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,7,30,30,10,128
Style: ED2,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00765932,&H00FFFFFF,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,3,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.00,0:11:14.00,biaozhi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(82,40)}{\move(490,30,490,45,0,2000)}{\t(0,2000,\fry360)}{\fade(500,500)}{\t(0,2000,\fs28)}動漫國字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.00,0:11:14.00,biaozhi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(82,54)}{\t(0,2000,\fs20)}{\fade(500,500)}bbs . dmguo . com
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.12,0:23:55.37,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由動漫國字幕組製作(bbs.dmguo.com)\N僅供試看,若您喜歡本作品,請支持購買正版音像製品
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.37,0:23:59.10,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}片源：Khy   翻譯:^★晞唲^&時の楔  時間:タママ  後期:小白  MKV：nuomi
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.47,0:24:05.34,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}9000G永不過期,同步連載的動漫下載站  http://x.dmguo.com
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.43,0:01:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竊笑…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.28,0:01:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.19,0:01:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在看什麼 姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.10,0:01:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 在觀察而已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.38,0:01:44.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別管我 你繼續
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.14,0:01:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就不管你繼續了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.34,0:01:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼時候有了這種興趣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.99,0:01:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用擔心哦 姊姊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.03,0:02:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是買的 都是借來的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.44,0:02:02.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明信片都是用部費買的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.61,0:02:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是懸賞部的活動啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.06,0:02:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姊姊覺得增刊套裝和鮭魚罐頭和特製多用小刀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.77,0:02:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪個比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.70,0:02:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 完全沒有參考價值
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.17,0:02:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼參考
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.95,0:02:18.86,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回活動 妹妹DAY 歡迎回來 哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.09,0:02:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是女僕是妹妹…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.33,0:02:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不太想像得出來
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.41,0:02:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說什麼呢 妹妹就是治癒和萌系的凝結哦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.76,0:02:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凝結嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.92,0:02:29.64,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五月 女僕.拿鐵店長
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.92,0:02:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對店裡來說 也是相當有爆點的活動呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.17,0:02:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 小美 我們來試著做做看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.53,0:02:36.01,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繪梨香 專業學生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.77,0:02:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頭髮還是弄得幼稚點好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.69,0:02:38.61,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穗香 自由業
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.59,0:02:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美果然還是適合雙馬尾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.34,0:02:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稱呼客人的時候不是「主人」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.27,0:02:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要叫「哥哥大人」「姊姊大人」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.06,0:02:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根據自己的性格 也可以改成「歐尼醬」「姊姊」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.16,0:02:53.13,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(670,165)}美   什麼顏色？天然色？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.16,0:02:53.13,biaoti1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(267,165)}咲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.21,0:02:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 比我想像的還適合
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.95,0:02:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美想怎麼稱呼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.80,0:03:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對客人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.99,0:03:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穗香想叫「歐尼醬」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.59,0:03:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大…大哥 之類的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.02,0:03:11.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼啊 小美
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.37,0:03:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還年輕 不說「歐尼炭」之類的怎麼行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.24,0:03:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歐尼炭？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.58,0:03:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如「歐尼炭 幫我換衣衣~」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.16,0:03:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如「歐尼炭 一起睡覺覺吧~」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.99,0:03:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹就應該是這樣的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.66,0:03:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾歲的妹妹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.86,0:03:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是穗香 一遇到擅長領域就更嚴格了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.86,0:03:27.88,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁年輕時不拿年輕當武器太浪費了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.98,0:03:31.87,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好現在要活用起來 有的方面就是女生才能被允許
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.66,0:03:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觸到狂熱開關了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.09,0:03:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來試試 你現在是等待最喜歡的哥哥回家的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.50,0:03:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒回來嗎 歐尼炭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.07,0:03:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還…還沒回來嗎 歐尼炭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.40,0:03:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.94,0:03:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可…可能回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.96,0:03:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回家 歐尼炭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.30,0:03:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回家 歐尼炭…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.55,0:04:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說了不符合我性格的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.95,0:04:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個對我可能有點勉強…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.52,0:04:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想把不符合性格當做工作無能的藉口？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.30,0:04:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穗香？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.56,0:04:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想是時候一吐為快了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.07,0:04:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿天然系 不諳世事當賣點我是無所謂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.60,0:04:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然拿人薪水 按常識至少也該學習下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.57,0:04:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑化穗香終於出現了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.57,0:04:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經無法阻擋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.64,0:04:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫你保持原樣你就當真 一點也不嘗試改變
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.27,0:04:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是蠢到家了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.70,0:04:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少撒嬌了吧 你個小丫頭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.75,0:04:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.44,0:04:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.77,0:04:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要在意 小美
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.30,0:04:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的話 我改下排班表就是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.97,0:04:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次再努力就行啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.85,0:05:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 下次活動是女僕戰隊DAY哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.13,0:05:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我絕對要當PINK
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.32,0:05:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穗香也說要PINK 都不肯讓給人家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.71,0:05:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美要什麼顏色
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.65,0:05:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隨便什麼顏色都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.52,0:05:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天下班了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.21,0:05:16.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.32,0:05:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總是來探望小美
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.79,0:05:20.36,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美少年 好萌
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.80,0:05:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫碓冰吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.79,0:05:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 你應該知道吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.03,0:05:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美的形象色
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.68,0:05:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,形象色？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.94,0:05:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次我們辦戰隊活動
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.37,0:05:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在想小美適合什麼顏色
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.05,0:05:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女僕戰隊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.79,0:05:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,個人認為淡紫色 水藍色的感覺比較適合
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.65,0:05:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是這樣會和其他女生撞色
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.12,0:05:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想製作顏色各異的琺琅女僕裝啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.59,0:05:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就透明的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.39,0:05:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴 你個變態
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.57,0:05:50.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦好啦 也不是讓你現在就給出答案
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.01,0:05:51.55,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺好萌
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.51,0:05:52.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能幫忙想想嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.59,0:05:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹 治癒…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.76,0:05:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 看這個
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.07,0:06:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還真控巨乳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.73,0:06:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒收
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.78,0:06:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在女僕交換筆記上給小美留言？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.77,0:06:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒用的 阿郁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.35,0:06:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美通常都不寫女僕交換筆記的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.64,0:06:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要試試才知道嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.69,0:06:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用試了 她不會回復的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.60,0:06:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能會被學校其他人看出筆跡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.93,0:06:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種會留下證據的企劃她絕對不會參加…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.53,0:06:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 只要傾注了深深的愛…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.98,0:06:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.31,0:06:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道有辦法吸引小美
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.86,0:06:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如 這樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.38,0:06:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在留言上添上插畫
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.66,0:06:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畫…畫得好棒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.47,0:06:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊 阿郁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.62,0:06:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來你還有這特長
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.00,0:06:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前一直瞞著你們
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.84,0:06:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我其實是個隱性宅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.66,0:06:46.26,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡畫漫畫之類的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.70,0:06:47.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿郁你個傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.83,0:06:51.21,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(150,280)}{\frz-10}隱\N性\N宅\N\N自\N稱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.04,0:06:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吐槽無力…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.75,0:06:53.52,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全員女僕咖啡店 超熟客
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.92,0:06:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.14,0:06:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還不賴 就放過你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.31,0:06:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被放過了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.51,0:07:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放過什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.56,0:07:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是這張畫 頭花會是什麼顏色
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.75,0:07:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.92,0:07:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顏色？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.12,0:07:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然問這幹嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.27,0:07:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,題目 適合小美又能表現其形象的顏色
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.75,0:07:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,限時10秒作答
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.48,0:07:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始 10  9  3  2  1
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.07,0:07:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡果然還是紅色好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.34,0:07:21.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓人感覺熱情似火 又有女性堅強的紅色
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.94,0:07:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又能與小美的黑髮相映
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.21,0:07:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得紫色好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.41,0:07:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又冷傲又性感的紫色
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.03,0:07:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還帶點成熟的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.80,0:07:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡黑色 那緊致的身材肯定是配黑色吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.40,0:07:35.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是自然地再加上蕾絲就更…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.42,0:07:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我反倒喜歡草莓內褲
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.30,0:07:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥時候扯到內褲上去了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.40,0:07:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 看 寫著妹妹特輯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.30,0:07:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別看啦 那是會長沒收的書吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.41,0:07:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會被罵的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.44,0:07:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是你看看 這個和幸村的妹妹好像
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.47,0:07:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.46,0:07:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是漫畫角色嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.33,0:08:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是真的很像啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.21,0:08:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說是吧 幸村
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.29,0:08:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.90,0:08:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說我對二次元沒興趣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.31,0:08:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每個看著都一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.85,0:08:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 這種我也喜歡哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.02,0:08:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但基本還是停留在三次元
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.73,0:08:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸村的妹妹會穿這種輕飄飄的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.03,0:08:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.33,0:08:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真羨慕你啊 身邊有那麼治癒的女生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.66,0:08:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太抬舉她了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.57,0:08:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 放送委員會要開始了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.08,0:08:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先走了 幸村 還要給花澆水
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.85,0:08:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.25,0:08:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸村
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.35,0:08:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.71,0:08:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 … 那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.72,0:08:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和你妹妹…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.44,0:08:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常都聊些什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.51,0:08:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聊些家常啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.43,0:08:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡能治癒你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.97,0:08:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,治癒嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.52,0:08:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那麼像這本書裡的動畫角色嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.27,0:08:59.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…快尿出來了 先走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.14,0:09:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.82,0:09:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在思考沒收的趨勢和對策…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.29,0:09:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.25,0:09:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說 你在看什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.19,0:09:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.65,0:09:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟姊妹？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.11,0:09:27.82,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,午餐時間
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.58,0:09:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有啊 我沒說過嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.43,0:09:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我家還有個哥哥和妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.26,0:09:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲 聽我說 聽我說
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.89,0:09:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靜子的兄妹 全都戴同一款眼鏡
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.85,0:09:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說了很像 但有不同的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.22,0:09:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且全都長一張臉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.11,0:09:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個倒不可否認
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.77,0:09:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 眼鏡有區別哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.75,0:09:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有個哥哥嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.58,0:09:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.44,0:09:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 我沒有哥哥弟弟 在想會是怎樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.81,0:09:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感 感情好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.16,0:09:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和哥哥嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.75,0:09:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好也不壞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.59,0:09:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為全是這副德行嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.77,0:10:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什麼意思
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.79,0:10:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小櫻呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.42,0:10:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有個姊姊哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.71,0:10:08.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感情好得不得了 經常兩人一起去購物哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.81,0:10:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣哦 靜子和小櫻都是妹妹啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.19,0:10:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的確看著她們倆就有種被治癒的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.34,0:10:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然 也不是因為她們是妹妹的關係
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.00,0:10:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長就是想營造這種治癒氣氛的地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.81,0:10:25.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.88,0:10:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 一直盯著我們看
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.12,0:10:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 就是覺得你們好可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.60,0:10:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等…到底怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.60,0:10:38.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該說 你想把我們怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.10,0:10:41.74,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 我要愛上你啦 美咲
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.47,0:10:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又認真思考了一次
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.42,0:10:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能做到嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.55,0:11:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣好嗎 阿郁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.10,0:11:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的要寫嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.73,0:11:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把24彩色筆都帶來了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.22,0:11:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說難道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.21,0:11:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫色
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.22,0:11:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畫那個不好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.60,0:11:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想畫的話根本不需要彩色筆  就黑蕾絲
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.18,0:11:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要畫還是草莓…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.69,0:11:16.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就折中 豹紋好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.13,0:11:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼折中法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.10,0:11:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了 主人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.52,0:11:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是萌萌蛋包飯特別優惠
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.38,0:11:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五月？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.01,0:11:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒼蠅？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.96,0:11:31.29,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(200,150)}五月蠅=吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.46,0:11:33.06,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9}向店長借的「我的哥哥」全30卷
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.43,0:11:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是努力得令人佩服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.70,0:11:39.48,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昴 自由業
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.79,0:11:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前休息時還一邊看課本一邊舉啞鈴
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.18,0:11:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之就是很認真呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.15,0:11:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作上手也快
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.30,0:11:47.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穗香說實話很討厭她哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.52,0:11:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管她什麼家庭狀況 但待遇好得讓我很不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.21,0:11:54.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 她會幫我搬重物
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.89,0:11:55.63,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力氣活就交給我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.02,0:11:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且關鍵是我被討厭的主人纏上時
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.41,0:12:00.75,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(100,210)}好…好萌
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.92,0:12:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人 能原諒她了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.33,0:12:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人也是大大的滿足
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.76,0:12:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以覺得這樣貌似也不錯 還方便
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.28,0:12:10.38,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,180)}耳朵塞住聽不見
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.40,0:12:10.46,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歐尼炭 醬 桑…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.75,0:12:12.11,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三段活用的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.69,0:12:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穗香還真是腹黑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.78,0:12:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.16,0:12:19.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在觀察 究竟是什麼顏色
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.85,0:12:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是說了隨便定嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.80,0:12:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了透明
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.27,0:12:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先不說那個 你現在滿腦子都想著怎麼改口歐尼炭？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.83,0:12:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.87,0:12:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長有個妹妹吧 比較容易想像吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.77,0:12:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妹妹又不會叫歐尼炭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.97,0:12:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且也從沒撒嬌嚷嚷著朝我要東西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.34,0:12:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的話就讓店長重新排班吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.75,0:12:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.86,0:12:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少撒嬌了吧 你個小丫頭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.72,0:12:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不想輕易說「不行 做不到」
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.91,0:12:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且「女僕.拿鐵」與一般咖啡店不同
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.58,0:13:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在於能體驗到超乎日常的快樂 治癒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.32,0:13:04.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之 是個能讓你感受不同氣氛的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.36,0:13:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而營造那種氛圍的能力 正是工作人員應當具備的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.43,0:13:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最近終於注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.59,0:13:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我也要扮演治癒角色
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.69,0:13:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就更不用勉強吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.49,0:13:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.80,0:13:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得保持這樣挺好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.36,0:13:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果現在最真實的會長是我妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.22,0:13:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是又怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.15,0:13:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超萌的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.09,0:13:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做個美咲天天365日睡顏收藏冊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.48,0:13:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想著今天要以怎樣的角度拍攝
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.81,0:13:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是個不折不扣的變態！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.40,0:13:42.97,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹DAY當天
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.57,0:13:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來 歐尼炭
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.55,0:13:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也辛苦了 來 坐這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.40,0:13:54.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想喝點什麼嗎 還是想吃飯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.85,0:13:52.27,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然還有點生硬 但總體來說自然多了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.90,0:13:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說話也有點死板 已經很夠格了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.17,0:14:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認同他挑戰蘿莉系妹妹角色的努力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.54,0:14:05.22,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穗香萌點考察
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.86,0:14:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美其實還適合另一種角色
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.19,0:14:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,認真清純的妹妹型
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.16,0:14:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但好像沒發現那種可能性啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.04,0:14:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來 歐尼炭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.93,0:14:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼來了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.23,0:14:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美才是 怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.01,0:14:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明從來都不叫我「歐尼炭」的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.03,0:14:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然變這麼機靈 有點噁心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.50,0:14:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又想找我要什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.56,0:14:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是做了什麼對不起我的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.72,0:14:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討 真討厭呢 歐尼炭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.37,0:14:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美一直是這…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.80,0:14:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道想抵消你上次在我面前放屁那件事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.37,0:14:48.94,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.84,0:14:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行哦 小美
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.14,0:14:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為客人的玩笑真生氣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.25,0:14:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然的確是個討厭的玩笑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.28,0:14:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真討厭呢 歐尼炭
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.21,0:14:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美沒有放屁哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.17,0:15:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來  水
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.03,0:15:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是哪的水
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.49,0:15:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歐尼炭想喝阿爾卑斯的水 你去打來
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.20,0:15:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又說那麼任性的話
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.62,0:15:10.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別讓小美為難嘛 歐尼炭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.05,0:15:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天要吃什麼 小美推薦蛋包飯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.89,0:15:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歐尼炭想吃烤龍蝦 紅酒沙司 蒸醬鵝肝 附加夏季松露最好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.81,0:15:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又說這種辦不到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.03,0:15:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說了不要為難小美嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.77,0:15:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美才是 這也不行那也不行 怎麼能這麼任性
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.10,0:15:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還撒謊說沒放屁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.33,0:15:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說了沒有放！你這個變態笨蛋大哥！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.13,0:15:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 還是發飆了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.85,0:15:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天小美心情不好呢 我還是回去算了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.29,0:15:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歐尼炭…可以再來的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.05,0:16:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這 這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.68,0:16:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.75,0:16:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一種妹妹角色
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.70,0:16:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那個
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.95,0:16:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 既不是蘿莉系也不是認真清純係
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.72,0:16:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天然
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.35,0:16:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傲嬌妹妹角色
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.37,0:16:14.98,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發現新萌點
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.08,0:16:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.22,0:16:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老實說 真沒想到她會努力到那份上呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.29,0:16:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 小美一直很努力的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.15,0:16:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還想再多看看她可愛的「嬌」呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.14,0:16:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確實 傲倒是見識過不少了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.37,0:16:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在活動中還不行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.44,0:16:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為 小美表現出最可愛的一面
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.40,0:16:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不謝謝我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.14,0:16:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憑什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.14,0:16:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多虧我活動才成功了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.98,0:16:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種根本算不上成功
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.88,0:16:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全是我實力欠佳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.30,0:16:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,演得太過投入的話 就變得不能冷靜判斷
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.12,0:16:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後就發起飆來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.64,0:16:55.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說了刻意演戲是不行的 保持本色就好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.17,0:16:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把本色表現出來 還怎麼治癒別人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.81,0:17:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 我覺得這樣是個很棒的妹妹哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.21,0:17:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 笨蛋碓冰
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.07,0:17:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然只有在身邊有碓冰的時候啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.13,0:17:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧 碓冰學長來了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.01,0:17:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.95,0:17:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我有事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.45,0:17:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 叫你出來真不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.83,0:17:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 有件事無論如何都想直接告訴你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.77,0:17:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實我…從入學那天開始就一直對學長…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.14,0:17:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能讓我做你女朋友嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.04,0:17:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好險
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.62,0:17:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰學長
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.72,0:17:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是個比起第三餐更喜歡女僕的深度宅男
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.94,0:17:55.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,愛讀的書都是女僕相關
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.84,0:17:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咖啡店一定選女僕店 當然手辦也在收藏
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.69,0:18:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩女僕遊戲的時候不停地說「好萌 好萌」
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.83,0:18:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亢奮起來就會自己穿上女僕服嘿嘿咻咻 再見
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.47,0:18:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,振作 這是在試探你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.05,0:18:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼可能是宅男啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.68,0:18:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不介意 我會變成學長喜歡的類型
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.53,0:18:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就更不行了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.70,0:18:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰 下節課要開始了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.50,0:18:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.40,0:18:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脫吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.77,0:18:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說什麼呢 你個變態
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.58,0:18:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼疼疼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.43,0:18:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都腫成這樣了 難道還想忍到這節下課
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.92,0:18:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又沒出血
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.86,0:18:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是會長風範的堅強想法
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.24,0:18:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說 為什麼當時你會看到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.50,0:18:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次都太巧了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.96,0:19:04.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼辦法 會長總是出現在我去的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.69,0:19:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是命運啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.02,0:19:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次吃驚的是我才對
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.29,0:19:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤其在學校裡碰見會長時 你總是袒護女生跟男生對著幹
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.22,0:19:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還以為是哪部少女漫畫裡的英雄呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.71,0:19:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不好意思啊 不像女生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.91,0:19:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女生保護女生有什麼不對
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.24,0:19:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又沒說不對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.29,0:19:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過像今天這樣挺身保護男生 還真是意想不到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.65,0:19:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法啊 當時總不能袖手旁觀吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.83,0:19:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 會長不管自己受多重的傷
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.85,0:19:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不論男女都會去救囉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.92,0:19:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.94,0:19:47.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是碓冰 我也會救
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.79,0:19:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那還真是可靠啊 小美
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.89,0:19:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在嘲笑我是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.00,0:20:01.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美 手怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.88,0:20:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在學校裡一不小心 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.21,0:20:04.31,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繃帶包成這樣了 沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.30,0:20:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉…只是藥塗得誇張了點
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.43,0:20:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腫成那樣你還好意思說
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.34,0:20:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰 這裡男生止步
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.57,0:20:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我馬上要去工作了 你也回去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.66,0:20:14.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.58,0:20:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我去了 店長
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.40,0:20:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼的話要告訴我啊 小美
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.13,0:20:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我今天就去幫小美的忙 碓冰也放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.16,0:20:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果幫得太明顯的話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.26,0:20:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙反而會更加努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.73,0:20:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請盡量別讓她發現 裝作不經意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.30,0:20:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行了 萌之花啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.32,0:20:35.87,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萌啊 萌啊 萌啊 萌啊 萌啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.42,0:20:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰也挺辛苦的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.00,0:20:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼 覺得蠻好玩的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.81,0:20:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒覺得辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.39,0:20:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 也是 光看著那麼努力的小美就覺得很快樂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.63,0:20:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凡事都全力以赴地去做
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.54,0:21:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有時候常人想做都不敢踏出第一步
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.28,0:21:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美卻總是全力以赴到讓人擔心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.63,0:21:07.77,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總有一天要超過碓冰
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.67,0:21:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在已經是個非常能幹的女孩了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.84,0:21:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總能感受到她想更加努力的決心 讓人無法放下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.15,0:21:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且自己也會受她影響 覺得還能加把勁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.78,0:21:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰也是這樣感覺到快樂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.37,0:21:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說小美的形象色我想過了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.78,0:21:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走自己的道路 不被染上任何人的顏色
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.61,0:21:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某種意義上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.61,0:21:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是純白的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.64,0:21:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點意外呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.31,0:21:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼 碓冰 你還在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.18,0:21:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是叫你快回去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.34,0:21:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 也包含著想給她染上點顏色的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.44,0:21:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在說些什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.24,0:21:54.19,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克制不住萌萌花啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.61,0:21:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臉紅了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.32,0:22:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好有型 純白小美
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.85,0:22:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放倒我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.27,0:22:05.60,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主人超級滿足
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.73,0:22:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要我也要
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.38,0:22:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命 老大
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.99,0:22:09.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是稍微手下留情吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.89,0:22:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.05,0:23:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 現在已經克制不住萌萌花啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.50,0:23:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長 這個活動服裝只用一次太浪費了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.65,0:23:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有機會再辦吧 妹妹DAY2 敬請期待哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.32,0:23:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次請穿上透明裝
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.98,0:23:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又出現了 碓冰給我閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.86,0:23:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 店長在家也是妹妹嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.13,0:24:01.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 有個哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.45,0:24:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店長 店裡來了個超可愛的女生
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.91,0:24:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.29,0:24:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.38,0:24:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小美超可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.04,0:24:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰給我閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.21,0:24:10.90,biaoti2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(680,357)}{\c&H509EF5&}{\fad(300,0)}網 絡 偶 像 AOI 醬
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.42,0:00:07.03,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}どうか Please！can you keep my secret
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.15,0:00:24.04,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}キラキラと輝くミラー
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.46,0:00:29.92,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}私はどんなふうに映っているの
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.58,0:00:34.58,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}ホラホラと手招く未来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.76,0:00:39.74,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}これからどんなコトが起こるの
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.48,0:00:50.82,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}目に見えているモノがスベテではないから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.87,0:00:53.57,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}無我夢中でThat's ALL RIGHT
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.62,0:00:56.21,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}迷わないで I wanna TRY
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.26,0:01:01.12,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}自分のキモチにまっすぐでいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.17,0:01:04.01,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}だけど１つや２つくらい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.06,0:01:06.47,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}誰にもバレたくない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.52,0:01:11.48,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}ナイショってあるものだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.78,0:01:17.31,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}胸がちょっと痛む　my secret
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.42,0:00:07.03,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}求求你 Please！can you keep my secret
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.15,0:00:24.04,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}閃爍光芒的鏡子裡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.46,0:00:29.92,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}我究竟是什麼模樣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.58,0:00:34.58,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}快樂招手的未來裡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.76,0:00:39.74,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}又將會發生些什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.48,0:00:50.82,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}因為所見並非一切
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.87,0:00:53.57,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}心醉神迷 That's ALL RIGHT
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.62,0:00:56.21,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}不要迷茫 I wanna TRY
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.26,0:01:01.12,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}想真心面對自己的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.17,0:01:04.01,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}但哪怕只是一兩件事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.06,0:01:06.47,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}也不想透露給任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.52,0:01:11.48,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}因為那是我心中的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.78,0:01:17.31,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}心口隱隱作痛　my secret
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.22,0:22:31.41,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}ほんの少しでも　吐き出してほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.67,0:22:36.62,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}この手で受け止めるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.67,0:22:42.12,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}とても強がりな君のことだから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.17,0:22:49.88,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}また何かを隠そうとして　ねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.93,0:22:57.74,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}確かな予感つかんだその手を握りしめて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.79,0:23:03.24,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}走り出した　行くあてもなく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.29,0:23:08.37,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}ただ僕の心の中にいて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.42,0:23:13.26,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}いつもそばで　見守るから
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.93,0:23:18.88,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}どんな時も離れはしないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.93,0:23:24.38,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}立ち留まらず　怖がらないで
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.43,0:23:29.54,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}君がもしも振り向いた時は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.59,0:23:36.47,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}僕らきっと笑い合おう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.22,0:22:31.41,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}哪怕一點點 也希望你吐露真心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.67,0:22:36.62,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}我會親手接受
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.67,0:22:42.12,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}我了解你的逞強
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.17,0:22:49.88,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}一定又想隱瞞什麼 對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.93,0:22:57.74,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}緊握那雙抓住明確預感的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.79,0:23:03.24,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}開始奔跑 沒有目標
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.29,0:23:08.37,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}只停留在我心中
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.42,0:23:13.26,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}因為我守候在身邊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.93,0:23:18.88,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}永遠不會離開
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.93,0:23:24.38,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}不要駐足 不要害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.43,0:23:29.54,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}當你有天回首時
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.59,0:23:36.47,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}我們一定能相視而笑


