[Script Info]
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,simhei,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H64000000,&H96040200,0,0,0,0,100,100,1,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,25,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.00,0:01:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个很久很久以前的故事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.35,0:01:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在某个地方 有一位失去了双亲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.85,0:01:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而深深陷入悲伤之中的小公主
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.40,0:01:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这位公主面前
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.30,0:01:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了一位骑着白马四处旅行的王子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.90,0:01:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威风凛凛的身影 温柔的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.95,0:01:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王子用蔷薇的芳香环抱着公主
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.15,0:01:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并轻轻地吻去了她的眼泪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.85,0:02:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,独自一人忍受着深深哀伤的幼小的你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.75,0:02:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你在长大之后也不要失去这份坚强与高尚
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.20,0:02:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个就作为今天的回忆吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.30,0:02:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还会再相见的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.90,0:02:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这枚戒指 或许会指引你来到我的所在之处
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.45,0:02:22.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王子所赠的戒指应该就是订婚戒指吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.25,0:02:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这是件好事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.90,0:02:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是公主太过于憧憬王子了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.15,0:02:33.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以决定自己也要成为王子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.95,0:02:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这样真的好吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.05,0:02:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第03话 「舞會之夜」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.85,0:03:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戒指确实还在我的手上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.30,0:03:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那次相遇 果然是真的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.80,0:03:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决斗广场 蔷薇新娘
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.80,0:03:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部都是这枚戒指的指引吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.60,0:03:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 欧蒂娜大人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.15,0:03:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吃饱了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.55,0:03:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要继续这种早晚都只有两个人的用餐吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.50,0:03:45.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静静的真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.60,0:03:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.00,0:03:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.50,0:03:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在班上也总是一个人独处
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.75,0:03:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的都没有朋友吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.00,0:03:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有啊 在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.50,0:04:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了，就别讨论你是不是有它就够了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.10,0:04:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个「欧蒂娜大人」的称呼还是免了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.90,0:04:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可以吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.50,0:04:32.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是欧蒂娜大人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.15,0:04:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧蒂娜大人 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.20,0:04:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呦 早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.40,0:04:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧蒂娜大人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.60,0:04:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.30,0:04:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊 早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.10,0:04:50.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 的确大家都是这样称呼的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.10,0:04:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是出自你口时
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.25,0:04:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉就不像是在开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.30,0:04:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 我已经和欧蒂娜大人订了婚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.75,0:05:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不要再说了 什么订婚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.00,0:05:02.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蔷薇新娘的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.80,0:05:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.10,0:05:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.38,0:05:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别看我穿这样 但却是个健全的女生耶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.15,0:05:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要什么新娘
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.25,0:05:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只对健全的男生感兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.60,0:05:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 那就太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.60,0:05:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承蒙欣赏
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.25,0:05:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是健全的男生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.65,0:05:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学生会会长桐生冬芽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.40,0:05:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.75,0:05:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熟人吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.30,0:05:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那当然喽
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.60,0:05:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟她是蔷薇新娘嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.80,0:05:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嘛 你也是那个决斗游戏的一分子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.55,0:05:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件事你有向谁说过吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.35,0:05:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种荒谬的事情能向别人提起吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.20,0:05:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.35,0:05:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生气的表情也是如此地威风凛凛而又美丽呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.30,0:05:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天上欧蒂娜同学
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.60,0:06:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太轻浮了 学生会会长
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.25,0:06:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别生气嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.60,0:06:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.95,0:06:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是完全没有缘份的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.35,0:06:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.10,0:06:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么会戴着那个？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.45,0:06:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还会为什么 不就是为了要与你邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.05,0:06:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.50,0:06:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想和你 更加地亲近
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.70,0:07:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说 他就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.10,0:07:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋壳若不啄破的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.10,0:07:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋里的雏鸟将无法诞生而死去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.55,0:07:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾等就是雏鸟 蛋就是这世界
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.90,0:07:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界之壳若不打破的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.90,0:07:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾等将无法诞生而死去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.50,0:07:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去破坏世界之壳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.15,0:07:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让世界革命！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.45,0:07:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天 再度与天上欧蒂娜决斗的西园寺
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.75,0:07:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又输了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.95,0:07:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西园寺学长从昨天起就把自己关在房里
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.50,0:07:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也没来学园的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.35,0:07:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就别管那家伙了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.35,0:07:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒是天上欧蒂娜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.40,0:07:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她也和我们一样 是想要让世界革命的吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.90,0:07:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.15,0:07:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她与我们不同
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.90,0:07:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎并没有收到「世界尽头」的来信
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.00,0:08:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又为何会持有蔷薇刻印呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.45,0:08:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 为什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.60,0:08:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧蒂娜
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.20,0:08:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧蒂娜 欧蒂娜 欧蒂娜大人！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.40,0:08:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若叶 刚才那样是很危险的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.10,0:08:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.95,0:08:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 在看冬芽学长啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.82,0:08:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此 是这么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.85,0:08:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么“这么回事”啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.25,0:08:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那个人还是算了的比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.50,0:08:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学园第一的花花公子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.45,0:08:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传言他让好多女孩子哭过耶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.50,0:08:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的花花公子 不可能是白马王子的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.50,0:09:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点忘了问了 欧蒂娜和谁同室呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.60,0:09:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬宫安希
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.30,0:09:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.30,0:09:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.10,0:09:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是听错了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.40,0:09:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听错了是指？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.10,0:09:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常听到一些不好的传闻
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.10,0:09:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说那女孩 在男生中似乎出乎意料地受欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.25,0:09:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传闻？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.55,0:09:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.10,0:09:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因为你的勾引
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.60,0:09:29.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的西园寺学长才会一蹶不振
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.10,0:09:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西园寺学长一直请假 就连剑道部都没去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.75,0:09:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可怕的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.30,0:09:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我们的西园寺学长还给我们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.00,0:09:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说话啊你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.90,0:09:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们在做什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.35,0:09:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七实小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.60,0:09:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们到底在嚷嚷些什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.70,0:09:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看情形不向学生会报告不行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.65,0:09:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有 这…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.65,0:09:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.90,0:09:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们先告退了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.00,0:10:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.10,0:10:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩 真是谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.00,0:10:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫七实是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.95,0:10:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为姬宫学姊很受男生欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.05,0:10:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不经意间就被嫉妒了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.45,0:10:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们一年级的男生中
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.65,0:10:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬宫学姐也是最有人气的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.55,0:10:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟都是被提名为今年舞会皇后的人了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.85,0:10:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舞会皇后?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.50,0:10:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个周末的舞会上
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.60,0:10:31.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将会选出学园第一的舞会皇后
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.05,0:10:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而姬宫学姐正是候选人之一哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.90,0:10:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还请您务必出席哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.15,0:10:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了男生们会很高兴以外
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.65,0:10:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也从很久以前就希望能和姬宫学姐更加的亲近呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.90,0:11:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讨厌 上当了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.05,0:11:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说你啊 姬宫
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.90,0:11:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.20,0:11:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的没有朋友吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.20,0:11:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有啊 在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.75,0:11:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 这样说也没错啦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.60,0:11:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬宫安希小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.20,0:11:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天上欧蒂娜小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.60,0:11:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有礼物要送交两位
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.10,0:11:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为舞会皇后候选人的证明
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.20,0:11:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,执行委员会特赠此套礼服
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.85,0:12:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请务必穿着出席周末的舞会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.95,0:12:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,委员会全体 诚心期待您的光临
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.30,0:12:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.70,0:12:12.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧蒂娜大人的呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.80,0:12:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此外 这盒是给欧蒂娜小姐的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.60,0:12:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是桐生会长送的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.00,0:12:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 给我的？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.85,0:12:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又和我无关啊 而且也没受到邀请
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.75,0:12:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,纸盒里应该有邀请函及留言卡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.45,0:12:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就先告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.45,0:12:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.55,0:12:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的打算让我穿上这个去参加舞会吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.40,0:12:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想去吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.85,0:12:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 因为没兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.15,0:12:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我也不去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.05,0:12:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.15,0:12:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难得被提名为舞会皇后的不是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.35,0:12:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我不习惯人多的场所
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.20,0:13:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得被大家用同样表情盯着看 很可怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.55,0:13:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 这回轮到奇奇了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.00,0:13:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 你还是去的好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.30,0:13:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要去哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.80,0:13:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很需要朋友的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.20,0:13:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是没错啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.30,0:13:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过得多交些朋友才行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.65,0:13:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果欧蒂娜大人如此吩咐的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.80,0:13:27.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 那个男的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.50,0:13:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底在想些什么啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.80,0:13:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗 知道吗 大家知道吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.10,0:13:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 这位太太 你知道吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.05,0:13:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,one
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.40,0:13:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不久之后就要举办舞会的传闻
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.65,0:13:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在城里到处都听得到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.15,0:13:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,one
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.65,0:13:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,two
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.85,0:13:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,one
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.15,0:13:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫作舞会 听起来觉得是不错
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.65,0:13:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是简单地说就是在吊凯子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.20,0:13:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近的小姐真令人担忧啊 令人头痛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.60,0:14:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,one
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.15,0:14:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,two
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.45,0:14:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,one
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.25,0:14:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寡廉鲜耻啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.75,0:14:36.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜猜我是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.75,0:14:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别闹了 七实
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.00,0:14:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是良宵呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.30,0:14:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.25,0:14:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真会撒娇啊 我的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.55,0:14:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢各位今晚的光临
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.70,0:14:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了让这满是春意的夜晚更添乐趣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.05,0:14:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这场小小的舞会
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.50,0:14:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将和往常一样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.75,0:15:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会举办舞会皇后的选拔
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.50,0:15:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还请各位多多协助
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.00,0:15:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是欧蒂娜大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.85,0:15:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱啊 欧蒂娜大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.05,0:15:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学生服的样子就威风凛凛 穿礼服更是如此美丽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.70,0:15:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧蒂娜大人好漂亮哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.85,0:15:31.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.90,0:15:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近哥哥都在谈姬宫学姐的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.45,0:15:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以人家就去邀请了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.30,0:15:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天上欧蒂娜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.50,0:15:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然不应该穿成这样过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.45,0:15:48.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是抱歉 欧蒂娜大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.55,0:15:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了我穿这么丢人的衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.40,0:15:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丢人？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.70,0:15:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.90,0:15:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎光临 姬宫学姐
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.10,0:15:58.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七实同学
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.90,0:16:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件礼服好漂亮 很适合你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.25,0:16:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.15,0:16:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 候选人请到这边来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.15,0:16:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.75,0:16:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛 姬宫还是有朋友的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.65,0:16:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 你的话就别提了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.85,0:16:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太美了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.00,0:16:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超乎想象啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.10,0:16:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不知道你在想象什么啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.05,0:16:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是这个样子 并不适合我啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.35,0:16:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.60,0:16:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是这所学园的皇后啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.55,0:16:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若能与穿着这身礼服的你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.90,0:16:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,共舞一曲的话 我会很高兴的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.90,0:16:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们会成为如画般的一对
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.90,0:17:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.65,0:17:29.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七实小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.90,0:17:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真的有穿着送她的礼服来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.75,0:17:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来还真合身呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.70,0:17:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从我这里夺走哥哥的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.60,0:17:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要让她好好地出出丑！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.10,0:18:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这 这真是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.95,0:18:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.55,0:18:20.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦 弄湿我特意赠送的特制礼服了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.20,0:18:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那件礼服碰到水就麻烦咯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.95,0:18:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 跳支舞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.45,0:18:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请别这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.30,0:18:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的舞会我本来就没兴趣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.90,0:18:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 为什么来了呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.90,0:18:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.85,0:18:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.65,0:18:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.40,0:18:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.80,0:18:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是 什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.45,0:19:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬宫！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.10,0:19:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七实的杰作吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.20,0:19:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟想干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.55,0:19:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正进入佳境却…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.70,0:19:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姬宫
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.90,0:19:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 那是…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.10,0:19:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欧蒂娜大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.35,0:19:32.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来跳舞吧 姬宫
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.75,0:20:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正按计划进行着却…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.90,0:20:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女的是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.40,0:20:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七实
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.95,0:20:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整人也要有个限度吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.80,0:20:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 您在说什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.90,0:20:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 和姬宫跳舞的女生是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.30,0:20:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天上欧蒂娜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.05,0:20:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天上欧蒂娜？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.60,0:20:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 很出色吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.95,0:20:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是她 却脱掉了我送的礼服
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.50,0:20:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥哥竟然送礼服给那个女的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.95,0:20:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女的！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.30,0:23:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薰干 通称米奇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.45,0:23:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钢琴和击剑都是全国级的美少年
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.40,0:23:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇哦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.15,0:23:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然只是中等部一年级
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.30,0:23:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却是选修了大学课程的超秀才
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.75,0:23:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害耶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.85,0:23:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他虽是学生会的成员
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.20,0:23:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却是唯一一个反对决斗的人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.85,0:23:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,岂止如此 还说要做姬宫的家庭教师呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.35,0:23:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油 请努力做吧 我会努力招待人家的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.95,0:23:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次回 少女革命欧蒂娜
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.20,0:23:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「流光傾瀉的庭園．序曲」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.65,0:23:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对命运默示录
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
