[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:JoJo's Bizarre Adventure(2012) TV #01
Original Script:A.I.R.nesSub & MYSUB
Website:http://airu.us/
Website:http://www.manyv.com.cn/
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000F0F0F,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,30,1
Style: Staff,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000F0F0F,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,5,5,5,1
Style: Comment,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000F0F0F,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,30,1
Style: Title,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000F0F0F,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,30,1
Style: EDE,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,========Avant========
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.43,0:00:06.98,Comment,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,570)\fad(800,1000)\blur4}- 1868年 英国 -
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.95,0:00:07.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你看 发生事故了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.46,0:00:19.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真够惨 这边的家伙估计也当场死亡了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.49,0:00:24.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在泥泞中打滑 掉下悬崖啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.91,0:00:28.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还真不愧是贵族 穿着一身好衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.79,0:00:32.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老板 马车里的女人死了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.64,0:00:34.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是小宝宝还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.95,0:00:37.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她是护着孩子死去的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.22,0:00:39.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小宝宝 管他毛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.11,0:00:42.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…你做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.91,0:00:44.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还要问啊 蠢货
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.62,0:00:47.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拿走值钱的东西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.76,0:00:49.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？这是什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.60,0:00:54.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好…好恶心的面具
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.71,0:00:55.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.63,0:00:57.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 过来帮忙！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.06,0:01:00.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拔了他的门牙卖给牙医
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.51,0:01:01.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能卖个高价
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.51,0:01:08.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…你…是你救治我的吗 谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.21,0:01:15.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我妻子…我妻子和儿子呢 他们俩没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.20,0:01:21.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死直…夫人和车夫已经身亡了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.90,0:01:24.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但…但是小孩子没事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.56,0:01:29.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这也是命运吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.33,0:01:32.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我姓乔斯达
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.01,0:01:35.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要报答你的救命之恩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.02,0:01:40.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我再次昏迷前 请告诉我你的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.75,0:01:45.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 这家伙以为我是他的救命恩人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.17,0:01:47.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这蠢货！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.66,0:01:50.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,报个名字不会亏
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.16,0:01:53.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫达利奥·布朗度
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.86,0:01:55.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,布朗度先生…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.00,0:02:01.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我乔斯达绝对不会忘记你的大恩大德
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.69,0:02:15.65,Comment,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,570)\blur4}-12年后-
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.53,0:02:14.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 很乖
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.22,0:02:17.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸 我去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.05,0:02:19.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小心啊 JoJo
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.25,0:02:21.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们走 丹尼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.63,0:02:34.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.46,0:02:36.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,过来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.58,0:02:40.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥 听不到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.51,0:02:46.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 老爸 要吃药吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.10,0:02:50.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,蠢货 药管个屁用
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.56,0:02:54.56,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,酒啊 有钱买药还不如给老子买酒来！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.12,0:03:02.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo 注意礼仪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.08,0:03:05.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.87,0:03:06.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将军
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.56,0:03:11.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拿去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.71,0:03:19.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真丢人啊 臭屁孩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.18,0:03:26.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要 还给我 还给我
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.30,0:03:27.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拿得到就拿啊 艾莉娜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.47,0:03:29.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个娃娃是爸妈给你买的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.96,0:03:33.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你那老爸庸医一个 倒是赚不少
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.23,0:03:38.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看我的 我来把娃娃的衣服脱掉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.53,0:03:41.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看看那里是不是跟真人一样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.27,0:03:50.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哭了 艾莉娜 艾莉娜 爱哭虫艾莉娜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.51,0:03:53.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手 把娃娃还给她！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.96,0:03:56.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么人啊 是艾莉娜的熟人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.51,0:03:59.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我不认识她 但是我有战斗的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.13,0:04:04.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这…混蛋 想在女孩子面前逞威风啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.60,0:04:11.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么啊 这货太弱了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.20,0:04:15.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有人比你更丢人的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.03,0:04:18.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,冲过来救人反而跪了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.97,0:04:25.57,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,噢 这家伙是乔斯达家的独生子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.98,0:04:29.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我虽然跟有钱人没什么仇 但就是讨厌他们
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.91,0:04:31.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别狗眼看人低啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.85,0:04:33.83,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.89,0:04:40.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥 我活不久了 我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.44,0:04:44.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我死后你把这封信寄出去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.18,0:04:47.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后到信上的地址…乔斯达家去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.26,0:04:50.62,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我对他有恩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.25,0:04:52.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你很聪明
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.40,0:04:57.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要当一个不输给任何人的有钱人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.29,0:05:03.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,二世祖就窝在自己家里玩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.43,0:05:04.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.18,0:05:11.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…你…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.01,0:05:12.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别管我！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.56,0:05:13.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,走开啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.01,0:05:18.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不是要你感谢才跟他们打的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.94,0:05:21.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了成为一个真正的绅士
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.39,0:05:24.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是因为你是个女孩子 还遇上麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.02,0:05:28.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算对方是个大个子 就算明知打不过
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.76,0:05:32.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,作为一个绅士 有时候也要挺身而出的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.61,0:05:37.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 终有一天 我不会输给他们的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.85,0:05:46.32,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,丑恶 狡猾 母亲为了你操劳而死
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.50,0:05:48.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是个最差劲的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.79,0:05:50.99,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫我当个最有权势的有钱人？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.13,0:05:55.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,行啊 我当给你看 能利用的我都利用
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.39,0:05:58.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,包括这个叫乔斯达的贵族
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.78,0:06:00.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人渣！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.15,0:06:10.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会成为不输给任何人的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.36,0:06:19.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乔纳森·乔斯达…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.05,0:06:24.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个故事 是围绕着一个神秘石面具
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.35,0:06:29.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生在两个少年身上的命运奇诡的冒险记
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.99,0:06:43.00,Staff,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\blur4\fs26}A.I.R.nesSub & 漫娱字幕组 联合制作
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.99,0:06:43.00,Staff,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\blur4\fs24}翻译: cunhan　校对: dgwxx　后期: 阳光下的草
Comment: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:01.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,========A Part========
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.74,0:06:38.21,Title,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(870,580)\fad(500,0)\blur4}第1话 「侵略者迪奥」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.82,0:07:00.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是谁呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.32,0:07:04.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你是迪奥·布朗度吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.74,0:07:07.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 你是乔纳森·乔斯达了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.11,0:07:09.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家都叫我JoJo的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.21,0:07:11.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以后请多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.99,0:07:13.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.63,0:07:17.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给你介绍 它叫丹尼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.07,0:07:19.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我的爱犬
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.55,0:07:22.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用怕 它绝对不会咬人的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.01,0:07:29.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…你干什么啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.01,0:07:29.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不可饶恕！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.21,0:07:32.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙就是乔斯达家的继承人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.69,0:07:36.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,家世钱财人脉都有的少爷
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.02,0:07:38.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在心理上把他逼上绝路
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.71,0:07:40.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后我迪奥…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.93,0:07:42.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.30,0:07:45.85,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究竟发生什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.58,0:07:50.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常抱歉 那只狗突然扑过来 我反射性地…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.41,0:07:55.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎你 迪奥
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.48,0:07:58.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从今天开始 你就是我们的家人了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.35,0:08:04.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诸位 这位迪奥·布朗度是我的救命恩人的公子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.96,0:08:07.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请你们待他如JoJo一般
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.62,0:08:08.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.85,0:08:11.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥你也不用客气
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.49,0:08:14.02,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟JoJo一样自由地在这个家里生活吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.64,0:08:17.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乔斯达卿 非常感谢您的厚意
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.44,0:08:20.44,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo的母亲也去世了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.78,0:08:22.10,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且你们同岁
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.38,0:08:24.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好相处吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.63,0:08:27.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo 丹尼的事情就不要计较了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.50,0:08:32.42,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 要是有陌生的狗冲我跑过来也会吓一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.93,0:08:34.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我没有在意
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.91,0:08:38.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实是希望他能道个歉的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.16,0:08:41.21,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 以后就要一起生活了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.43,0:08:43.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得尽快跟他成为朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.84,0:08:45.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 迪奥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.68,0:08:47.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我领你到房间去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.30,0:08:48.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.22,0:09:00.45,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么 别随随便便碰我的提包
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.45,0:09:00.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诶？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.08,0:09:04.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫你别用这脏手碰 蠢材
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.39,0:09:06.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是想帮你拿…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.78,0:09:07.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不必！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.14,0:09:11.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,马上让佣人来搬
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.91,0:09:14.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 JoJo
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.53,0:09:18.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别以为我寄住在你家 就能对我呼喝啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.93,0:09:22.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢第一 喜欢NO.1！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.03,0:09:24.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论是谁 都不能在我面前嚣张
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.59,0:09:26.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪有啊 我只是想增进感情…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.85,0:09:29.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有一点 我讨厌狗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.68,0:09:34.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是怕 是对它们向人类讨媚看不顺眼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.17,0:09:37.77,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别让那只叫丹尼的蠢狗接近我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.11,0:09:41.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩在做什么 快来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.83,0:09:42.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.64,0:09:50.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥的登场 令JoJo的愉快的生活变得非常艰苦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.31,0:09:53.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又错了 JoJo！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.31,0:09:57.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看看迪奥 二十题全对
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.70,0:10:04.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo 你还算是个绅士吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.73,0:10:06.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一点礼仪都没有 礼仪啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.20,0:10:10.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把JoJo的餐具收了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.39,0:10:12.88,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今晚没饭吃
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.35,0:10:16.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥来了之后 我发现自己太宠你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.08,0:10:18.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我这个父亲真是非常羞愧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.15,0:10:21.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥的用餐礼仪可是无可挑剔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.73,0:10:28.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哼 蠢材
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.02,0:10:34.65,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来上场的是 乔纳森·乔斯达
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.24,0:10:37.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最近 他强了壮了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.29,0:10:42.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接下来他的对手 其实这次有所变动
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.35,0:10:44.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是一个刚到这个城市
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.06,0:10:47.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还只知道他名字的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.34,0:10:46.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}好啊 有意思！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.34,0:10:47.91,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}那是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.17,0:10:49.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.35,0:10:54.89,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给大家介绍 迪奥·布朗度！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.31,0:11:00.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 被打中脸就当场算输
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.37,0:11:00.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开始！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.05,0:11:03.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上啊 JoJo！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.84,0:11:04.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干掉这外地人！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.80,0:11:11.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好快的动作啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.26,0:11:12.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没见过有人像他那样快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.94,0:11:14.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打不中啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.58,0:11:17.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo 这家伙的拳比我想象中更加迅猛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.37,0:11:19.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.09,0:11:24.26,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让你们看看
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.40,0:11:28.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,破落户们打的贫民窟的街头拳击技巧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.63,0:11:29.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好好尝尝吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.39,0:11:31.74,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打中了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.29,0:11:34.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo输了！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.58,0:11:37.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可别以为这样就结束了 JoJo
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.46,0:11:40.73,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就势将拇指戳进对方的眼睛…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.76,0:11:42.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一拳揍到底！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.08,0:11:49.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 这人好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.67,0:11:50.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥～！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.09,0:11:53.01,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥 你好厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.20,0:11:54.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才是怎样做到的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.25,0:11:58.75,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是用了点新式拳击的防御技巧而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.05,0:12:02.17,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,特别告诉你们也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.17,0:12:03.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.33,0:12:06.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 绝对不要告诉JoJo哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.14,0:12:08.52,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是个大嘴巴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.95,0:12:09.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.96,0:12:11.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还真不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.02,0:12:15.47,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 你故意的 为什么这样做
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.70,0:12:21.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孤独使人空虚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.74,0:12:24.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要令JoJo变成一个无力的胆小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.93,0:12:27.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后一样一样从他手上抢走一切
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.11,0:12:32.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到我成人的时候 他的一切都是我的
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,========B Part========
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.46,0:12:37.79,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的迪奥
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.62,0:12:42.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真惨 感觉我的领地慢慢被侵略了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.54,0:12:44.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦 快走
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.26,0:12:47.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你们去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.49,0:12:49.72,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来这边吧 一起玩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.40,0:12:54.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那边的怪东西在说话呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.87,0:12:57.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无视无视 他会告状的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.47,0:13:01.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么 站住 你说谁告状了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.96,0:13:02.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.08,0:13:04.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爱告状的JoJo
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.73,0:13:08.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟他玩的话 有什么事都让他给广播了 傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.29,0:13:13.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,站住 回来啊 我什么时候告状过什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.48,0:13:16.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爱告状的JoJo 哈哈哈！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.63,0:13:18.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥 是迪奥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.03,0:13:21.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是他散布中伤我的谣言
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.03,0:13:25.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么迪奥老是害我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.77,0:13:32.94,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 迪奥 迪奥…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.67,0:13:38.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自从他到了家里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.30,0:13:40.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的生活就一团糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.54,0:13:41.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好孤独
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.79,0:13:45.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼 无论迪奥做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.72,0:13:48.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,唯有你仍然是我的朋友呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.26,0:14:04.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的女孩子是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.77,0:14:07.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感觉在哪里见过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.61,0:14:11.12,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是我的手帕
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.81,0:14:15.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 谢谢你的葡萄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.88,0:14:19.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我明天也在这里 你也来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.16,0:14:27.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一声不吭的 女孩子真可爱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.30,0:14:33.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恋爱！这份美妙的好奇心驱动着JoJo
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.01,0:14:36.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们很快就成为了朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.18,0:14:38.25,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo爱上了她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.78,0:14:41.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾莉娜 艾莉娜·班鲁多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.83,0:14:43.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她真是太可爱了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.55,0:14:47.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo你在刻什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.88,0:14:52.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 JoJo真讨厌 不理你了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.36,0:14:57.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.65,0:15:15.70,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哟 你叫艾莉娜吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.12,0:15:19.15,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好像跟JoJo很要好嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.27,0:15:22.03,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就觉得奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.63,0:15:26.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他本应该很沮丧的 最近却很得意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.41,0:15:27.92,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.04,0:15:36.34,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做…做了！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.13,0:15:40.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是迪奥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.46,0:15:43.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们做不到的事情 他能面不改色地办到
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.32,0:15:46.46,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是这点叫人拜服 叫人仰慕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.41,0:15:49.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你已经跟JoJo亲过了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.63,0:15:52.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还没吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.72,0:15:55.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的第一次不是给JoJo了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.41,0:15:56.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而是我迪奥！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.47,0:16:03.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,手段不是问题 只要达成强吻的结果就够了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.20,0:16:06.63,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样她跟JoJo的关系也完了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.12,0:16:10.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让JoJo身边存在朋友和恋人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.51,0:16:12.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看…看！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.81,0:16:14.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这人究竟…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.39,0:16:17.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这人究竟在想什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.81,0:16:19.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在用泥水擦嘴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.45,0:16:22.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,脑子有问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.35,0:16:24.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没多远就是条河啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.71,0:16:26.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这…这个女人！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.52,0:16:30.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,故意用泥水擦嘴来向我示威吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.23,0:16:41.27,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 我迪奥竟然被一个女人折了威风…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.66,0:16:44.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,够了 走
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.77,0:16:50.54,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 艾莉娜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.26,0:16:57.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾…艾莉娜 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.82,0:17:00.86,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有点奇怪 究竟发生什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.24,0:17:06.20,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看吧 JoJo那副可怜的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.20,0:17:10.22,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 去告诉他吧 为什么她那样对他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.69,0:17:15.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才不要呢 我可不想看到JoJo伤心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.24,0:17:22.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们… 对艾莉娜…对艾莉娜做什么了！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.95,0:17:29.49,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.06,0:17:38.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还真会…随便…叫别人的名字啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.52,0:17:39.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不可饶恕
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.04,0:17:42.69,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不为你陷害我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.85,0:17:44.78,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我自己无所谓！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.78,0:17:46.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦 那么你是知道了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.05,0:17:48.87,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那位心爱的艾莉娜的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.05,0:17:52.53,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后想用拳头报复我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.80,0:17:55.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我绝不允许任何对她的侮辱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.37,0:17:58.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太丑陋了！你那妒忌的样子！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.26,0:18:03.37,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又想我像上次拳击那样修理你吗 蠢材
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.96,0:18:09.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打…打不过
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.02,0:18:11.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是现在认输的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.00,0:18:15.96,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以后就要一辈子在迪奥的阴影下苟且过活
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.29,0:18:21.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,更重要的是 我必须为了挽回艾莉娜的名誉而战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.21,0:18:27.14,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就打到你认输为止 而且要堂堂正正地！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.29,0:18:31.60,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以这样的方式 把赢不了我迪奥的事实
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.89,0:18:34.41,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,深深地烙印在JoJo自己的身体上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.75,0:18:37.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无论是打架还是人生！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.12,0:18:39.81,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.99,0:18:46.38,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好！这触感真好！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.67,0:18:48.98,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这…这家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.09,0:18:51.31,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃了我的膝撞反而抓住我了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.88,0:18:53.64,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还想吃一发吗！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.68,0:19:01.16,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪～奥～！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.76,0:19:05.39,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要打到你哭出来！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.20,0:19:08.71,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}这样…这样…这样的渣滓究竟把我…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.02,0:19:30.28,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然…竟然…竟然对我…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.05,0:19:32.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哭…哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.07,0:19:35.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这个卑鄙的笨蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.67,0:19:38.51,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.05,0:19:40.68,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.32,0:19:44.95,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,男子汉打架很平常
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.13,0:19:48.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 JoJo 刚才看来是你单方面
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.21,0:19:51.82,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,殴打已经没有反抗之力的迪奥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.96,0:19:53.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不是绅士的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.89,0:19:54.11,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.01,0:19:55.05,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用辩解
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.21,0:19:57.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩都回房间去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.00,0:20:00.33,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,待会再惩罚你们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.28,0:20:11.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么箱子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.98,0:20:13.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘛 不管了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.80,0:20:16.07,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是哪个女佣扔的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.84,0:20:28.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 这撞击的声音是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.23,0:20:31.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,难道…里面有人！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.14,0:20:36.09,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕了 被活活烧死了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.15,0:20:42.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾莉娜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.15,0:20:44.76,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 迪奥！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.04,0:20:48.29,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你那肮脏的吻是为了拆散我们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.38,0:20:50.48,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你得到绝佳的效果了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.82,0:20:58.80,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,实在死得太惨了 不忍心让你看到就先埋葬了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.38,0:21:05.06,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,据警察说 大概是小偷为了干掉看门狗…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.55,0:21:06.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.82,0:21:10.67,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,迪奥少爷？他还没从学校回来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.36,0:21:16.36,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo回到自己的房间 睡了两个小时
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.80,0:21:20.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后 醒过来没多久后
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.67,0:21:25.19,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想起丹尼的死 他哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.49,0:21:29.84,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干掉了那条蠢狗 算是出了口气
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.93,0:21:32.24,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但没想到JoJo能有那么强大的爆发力
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.27,0:21:33.58,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太小看他了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.97,0:21:37.04,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是那种越是压迫就越会成长的类型
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.68,0:21:41.90,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的缺点是太易动怒了 要好好反省
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.22,0:21:47.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要学会冷静地控制自己的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.32,0:21:51.93,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而后 七载的岁月过去了
Comment: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,========Ending========
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.21,0:22:07.53,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}I'll be the roundabout
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.82,0:22:11.42,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}The words will make you out 'n' out
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.43,0:22:16.75,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}I spend the day your way
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.75,0:22:24.01,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}Call it morning driving thru the sound and in and out the valley
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.30,0:22:34.59,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}The music dance and sing
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.92,0:22:38.43,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}They make the children really ring
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.48,0:22:43.88,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}I spend the day your way
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.88,0:22:50.45,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}Call it morning driving thru the sound and in and out the valley
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.45,0:22:53.11,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}In and around the lake
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.16,0:22:58.27,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}Mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.24,0:23:05.03,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.66,0:23:11.46,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.15,0:23:20.70,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\blur3}Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be there with you
Comment: 0,0:00:00.50,0:00:00.50,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,========Trailer========
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.37,0:23:29.59,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,七年过去了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.09,0:23:33.43,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,690)\fad(0,1600)}乔纳森·乔斯达抢到球了！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.78,0:23:35.23,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,690)\fad(300,1000)}我想象到一副非常恐怖的景象
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.26,0:23:37.08,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,690)\fad(300,320)}你说就算失去四根手指也在所不惜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.76,0:23:37.97,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,690)\fad(300,300)}你会失去我们的友情的！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.81,0:23:40.61,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,690)\fad(300,0)}我要保护父亲 保护乔斯达家
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.48,0:23:42.48,Title,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,560)\i1\blur4}第2话 「来自过去的书信」
