[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2009-12-26 04:07:30
; // 版本: 0.76
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 歡迎訪問漫遊天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:Stand_Alone_Complex
Original Script: 未設定
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1920
PlayResY:1080
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: oped,Arial Unicode MS,90,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: Default,Arial Unicode MS,90,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: logo,Arial Unicode MS,90,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: SP,Arial Unicode MS,90,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.22,0:00:08.09,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Ангелы и демоны кружили надо мной
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.00,0:00:14.40,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Разбивали тернии и звёздные пути
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.40,0:00:20.18,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Не знает счастья только тотж
;靈
;風
;工
;作
;室
;
;www.fosky.com/bbs
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.18,0:00:26.71,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Кто его зова понять не смог
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.30,0:00:54.22,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}I am Calling…Calling now…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.30,0:01:01.22,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Spirits rise and falling
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.22,0:01:06.39,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Собой остаться дольше
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.39,0:01:11.17,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Calling…Calling…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.39,0:01:18.47,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}in the depth of longing
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.47,0:01:26.13,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Собой остаться дольше
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.62,0:23:19.55,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}she's so cold and human
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.85,0:23:23.02,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}it's something humans do
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.79,0:23:26.16,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}she stays so golden solo
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.16,0:23:28.49,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}she's so number nine
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.03,0:23:31.40,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}she's incredible math
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.97,0:23:35.30,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}just incredible math
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.57,0:23:39.73,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}and is she really human
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.81,0:23:42.97,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}she's just so something new
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.88,0:23:46.21,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}a waking lithium flower
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.21,0:23:48.54,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}just about to bloom
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.08,0:23:51.11,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}I smell lithium now
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.92,0:23:55.39,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}smelling lithium now
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.06,0:24:00.96,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}how is she when she doesn't surf
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.13,0:24:05.03,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}how is she when she doesn't surf
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.20,0:24:08.00,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}how is she when she doesn't surf
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.00,0:24:11.37,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}I wonder what she does when she wakes up?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.41,0:24:15.50,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}when she wakes up
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.59,0:01:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿著紅鞋的女孩…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.80,0:01:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被外國人帶走了…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.84,0:01:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊，巴特先生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.85,0:01:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們幾個，知道這首歌的意思嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.55,0:02:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭啦，當然知道囉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.69,0:02:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是女孩子被帶到外國去對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.66,0:02:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親為了去開墾
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.30,0:02:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才把她交給外籍的神父養啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.50,0:02:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.67,0:02:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親情輸給了貧窮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.13,0:02:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯，沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.54,0:02:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉呀呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.87,0:02:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們好像要被送去實驗室了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.94,0:02:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就再見了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.85,0:02:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.79,0:02:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「心的破綻 Ag2O」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.43,0:02:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.77,0:02:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關於縣警公安部請求協助臥底調查的案子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.07,0:02:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出發的手續已經完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.58,0:03:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是我的新履歷啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.25,0:03:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與有間諜嫌疑而成為跟蹤監視對象的帕布羅·柴瑟夫接觸
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.89,0:03:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找出唆使他進行間諜活動的人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.43,0:03:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後逮捕兩方面人馬
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.76,0:03:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外正在出席國際恐怖主義對策協調會的課長
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.90,0:03:21.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在18分鐘前要我轉告說
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.53,0:03:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「在他從英國回來之前處理好」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.08,0:03:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大我問你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.48,0:03:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.28,0:03:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很在意塔奇克馬要被送去實驗室的事嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.08,0:03:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼這麼問？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.09,0:03:41.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事…要是不在意就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.79,0:03:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才用不著你替我操心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.52,0:03:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也沒有在擔心什麼啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.96,0:03:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼看你都心不在焉的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.86,0:03:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不見得哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.70,0:03:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我可是這個柴瑟夫的頭號拳迷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.54,0:03:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拳迷？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.94,0:04:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先別管這個，等我到了基地之後\N要好好把這輛車開回9課去喔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.94,0:04:06.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.65,0:04:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不會開這種車去兜風呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.83,0:04:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來，來…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.70,0:04:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更認真一點打過來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.34,0:04:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不只這樣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.41,0:04:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底聽說過什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.04,0:04:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是還少了那麼一點可信度
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.88,0:04:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.35,0:04:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好，既然對我這麼懷疑的話
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.81,0:04:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就用全力來打倒我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.92,0:04:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他這麼說耶
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.82,0:04:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就成全他，好好給他一拳
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.76,0:04:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好，放馬過來
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.36,0:04:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.01,0:05:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼啦？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.51,0:05:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有你嘴巴上說的那麼強嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.31,0:05:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腦震盪了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.18,0:05:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是沒用
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.91,0:05:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂，怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.18,0:05:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弟兄被幹掉，你們不會不甘心嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.75,0:05:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來打倒我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.45,0:05:21.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.79,0:05:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有人敢過來挑戰嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.86,0:05:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們這群膽小鬼！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.59,0:05:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就讓我來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.56,0:05:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從你臉上的表情看來，你應該不是菜鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.07,0:05:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.34,0:05:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本來想翹掉這次無聊透頂的聯合訓練呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.68,0:05:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是聽說你最近調來這裡擔任格鬥技教官
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.48,0:05:52.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才特地出席的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.45,0:05:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可別讓我失望哦，銀牌選手
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.42,0:05:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼久以前的事情你還記得啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.66,0:05:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.06,0:06:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用拳擊來玩玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.24,0:06:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.21,0:06:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連我的打法都徹底研究過了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.46,0:06:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來你的拳頭還沒死嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.98,0:06:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.69,0:07:09.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂，你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.67,0:07:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼回事…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.53,0:07:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打中了你義體的破綻
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.94,0:07:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還以為贏了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.71,0:07:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我蠻欣賞你的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.41,0:07:26.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的想知道為什麼會輸的話，就來我家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.31,0:07:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會詳細說明給你聽的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.32,0:07:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我巡迴各個基地教授格鬥技巧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.19,0:07:44.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就只剩那一點點而已了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.20,0:07:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.23,0:07:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種數量不能說是「一點點」吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.80,0:07:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.67,0:07:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打過這麼多大賽
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.87,0:07:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾乎都拿冠軍
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.61,0:07:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是冠軍的只有那個
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.35,0:08:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這場比賽我有去看…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.72,0:08:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很吃驚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.39,0:08:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我從來沒想過你會輸
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.39,0:08:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己都很吃驚呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.96,0:08:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為那場唯一的敗績
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.90,0:08:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全打亂了我的人生規劃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.13,0:08:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直討好我的新聞媒體，還有義體的製造商
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.20,0:08:24.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都離我而去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.40,0:08:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個時候…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.94,0:08:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你沒有攻擊義體的破綻呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.48,0:08:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有那場比賽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.68,0:08:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到現在想起來還是無法接受
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.08,0:08:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,義體的…破綻嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.72,0:08:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯，義體的破綻
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.25,0:08:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白天那招就是這個手法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.19,0:08:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是為了聽那個才來這裡的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.86,0:08:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個呀…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.73,0:08:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實那個是有一點小秘密的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.16,0:08:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來你們今晚談得挺投機的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.53,0:08:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊，你好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.87,0:09:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們在說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.74,0:09:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我也加入吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.91,0:09:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂，你要用那種東西招待客人嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.32,0:09:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該還有更貴的酒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.38,0:09:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀，東西又不是貴就是好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.22,0:09:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,招待客人，心意最重要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.62,0:09:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本沒搞懂…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.59,0:09:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂，我們出去喝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.83,0:09:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道附近有家店會拿好酒出來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.87,0:09:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.10,0:09:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又不介意喝這個啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.50,0:09:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別這麼說啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.17,0:09:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我請客
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.21,0:09:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.25,0:09:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有緊急通訊進來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.88,0:09:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我馬上回來，等我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.05,0:09:48.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.45,0:09:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為難得今天他心情那麼好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.19,0:09:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想說拿「梅多布哈」來助興
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.89,0:09:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果好像惹他生氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.63,0:09:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅多布哈？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.76,0:10:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我們家鄉每個家庭都會釀製的自製酒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.97,0:10:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道合不合你的口味？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.58,0:10:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好甜
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.11,0:10:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然囉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.41,0:10:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為那是用蜂蜜發酵釀成的呀
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.99,0:10:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起來是個非常好的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.25,0:10:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結婚了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.46,0:10:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，結是結了…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.99,0:10:27.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一個小孩，馬上就要六歲了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.16,0:10:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.69,0:10:30.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真看不出來耶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.70,0:10:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思，有緊急的事情要辦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.80,0:10:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們下次再去喝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.60,0:10:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到時候再繼續聊那個話題
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.80,0:10:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊，真可惜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.87,0:10:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再來玩哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.11,0:10:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，過幾天我再來打擾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.45,0:10:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.55,0:10:48.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.29,0:10:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你久等，我讓客人回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.56,0:10:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.66,0:11:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼傳給你下一個指示
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.85,0:12:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊，教官好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.66,0:12:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂，巴特還沒來嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.86,0:12:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.43,0:12:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…昨天的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.96,0:12:12.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒看到他的人耶
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.03,0:12:16.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎？那傢伙在這裡很出名嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.34,0:12:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.44,0:12:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他應該是昨天進港的「三雲」號上面103航空隊的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.21,0:12:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找我有事嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.71,0:12:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.61,0:12:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要去吃個飯？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.81,0:12:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃飯？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.05,0:12:32.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起吃飯我現在比較想洗個澡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.42,0:12:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.72,0:12:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就自己去吃好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.82,0:12:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶著拳套去吃飯嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.69,0:12:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可別讓我失望哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.55,0:13:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.52,0:13:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.29,0:13:13.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拜託的簽名
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.83,0:13:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得簽在這上面比簽在紙板上好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.73,0:13:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.86,0:13:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我侄子一定會很高興的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.50,0:13:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.50,0:13:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了，我買了不錯的咖啡豆
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.07,0:13:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就讓我請你喝一杯當做謝禮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.47,0:13:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別麻煩了，我也得快點回去才行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.34,0:13:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就煮好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.58,0:13:35.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顆粒磨粗一點可以嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.41,0:13:36.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個嘛…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.82,0:13:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記得你有一個金屬濾網
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.45,0:13:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就磨粗一點好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.16,0:13:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.56,0:13:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.77,0:13:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦，佐川公司的替身防壁嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.70,0:14:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用的東西不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.24,0:14:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了，現在不是有從其他地方過來做聯合訓練的人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.75,0:14:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是說搭航空母艦進港的海軍隊員？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.89,0:14:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.05,0:14:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天那邊有個傢伙到體育館來了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.86,0:14:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是個相當有骨氣的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.86,0:14:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.09,0:14:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，很有前途
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.99,0:14:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是很好嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.13,0:14:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能成為朋友嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.63,0:14:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就難說了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.30,0:14:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我這個人比較怕生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.67,0:14:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,設了雙重防壁，他還真是小心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.74,0:14:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手法是先將資料移轉到這裡，然後再送到外面去嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.81,0:14:41.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算傳送到哪裡去呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.65,0:14:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.22,0:14:49.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道有人竊聽
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.16,0:14:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡！就剩一點點而已…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.17,0:15:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.87,0:15:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起，突然想起有急事要辦！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.27,0:15:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂，喂
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.01,0:15:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在消滅證據上未免花了太多時間吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.45,0:15:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣真的能當間諜嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.22,0:15:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢吞吞的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.32,0:15:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧，到底要傳送到哪裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.16,0:15:30.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.90,0:15:35.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我問你們
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.90,0:15:37.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有誰跑進我的房間嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.40,0:15:40.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有人進去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.03,0:16:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「豆子」怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.60,0:16:10.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經磨好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.77,0:16:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那為什麼不過濾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.07,0:16:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感覺到有人在竊聽
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.74,0:16:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了以防萬一，那個過濾式咖啡機不要再使用了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.81,0:16:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有可能已經被污染了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.85,0:16:23.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，我會改到其他地方過濾
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.18,0:16:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豆子就先放到罐子裡面等
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.62,0:16:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過幾天告訴你送貨地點
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.05,0:16:29.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是身邊出現不熟悉的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.55,0:16:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千萬要小心
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.33,0:16:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不熟悉的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.51,0:16:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂，巴特
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.44,0:16:52.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚我一定請客
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.68,0:16:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陪我喝一杯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.88,0:16:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊不會有甜酒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.32,0:17:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這家店不錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.96,0:17:07.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自從到這裡上任
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.16,0:17:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒見到過什麼像樣的人物
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.19,0:17:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以幾乎都是在這裡消磨時間
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.83,0:17:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.40,0:17:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是你頭一次坐在包廂呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.63,0:17:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，總算可以交到朋友了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.50,0:17:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.11,0:17:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.68,0:17:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說你結過婚了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.55,0:17:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該有帶著老婆的照片吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.61,0:17:29.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借我看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.82,0:17:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是那種類型的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.32,0:17:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.76,0:17:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這酒很貴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.42,0:17:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太浪費了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.86,0:17:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.89,0:17:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以幫我借塊抹布過來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.83,0:17:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.11,0:17:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那種類型嗎…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.98,0:18:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是個難懂的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.55,0:18:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我馬上拿過去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.92,0:18:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝啦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.39,0:18:11.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他說等一下會拿過來
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.96,0:18:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.76,0:18:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又有人找我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.90,0:18:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思，請你暫時一個人…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.67,0:18:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.94,0:18:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起來跟情報部一樣忙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.10,0:18:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罐子呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.46,0:18:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帶來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.97,0:18:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冷啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.51,0:19:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂，這是什麼東西？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.18,0:19:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你竟然只抓到了一堆數字
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.25,0:19:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.48,0:19:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是照你們的指示，抓資料出來而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.59,0:19:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,內容不對是你們自己指示錯誤吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.76,0:19:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對你太失望了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.09,0:19:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要囉嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.86,0:19:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請你把該付的錢給我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.46,0:19:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難看死了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.20,0:19:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.26,0:19:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被跟蹤了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.17,0:19:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…情報部？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.24,0:19:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不對…是監察部的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.51,0:19:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了秘密調查我，故意假裝是我的拳迷來接近我？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.15,0:19:44.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全被騙了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.12,0:19:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連我的過去也都研究過了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.35,0:19:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的目的是錢嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.59,0:19:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說你的人生規劃亂掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.82,0:19:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不認為你有過得那麼慘啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.79,0:19:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂什麼！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.13,0:20:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逮捕你之前我想問你一個問題
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.00,0:20:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是關於「義體的破綻」這件事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.10,0:20:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎？那件事還沒跟你說過啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.07,0:20:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.47,0:20:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能再一次打中義體的破綻，並且把我撂倒的話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.41,0:20:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就放你一條生路
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.05,0:20:15.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瞧不起我？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.31,0:20:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管打多少次，你都打不贏我的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.08,0:20:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此你就快點下來啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.82,0:20:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會後悔把槍收起來的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.19,0:20:30.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少說大話，給我放馬過來！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.67,0:20:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要比義體輸出功率的話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.34,0:20:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是贏不了我的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.70,0:21:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙…昨天是故意輸給我的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.37,0:21:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已經生銹到連對手是不是故意的都搞不清楚了？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.61,0:21:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.58,0:21:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時候也是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.58,0:21:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心裡有破綻的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.88,0:21:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.84,0:21:52.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.54,0:21:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能再見到你真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.28,0:21:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒跟我丈夫一起嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.11,0:21:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.65,0:21:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到半路上還是一起的，不過…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.82,0:22:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.05,0:22:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那正好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.05,0:22:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許不合你的胃口
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.09,0:22:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過這是送給你太太的…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.87,0:22:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？老大
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.27,0:22:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任務結束啦？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.74,0:22:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.94,0:22:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.34,0:22:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任務都已經解決了，怎麼還跟出發前一個樣啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.75,0:22:30.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看起來是那樣的嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.18,0:22:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.59,0:22:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.49,0:22:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.00,0:22:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽的！


