[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2009-12-25 20:16:44
; // 版本: 0.76
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 歡迎訪問漫遊天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:Stand_Alone_Complex
Original Script: 未設定
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1920
PlayResY:1080
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: oped,Arial Unicode MS,90,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: Default,Arial Unicode MS,90,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: logo,Arial Unicode MS,90,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1
Style: SP,Arial Unicode MS,90,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.32,0:00:08.19,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Ангелы и демоны кружили надо мной
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.10,0:00:14.50,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Разбивали тернии и звёздные пути
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.50,0:00:20.28,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Не знает счастья только тотж
;靈
;風
;工
;作
;室
;
;www.fosky.com/bbs
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.28,0:00:26.81,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Кто его зова понять не смог
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.40,0:00:54.32,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}I am Calling…Calling now…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.40,0:01:01.32,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Spirits rise and falling
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.32,0:01:06.49,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Собой остаться дольше
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.49,0:01:11.27,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Calling…Calling…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.49,0:01:18.57,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}in the depth of longing
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.57,0:01:26.23,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Собой остаться дольше
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.72,0:23:19.65,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}she's so cold and human
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.95,0:23:23.12,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}it's something humans do
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.89,0:23:26.26,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}she stays so golden solo
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.26,0:23:28.59,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}she's so number nine
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.13,0:23:31.50,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}she's incredible math
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.07,0:23:35.40,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}just incredible math
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.67,0:23:39.83,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}and is she really human
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.91,0:23:43.07,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}she's just so something new
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.98,0:23:46.31,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}a waking lithium flower
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.31,0:23:48.64,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}just about to bloom
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.18,0:23:51.21,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}I smell lithium now
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.02,0:23:55.49,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}smelling lithium now
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.16,0:24:01.06,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}how is she when she doesn't surf
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.23,0:24:05.13,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}how is she when she doesn't surf
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.30,0:24:08.10,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}how is she when she doesn't surf
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.10,0:24:11.47,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}I wonder what she does when she wakes up?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.51,0:24:15.60,oped,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}when she wakes up
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.73,0:01:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想做什麼啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.00,0:01:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要給那些傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.70,0:01:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖的感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.57,0:01:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了這個目的，就算地球上少了一個人類…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.77,0:01:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也沒什麼大不了的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.61,0:02:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「適合在密林航行的日子」
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.45,0:02:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被害者人數不明…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.12,0:02:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在確定人數之後…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.13,0:02:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉，我們是公安九課
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.60,0:02:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們應該有接到聯絡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.22,0:02:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特，狀況如何？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.09,0:02:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腐爛得很嚴重
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.82,0:02:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是老經驗的檢察官，也很難只看外表就下判斷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.06,0:02:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是！我是在問你覺得怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.83,0:02:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.66,0:02:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猜中了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.54,0:03:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真噁心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.74,0:03:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才勸你用螢幕看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.64,0:03:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特，已經夠了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.81,0:03:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戶草，繼續
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.98,0:03:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這二個月間
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.61,0:03:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在市區裡發生五起兇殺案
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.72,0:03:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加上今天一家四口總共六件，合計12人遇害
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.59,0:03:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每個被害者都有個共通點
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.39,0:03:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是上半身皮膚都被以T-Shirt形狀剝離
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.83,0:03:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根據驗屍結果
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.13,0:03:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被害者活生生被剝下皮膚後
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.03,0:03:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那樣棄置不管的可能性極高
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.53,0:03:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是個神經病
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.17,0:03:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,縣警的測寫員怎麼說
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.64,0:03:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有什麼表示
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.91,0:03:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有沒有可能是無政府主義者的恐怖攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.17,0:03:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是新興宗教的儀式？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.58,0:03:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.01,0:03:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能是政治或宗教性質的組織犯罪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.98,0:03:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就從性犯罪前科犯的名單著手
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.82,0:03:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兇手的性癖好不是問題所在
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.56,0:03:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙在這種犯罪行為中得不到絲毫快感
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.73,0:03:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你能夠肯定？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.73,0:04:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要說這裡面有什麼的話，那就是「義務感」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.67,0:04:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有那樣的連續殺人案嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.30,0:04:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然叫我們過來，應該有什麼隱情吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.21,0:04:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,課長
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.08,0:04:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬可·亞莫雷迪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.61,0:04:20.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前美帝海軍中士
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.85,0:04:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根據美帝所提供的資料
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.59,0:04:27.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次的嫌犯非常有可能是這個人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.72,0:04:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,國防省的資料顯示
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.12,0:04:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個人在大戰中轉戰各地
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.66,0:04:34.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留下為數不少的戰績
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.10,0:04:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但2028年3月以「志願退伍」的方式退役
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.34,0:04:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其後就下落不明瞭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.71,0:04:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有何根據證明這個男人就是嫌犯？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.34,0:04:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,據說他曾經捲入某個非常相似的案子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.91,0:04:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常相似的案子？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.78,0:04:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.88,0:04:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,課長
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.35,0:04:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然對那傢伙已經瞭解得這麼清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.95,0:04:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該已經下令通緝了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.35,0:05:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.76,0:05:03.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,CIA今天剛透過外交部
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.19,0:05:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要求這次的殺人犯要秘密逮捕並且無條件引渡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.23,0:05:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請等一下…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.63,0:05:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這很明顯是干預內政了耶
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.20,0:05:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更何況我們幹嘛幫CIA擦屁股
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.74,0:05:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別這樣嘛。這一點無論如何請多擔待
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.94,0:05:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來介紹一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.11,0:05:25.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這位是從美帝來的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.25,0:05:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是CIA的佐籐鈴木
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.38,0:05:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是渡邊田中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.08,0:05:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們好，請多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.72,0:05:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們好，請多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.80,0:05:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把這個散佈到敵方陣地去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.11,0:05:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次可是最棒、最夠勁的喔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.78,0:06:05.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被發現前好像被鳥啄過
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.35,0:06:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地面上有打鬥的痕跡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.19,0:06:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然已經請縣警削下表面的泥土帶回警局
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.93,0:06:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但還是沒有可以追蹤嫌犯的線索
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.43,0:06:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.97,0:06:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說這裡下個月就要開始施工了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.77,0:06:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,案件現場會消失掉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.30,0:06:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會讓他逍遙法外那麼久的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.28,0:06:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鶴見台…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.94,0:06:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有鶴嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.75,0:06:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鶴已經沒有了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.75,0:06:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全剩些烏鴉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.02,0:06:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.49,0:06:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以問你一件事嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.96,0:06:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次的案子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.29,0:06:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是隱瞞了些事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.99,0:06:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔…我對這個也有興趣耶
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.86,0:06:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好，當我找到那傢伙的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.43,0:06:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就得永別人世
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.17,0:06:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好記住
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.17,0:06:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說話像演戲一樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.19,0:07:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特…巴特…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.86,0:07:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.03,0:07:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.83,0:07:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂！別隨便偷窺別人的腦袋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.53,0:07:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天一點都不像你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.10,0:07:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會是發燒了吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.94,0:07:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖說老大應該跟這種問題無緣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.17,0:07:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戶草，這是密碼通訊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.41,0:07:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不動聲色聽我說
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.38,0:07:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,處理這件案子的期間
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.11,0:07:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果巴特有失控的行為
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.88,0:07:42.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由你來制止他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.89,0:07:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真難喝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.82,0:07:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有比冷掉的罐裝咖啡更能讓人清醒的東西了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.56,0:07:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特和嫌犯之間有什麼過節嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.26,0:07:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.56,0:07:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但好像和平常的精神狀態不太一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.13,0:07:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的確
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.47,0:08:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了，我會盡力而為
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.80,0:08:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…沒放咖啡因
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.24,0:08:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難喝就閉上嘴做點預習工作
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.34,0:08:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交給你了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.08,0:08:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞭解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.88,0:08:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個案子我瞭解了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.02,0:08:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會退出偵查工作
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.35,0:08:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與檢察官那邊的交涉，就拜託你們了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.36,0:08:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是當然
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.56,0:08:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是若讓CIA押走嫌犯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.03,0:08:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個案子就會成為懸案
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.97,0:08:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下就是怎麼讓第一線人員接受了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.60,0:08:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉，那也是工作的一部份
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.00,0:08:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之，這個案子就麻煩了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.31,0:08:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊，你好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.91,0:08:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少校
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.08,0:08:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟石川一起去探探這小子的底
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.35,0:08:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞭解
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.62,0:08:50.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渡邊…田中先生？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.32,0:08:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.86,0:08:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,部長
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.49,0:08:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請快到搜查本部來
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.53,0:09:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在開會
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.93,0:09:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發現直接記錄犯罪現場的影像
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.30,0:09:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.93,0:09:07.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪裡發現的？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.34,0:09:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們被放在新濱市秋葉原無線電大道的錄影帶店裡出售
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.27,0:09:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帕茲、博馬，火速趕往電器街
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.91,0:09:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盤問一下錄影帶店老闆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.11,0:09:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入侵IR系統徹查一下記錄看看
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.25,0:09:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞭解
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.22,0:09:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,課長
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.65,0:09:24.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯，你也發現了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.95,0:09:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渡邊好像早就料到了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.40,0:09:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好有趣的地方喔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.54,0:09:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像可以提升經驗值耶
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.08,0:09:50.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可沒有閒功夫逛街喔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.11,0:09:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是！
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.92,0:09:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帕茲負責調查周邊的商店
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.65,0:09:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博馬盤問老闆
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.02,0:10:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,查出影片進貨的途徑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.12,0:10:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞭解
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.32,0:10:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓出從昨天到現在所有客人的影像
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.46,0:10:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞭解
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.46,0:10:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少校，能不能想點辦法？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.13,0:10:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣下去，我根本沒辦法好好敲後門啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.17,0:10:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是打算監視我們吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.07,0:10:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不被信任啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.07,0:10:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才要去敲後門嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.34,0:10:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定有什麼隱情
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.04,0:10:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渡邊先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.14,0:10:23.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轄區警方沒收的影像，好像已經到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.28,0:10:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要看嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.35,0:10:26.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好，就這麼辦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.11,0:10:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼請到那邊的放映室去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.02,0:10:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…那邊嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.95,0:10:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的就交給你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.96,0:10:35.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.15,0:11:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畜生！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.28,0:11:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙幹嘛故意把這種資料散佈出來呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.72,0:11:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為對那傢伙而言，這就是他的目的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.46,0:11:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對吧？佐籐先生
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.59,0:11:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.30,0:11:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來9課之前曾待過游擊隊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.73,0:11:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也有潛伏在南美叢林的經驗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.00,0:11:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喔…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.74,0:11:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你的經歷，跟這個資料有什麼關係呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.01,0:11:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少裝蒜了！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.34,0:11:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事在你們美帝撤退後還一直在進行喔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.18,0:11:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而現在
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.72,0:11:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個惡夢又再度出現在我眼前
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.72,0:11:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惡夢？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.48,0:12:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個是？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.48,0:12:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是將犯人的視覺情報傳給被害人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.39,0:12:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是讓被害人親眼看著自己活生生的被人剝皮？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.63,0:12:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.76,0:12:24.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好殘忍
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.67,0:12:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來六個案子的影像都有
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.14,0:12:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石川，有發現什麼嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.71,0:12:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…真不愧是CIA
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.48,0:12:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然防壁很硬
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.18,0:12:40.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過在影像資料庫裡殘留了幾份記錄
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.78,0:12:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,CIA的檔案裡留有不少
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.75,0:12:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由心理分析師所寫關於馬可的報告書
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.29,0:12:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那裡面沒有更深入的情報嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.13,0:12:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…等等、等等
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.76,0:12:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼檔案
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.26,0:12:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日落計劃？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.18,0:13:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日落計劃
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.71,0:13:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你說不知道，那就讓我告訴你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.78,0:13:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在先前的大戰中，為了使敵國喪失戰鬥意志
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.55,0:13:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由CIA所想出的作戰計劃
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.46,0:13:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓工作人員潛入敵方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.26,0:13:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和當地人混熟了以後
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.60,0:13:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用盡所有可能的殘酷手法殺害女人和小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.53,0:13:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落日計劃就是這個游擊戰的代號
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.34,0:13:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也叫作戰？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.37,0:13:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.64,0:13:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣的計劃並不存在
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.88,0:13:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我國的官方看法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.18,0:13:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傳說中執行這個任務的人，很多都患有精神疾病
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.78,0:13:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼那種傢伙會出現在這個城市？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.92,0:13:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事誰也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.39,0:13:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要看看心理分析師，像是占星一樣的報告書？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.26,0:14:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.63,0:14:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙的戰爭還沒有結束
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.24,0:14:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我的也是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.68,0:14:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然曾聽過傳聞
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.38,0:14:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來真的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.81,0:14:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過如果他的目的是「使敵人喪失戰鬥意志」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.25,0:14:25.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要他待在這個對他人生死漠不關心的國家
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.19,0:14:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬可的犯行就停不下來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.82,0:14:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少校
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.46,0:14:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬可是透過住在無線電大道附近公園的遊民
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.26,0:14:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四處兜售殺人影片
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.30,0:14:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在傳送剛沒收的第七件案子的檔案
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.47,0:14:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說第七件？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.50,0:14:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一位被害者已經出現了？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.50,0:14:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也馬上傳到這邊的終端機來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.55,0:14:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你…不要啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.41,0:14:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要…啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.52,0:14:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡！這次換成被害人的視覺情報嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.95,0:15:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博馬，原始檔案上有建檔的日期時間嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.42,0:15:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是昨天晚上！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.76,0:15:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用聲紋檢索找出被害人的地址。她有可能還活著
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.80,0:15:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不禁覺得她還活著真是一樁慘事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.57,0:15:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在皮膚再生技術很進步
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.58,0:15:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然無法恢復到原來的樣子…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.01,0:15:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這混蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.98,0:15:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣你滿意了吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.65,0:15:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們製造出來的怪物正在完美地執行著任務！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.75,0:15:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我們才來回收他啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.29,0:15:36.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然說是回收…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.62,0:15:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個混蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.56,0:15:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.46,0:15:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算現在勒死這傢伙也沒什麼意義了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.59,0:15:41.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.86,0:15:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次不會再讓他逃走了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.40,0:15:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定讓那傢伙嚥下最後一口氣
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.80,0:15:46.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.53,0:15:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.47,0:15:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你之前好好處理的話
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.27,0:15:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也就不必出面了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.71,0:15:53.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們二個在說些什麼啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.51,0:15:54.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.68,0:15:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪裡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.98,0:15:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙藏身在哪裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.01,0:16:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請我給點意見怎麼樣？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.62,0:16:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是為此才這樣子跟你們一起跑現場
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.29,0:16:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他媽的能出什麼意見！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.29,0:16:09.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.76,0:16:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.63,0:16:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這下面不是有下水道經過嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.33,0:16:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與其說是下水道…不如說是暗渠吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.80,0:16:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗渠？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.77,0:16:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.80,0:16:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被蓋住的河
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.57,0:16:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.51,0:16:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙交資料給遊民的公園底下，也有暗渠通過
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.98,0:16:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟河川的流向一致…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.32,0:16:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙溯至河川的上游犯罪
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.06,0:16:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又為了要散播這些畫面，回到下游的街上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.93,0:16:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說那傢伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.89,0:16:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在我們的腳下！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.40,0:16:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你給我在那等著
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.73,0:16:52.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等會就把屍袋交給你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.94,0:17:04.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果馬可在地下水道移動
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.48,0:17:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那裡當根據地的可能性極高
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.88,0:17:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓博馬他們直接進入下水道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.78,0:17:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用夾擊的方式逮捕他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.02,0:17:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特，我該不該把你剛剛說的話當真？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.59,0:17:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.06,0:17:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,濕氣好重喔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.50,0:17:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光學迷彩的肉眼辨識值會提高耶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.47,0:17:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,密封墊不會被腐蝕吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.47,0:17:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別抱怨了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.67,0:17:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們好歹聞不到氣味吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.71,0:17:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以用感應器分析啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.81,0:17:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,令人不舒服嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.81,0:17:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,博馬兄的不舒服指數68%
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.65,0:17:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.42,0:17:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.62,0:17:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了對付外來的襲擊預先藏的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.06,0:17:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看樣子找對地方了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.92,0:17:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發現藏有槍械
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.43,0:17:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種濕氣、這種水的腐臭味道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.13,0:17:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.46,0:17:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡確實是我們戰鬥過的叢林
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.93,0:18:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一個人在自言自語什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.94,0:18:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂，巴特
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.14,0:18:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.64,0:18:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戶草，巴特怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.61,0:18:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把電子腦通訊給關了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.84,0:18:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老大相當火大喔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.88,0:18:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真的打算幹掉馬可
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.75,0:18:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一個人跟著他恐怕也…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.05,0:18:16.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.08,0:18:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下水道內鋪設的光纖纜線似乎成了障礙
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.92,0:18:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘖，經由自來水公司所使用的中繼站繞道看看
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.53,0:18:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞭解
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.90,0:18:29.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少校
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.03,0:18:33.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從與CIA總部的通訊紀錄中，發現了不得了的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.67,0:18:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些傢伙一開始就沒打算回收馬可
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.87,0:18:40.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下達的命令是要他們假裝發生意外來除掉嫌疑犯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.57,0:18:41.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒說錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.81,0:18:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們知道巴特的過去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.48,0:18:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,CIA那邊也留有巴特的記錄
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.08,0:18:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他游擊隊的時代
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.58,0:18:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛好駐紮在實行日落計劃的現場
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.59,0:18:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圈套？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.62,0:18:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.16,0:18:57.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,利用了我們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.46,0:19:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們一開始就打算利用巴特來消滅馬可
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.06,0:19:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全不懂你們想說什麼耶
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.70,0:19:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.90,0:19:10.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們違法連上CIA這件事本身，才是嚴重的破壞行為
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.74,0:19:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石川，把這傢伙抓起來！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.11,0:19:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍後再讓他把事情說清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.18,0:19:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到巴特那裡去
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.75,0:19:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.78,0:19:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們並沒有做什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.69,0:19:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是無法忘懷叢林的他們
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.75,0:19:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞錯時代和地點的戰爭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.71,0:19:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住了嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.28,0:19:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉，讓他給逃了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.81,0:19:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本來就沒指望你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.78,0:19:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等！別一個人過去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.69,0:20:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴特，你在哪裡？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.54,0:20:19.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬可！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.98,0:20:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該讓它結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.69,0:21:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.79,0:21:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺了我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.63,0:21:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你殺了我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.60,0:21:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.13,0:21:18.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.17,0:21:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用那把刀把我的皮剝下來
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.00,0:21:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你殺了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.37,0:21:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這傢伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.64,0:21:31.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為這樣就可以從任務當中解脫嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.18,0:21:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少天真了！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.05,0:21:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別開槍！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.16,0:21:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.23,0:21:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的戰爭早就結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.30,0:21:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡是5號車
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.50,0:21:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往新濱市的環狀6號道路旁發生204狀況
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.80,0:21:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能夠趕往現場的車輛，請火速趕往現場
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.57,0:22:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛逮捕到連續殺人案的嫌犯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.84,0:22:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確認交給囚車後，立刻趕往現場
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.58,0:22:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞭解
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.35,0:22:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回程的機票只有二人份啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.65,0:22:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑了！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.19,0:22:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉不是給你們馬可的屍袋啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.69,0:22:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你認為我會開槍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.33,0:22:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想洗刷過去污名的迂腐正義感確實掠過腦海
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.34,0:22:32.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然是無法改變的過去，乾脆就這樣帶到墳墓裡去算了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.67,0:22:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡並不是他的叢林，而是我們的城市
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.94,0:22:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何況我是個警官
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.72,0:22:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這次救了一個人不是嗎？


