[Script Info]
Title:龙珠改
Original Script:月光恋曲字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.2,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: zs,方正准圆_GBK,22,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1.2,0,8,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.20,0:00:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仰仗着波波先生的智慧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.34,0:00:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一行人得到了神仙的宇宙飞船
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.69,0:00:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱着一定会有龙珠的信念
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.78,0:00:23.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布尔玛 小林以及悟饭
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.33,0:00:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以那美克星为目标 向着宇宙出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.77,0:02:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新的强敌\N宇宙帝王弗利萨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.46,0:02:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无聊死了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.92,0:02:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真头疼啊 这才第七天
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.76,0:02:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有二十几天呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.58,0:02:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早知道装个长期睡眠装置就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.49,0:02:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们又在做冥想训练啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.88,0:02:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不错 至少可以打发时间
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.25,0:03:44.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.36,0:03:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然很强呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.30,0:03:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有着悟空的血统外加短笛的训练
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.80,0:03:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过小林叔叔的绝招也很多啊 我很佩服
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.25,0:03:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.82,0:03:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你们一直在做冥想修炼是你们的自由
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.89,0:03:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这里很凌乱了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.88,0:04:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不能收拾下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.81,0:04:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里可是有淑女的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.52,0:04:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是乱扔东西的是布尔玛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.57,0:04:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们自己的东西已经收拾好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.21,0:04:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是很忙的哦 还有很多东西要想呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.55,0:04:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们只知道坐着
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.42,0:04:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才还在说无聊呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.06,0:04:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗嗦 对温柔的淑女要体贴
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.39,0:04:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真忙 真忙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.80,0:04:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淑女还穿着内衣走来走去的…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.08,0:04:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.93,0:04:43.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直想问你们
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.29,0:04:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个逃走的赛亚人贝吉塔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.15,0:04:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会跑到哪里去呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.60,0:04:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跑到哪里啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.05,0:04:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赛亚人的星球不是早就毁灭了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.99,0:05:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 他当时伤得非常严重
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.09,0:05:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是前往某些科技发达的星球去了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.54,0:05:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有那种地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.04,0:05:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前孙君的哥哥说过
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.01,0:05:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“我们把环境好的星球上的居民消灭”
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.66,0:05:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,“然后再卖给外星人”
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.98,0:05:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概贝吉塔跑到外星人那里去疗伤了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.46,0:05:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么看来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.30,0:05:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他什么时候再去地球 就要视之间的距离而定了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.29,0:05:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果远的话 时间就会长一些
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.34,0:05:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.64,0:05:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地球真被那个坏蛋盯上了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.05,0:05:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然会这么狼狈
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.43,0:05:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝吉塔离开地球的第18天
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.00,0:06:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 这里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.32,0:06:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有物体靠近
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.27,0:06:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是弗利萨大王吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.35,0:06:12.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.42,0:06:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他刚刚才出去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.70,0:06:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圆形物体 是战斗员
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.50,0:06:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个信号是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.97,0:06:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝吉塔大人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.54,0:06:23.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪 没有收到返回的消息啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.53,0:06:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出什么事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.47,0:06:26.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是观测室
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.81,0:06:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝吉塔大人归来 马上去迎接
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.80,0:06:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.91,0:06:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会只有一架
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.51,0:06:38.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那巴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.57,0:06:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么还不出来…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.16,0:06:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生命反应很弱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.23,0:06:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.60,0:07:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他正在使用生命维持装置
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.69,0:07:04.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好 赶快送去医疗室
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.01,0:07:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.69,0:07:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经治好了 您可以睁开眼睛了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.31,0:07:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真遗憾 尾巴没能再生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.64,0:07:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 迟早会长出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.14,0:08:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来贝吉塔大人碰到了相当厉害的对手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.46,0:08:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连超级防护服都被打烂了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.06,0:08:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好你平安归来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.02,0:08:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不是轻微打击能造成的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.39,0:08:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您在地球上究竟怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.71,0:08:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗利萨大王在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.45,0:08:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在 刚刚出去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.10,0:08:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经厌倦这个星球了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.43,0:08:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.99,0:08:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邱夷大人说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.28,0:08:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您治疗结束后去一下训练室 他有话对你说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.29,0:08:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.60,0:09:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟他没什么好说的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.02,0:09:03.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.58,0:09:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝吉塔大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.34,0:09:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您忘了探测器…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.51,0:09:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送给你了 我不要了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.18,0:09:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天就动身前往地球
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.58,0:09:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定要让他们死无葬身之地
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.56,0:09:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 还是先去那美克星吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.56,0:09:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝吉塔
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.82,0:09:34.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来很狼狈啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.08,0:09:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说拉蒂茨和那巴都死了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.94,0:09:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁这么厉害 将天下无敌的赛亚人打得落花流水
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.54,0:09:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混开 邱夷
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.93,0:09:48.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没空跟你废话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.15,0:09:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.86,0:09:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗利萨大王对你擅自去地球很生气
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.64,0:09:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山高皇帝远 他管不着
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.71,0:10:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 把你的脏手拿开
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.77,0:10:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.84,0:10:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗利萨大王宽宏大量
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.65,0:10:11.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经原谅了你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.46,0:10:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你发现了些有价值的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.59,0:10:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.57,0:10:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他非常高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.86,0:10:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许能长生不老呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.05,0:10:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.43,0:10:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗利萨大王去了…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.67,0:10:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那美克星
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.33,0:10:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 通过探测器知道的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.70,0:10:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果让他先得逞 以后就得唯命是从了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.39,0:10:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是也想利用龙珠长生不老啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.42,0:10:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.00,0:10:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗利萨大王实现愿望后会杀光所有那美克星人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.20,0:10:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个混蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.28,0:10:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝吉塔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.77,0:10:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝吉塔大人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.03,0:10:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.64,0:10:57.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来还是需要这东西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.13,0:11:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝吉塔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.48,0:11:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让你得逞的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.14,0:11:11.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.40,0:11:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.73,0:11:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有四下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.12,0:11:44.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 孙先生 这样可不行 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.90,0:11:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,护士小姐 我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.77,0:11:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悟空可是不死之身哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.35,0:11:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 刚才我干吗了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.75,0:11:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在老了 记性不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.51,0:12:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.66,0:12:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些点心很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.66,0:12:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大夫
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.47,0:12:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要跟你说多少次才行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.71,0:12:24.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样永远都别想出院
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.50,0:12:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 我已经好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.31,0:12:28.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很疼的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.18,0:12:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之 你的伤情很严重
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.32,0:12:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回床上去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.08,0:12:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.25,0:12:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性骚扰爷爷 来帮个忙
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.74,0:12:40.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性…性骚扰爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.28,0:12:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性骚扰爷爷吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.88,0:12:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.36,0:12:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,性骚扰爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.45,0:12:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,患者的太太呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.53,0:13:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了等信 又去屋顶了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.18,0:13:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悟饭 过得还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.78,0:13:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都说每天要写信的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.11,0:13:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一封也没有
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.25,0:13:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快回来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.84,0:13:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离开地球的第34天
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.27,0:13:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布尔玛一行终于到达了那美克星
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.10,0:13:37.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.50,0:13:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是它 就是它
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.99,0:13:41.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好漂亮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.52,0:13:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是那美克星啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.24,0:13:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 货真价实的那美克星
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.29,0:13:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电脑上是这么显示的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.17,0:13:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然按计划到达了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.53,0:13:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是神仙的宇宙飞船啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.44,0:13:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正所谓一帆风顺嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.61,0:13:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.45,0:14:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 准备着陆 系上安全带坐好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.59,0:14:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,着陆时的冲击会比较大
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.17,0:14:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选择适当的地形开始着陆
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.17,0:14:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 到达那美克星了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.70,0:14:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.77,0:14:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.61,0:14:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先来检查一下大气的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.62,0:14:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特意安装了传感器 准备充分吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.36,0:14:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果含有一定程度的氧气就好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.27,0:14:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然准备了氧气罩
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.12,0:15:02.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但时间有限 未必能派上…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.14,0:15:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里很像短笛叔叔与我修炼的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.91,0:15:22.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我们最初和赛亚人战斗的地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.68,0:15:26.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能在与故乡相似的地方 心里会本能地平静一些
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.27,0:15:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短笛叔叔…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.90,0:15:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们丝毫没有常识啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.51,0:15:37.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然这么冒冒失失地跑了出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.60,0:15:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是这么容易生气啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.12,0:15:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.56,0:15:44.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了 有龙珠就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.50,0:15:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.36,0:15:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 有反应
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.78,0:15:51.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.35,0:15:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.59,0:15:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小林叔叔 那边有很强的气
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.56,0:16:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,气
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.32,0:16:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.35,0:16:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉到很多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.12,0:16:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且都是相当厉害的气
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.34,0:16:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.97,0:16:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真讨厌 说什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.82,0:16:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些都是那美克星人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.80,0:16:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神仙和短笛那么厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.98,0:16:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正的那美克星上
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.24,0:16:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很强的气也不足为奇啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.90,0:16:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.64,0:16:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉这些气有点邪恶…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.99,0:16:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.70,0:16:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,界王不是说过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.60,0:16:31.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那美克星人非常温和
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.64,0:16:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边的方向有四颗龙珠聚集在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.75,0:16:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我们去找那美克星人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.61,0:16:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 也对
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.20,0:16:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是那美克星人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.06,0:16:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白白紧张了半天
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.71,0:16:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是…好像在哪儿见过
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.15,0:17:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是赛亚人的宇宙飞船
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.01,0:17:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.35,0:17:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.74,0:17:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 为什么会这样…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.42,0:17:17.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悟饭 屏住气息 会被发现的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.67,0:17:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…是贝吉塔
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.67,0:17:21.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有那家伙了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.93,0:17:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.55,0:17:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤已经治好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.42,0:17:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了 他肯定也是来找龙珠的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.14,0:17:35.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎…怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.57,0:17:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙 还是回地球吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.89,0:17:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.20,0:17:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被他得到龙珠可就完了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.89,0:17:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布尔玛 你把这件事告诉地球
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.62,0:17:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你先回去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.74,0:17:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和悟饭留在这里收集龙珠
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.23,0:17:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.28,0:17:58.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧 我们有龙珠雷达
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.34,0:17:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎样 悟饭
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.59,0:18:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 回去后我就把孙君带来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.03,0:18:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大约要两个月
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.85,0:18:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.36,0:18:14.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧 两个月很快的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.32,0:18:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是60天 1440小时 86400分 5184000秒
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.43,0:18:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.23,0:18:25.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大约两个月…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.47,0:18:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗利萨那个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.17,0:18:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝不会让你得逞的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.56,0:18:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗利萨以外的人不难对付
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.05,0:18:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但和他正面对抗却毫无胜算…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.10,0:18:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须先设法搞到龙珠 然后长生不老…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.39,0:19:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还得用一下探测器…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.72,0:19:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.75,0:19:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨博和多多利亚也来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.09,0:19:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.92,0:19:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.66,0:19:26.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 所以转告孙君
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.62,0:19:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.67,0:19:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要对琪琪保密啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.62,0:19:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.84,0:19:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 对对
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.42,0:19:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.91,0:19:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.55,0:19:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那样 真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.45,0:19:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对 知道了吗 拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.39,0:19:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.49,0:19:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.62,0:19:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.21,0:19:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.81,0:20:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为…为什么 又…来了一个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.24,0:20:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…也想知道呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.04,0:20:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了 弗利萨大王
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.24,0:20:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.21,0:20:44.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样还剩下三颗了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.84,0:21:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪恶的主宰者弗利萨终于出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.02,0:21:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此外 野心勃勃的贝吉塔也复活了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.83,0:21:14.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三人突遇的危机…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.84,0:21:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙啊 大事不妙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.37,0:21:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悟饭他们能否平安地收集龙珠呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.23,0:22:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好 我是悟空
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.16,0:22:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比贝吉塔还强的家伙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.19,0:22:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是我 面对弗利萨也毫无胜算
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.67,0:22:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先收拾小杂鱼们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.07,0:22:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到达那美克星前 我要努力修行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.07,0:22:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要变得更强才行
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.25,0:22:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙珠是不会交给任何人的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.74,0:22:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集 龙珠改
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.50,0:22:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背叛弗利萨\N野心勃勃的贝吉塔
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.02,0:23:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正宗的龙珠可真大啊


