[Script Info]
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 874
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.0000

字幕：dmhy&POPGO 字幕组
抄写：炎之川
检查：FWS

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: OPED,Celebrity,26,&H90ffffff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100.00,100.00,0.00,0.00,1,1.00,0.00,1,20,20,10,1
Style: Title,微软雅黑,26,&H00ffffff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,83.00,100.00,0.00,0.00,1,0.00,0.00,7,20,20,10,1
Style: Default,微软雅黑,36,&H00ffffff,&H00ffffff,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,83.00,100.00,0.00,0.00,1,1.00,0.00,2,20,20,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.08,0:00:21.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都不自然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.17,0:00:25.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生活在空无一物的房间的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.97,0:00:32.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文森特
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.93,0:00:35.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在这里到底在想些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.69,0:00:44.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱着必死的觉悟追求的东西是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.84,0:01:13.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收获只有这点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.51,0:01:18.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉露·梅尔！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.81,0:01:24.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分明只是个移民
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.36,0:01:28.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…到底是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.53,0:01:36.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 伊基不在就什么都查不到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.46,0:01:50.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感染上病毒的奥特雷逃跑路径预测图？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.84,0:01:53.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.25,0:03:43.92,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(110,40)\fad(400,300)\be1}省察       歌咏未来、未来黄泉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.15,0:03:43.92,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(350,355)\fad(400,300)\be1}冥想Ⅳ  futu{\fnsimhei\fs20}·{\r}risk
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.79,0:03:51.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.30,0:03:56.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.84,0:04:03.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里所有的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.26,0:04:06.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是城市 不是教会 不是河流
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.14,0:04:11.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是色彩 不是光芒 也不是阴影
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.32,0:04:16.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,移民？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.24,0:04:18.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正是些不合时宜的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.53,0:04:21.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么？ 是谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.95,0:04:22.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那个给我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.37,0:04:25.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这个 皮诺你真聪明
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.66,0:04:29.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮诺
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.29,0:04:35.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里真热
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.46,0:04:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多萝西 开空调
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.02,0:05:00.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是…染上病毒的奥特雷
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.67,0:05:15.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片刻之间
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.29,0:05:17.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一动不动
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.92,0:05:20.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉到这无比汹涌的海潮
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.17,0:05:24.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万里晴空与此刻的忧郁一道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.30,0:05:28.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正无所顾忌地渗透到我的心里
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.24,0:05:47.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是所谓的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.04,0:05:51.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.83,0:05:55.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,移民终究只是移民而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.86,0:06:20.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 做了这么个噩梦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.61,0:06:24.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警备局竟然误以为我杀害了多萝西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.78,0:06:26.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是愚蠢的噩梦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.82,0:06:27.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧 多萝西
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.74,0:06:30.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不会做这种…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.05,0:06:45.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别再依赖从者了 多萝西已经不在了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.51,0:06:49.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也成不了优秀市民
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.69,0:07:01.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的意识里不清楚发生了什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.32,0:07:03.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有能力表达出来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.28,0:07:07.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.36,0:07:09.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为优秀市民
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.20,0:07:13.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直很努力 只为了成为优秀市民
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.12,0:07:14.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.54,0:07:20.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是罪犯 文森特·罗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.75,0:07:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.42,0:07:27.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是现实
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.98,0:07:36.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.89,0:07:41.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此时的你会感觉到自己内心某些事物将要沉睡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.65,0:07:44.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时有些意识即将觉醒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.53,0:07:50.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是难以用笔墨形容的瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.51,0:08:14.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从他衍生出的世界里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.18,0:08:17.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人可以变成任何事物
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.19,0:08:20.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是乔布斯科说的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.90,0:08:21.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.40,0:08:25.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔布斯科
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.32,0:08:27.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.57,0:08:29.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是文森特·罗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.32,0:08:32.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.03,0:08:34.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.78,0:08:37.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的身体已经战胜了病毒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.91,0:08:40.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过也多亏了我替你治病
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.46,0:08:46.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这里的人八成以上都患有传染病
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.75,0:08:47.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撑不过一个星期
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.42,0:08:50.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传染？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.72,0:08:54.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你睡了十天
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.85,0:08:57.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在没事了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.72,0:08:58.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十天？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.73,0:09:02.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这十天我打听了很多关于你的事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.10,0:09:03.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向皮诺
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.23,0:09:09.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 皮诺 文森特已经醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.24,0:09:13.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文斯 你醒了？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.53,0:09:17.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 文斯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.83,0:09:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮诺…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.00,0:09:28.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥特雷逃跑的路线
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.40,0:09:47.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难怪警备局的人找不到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.96,0:10:09.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 乔先生
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.46,0:10:12.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.05,0:10:13.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.01,0:10:17.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.02,0:10:24.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.56,0:10:28.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.57,0:10:32.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫胡迪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.61,0:10:34.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔是写这本书的诗人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.59,0:10:56.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要对我这么好 就我这副模样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.30,0:10:58.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不觉得麻烦吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.64,0:11:05.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也曾经被温暖的保护着
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.10,0:11:07.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.35,0:11:12.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也还很漂亮吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.98,0:11:17.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种城市什么都是骗人的 全都是假的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.65,0:11:20.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在不知道那是骗人的之前 那就是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.41,0:11:24.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看穿谎言发掘真理可能是正确的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.50,0:11:27.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是不一定就会幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.29,0:11:30.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谎言等于幸福吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.04,0:11:32.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谎言等于幸福吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.21,0:11:36.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对哦 皮诺真聪明
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.05,0:11:37.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我仔细看看
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.84,0:11:43.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真精致 奥特雷果然越来越像我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.72,0:11:47.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近那边的奥特雷都是这样的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.14,0:11:50.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边？什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.36,0:11:52.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然是罗姆德了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.65,0:11:57.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗姆德 好熟悉的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.74,0:12:01.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 这里难道不是移民地区吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.50,0:12:10.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.50,0:12:13.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干吗现在还说这种傻话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.92,0:12:16.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是和她一起逃到城市外边了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.76,0:12:18.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城市外边？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.92,0:12:21.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 皮诺知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.05,0:12:26.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城市在离这里1246.65单位距离的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.14,0:12:34.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 文斯跳的那个Plugvent距地面大概有517单位
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.19,0:12:37.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到处转了很久 还问了很多人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.61,0:12:39.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在很博学的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.65,0:12:42.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我厉害吧 文斯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.41,0:12:46.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文斯？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.71,0:12:53.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外边？罗姆德？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.79,0:12:55.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文斯！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.49,0:13:30.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像没什么精神
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.29,0:13:33.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是上次受了伤的缘故
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.04,0:13:36.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为被代表惩罚了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.84,0:13:41.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连伊基也被撤走了 有点过分呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.34,0:13:43.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.18,0:13:45.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那到底是为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.98,0:13:58.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能告诉我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.69,0:14:01.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 我不能说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.07,0:14:04.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为杜鲁斯和葛塔莉在？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.03,0:14:09.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 我对他们做过一些手脚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.29,0:14:12.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不会对任何人说任何事的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.62,0:14:14.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事 爷爷…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.46,0:14:16.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是两个人的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.50,0:14:20.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不光只是你的主治医生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.96,0:14:22.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直都是站在你这边的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.47,0:14:27.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会相信我吧 莉露
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.97,0:14:31.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会告诉任何人？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.14,0:14:32.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.81,0:14:37.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到Proxy的尸体了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.15,0:14:40.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警备局也还不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.15,0:14:46.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是劳尔他们瞒着情报局在寻找的怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.66,0:14:49.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮我的忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.24,0:14:51.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你替我调查一下他的来历
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.04,0:14:55.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爷爷也瞒着我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.04,0:14:59.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想自己查出来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.54,0:15:02.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道答案对你来说未必是幸福的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.96,0:15:03.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.92,0:15:06.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你了 迪达尔斯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.72,0:15:15.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 我会帮你的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.73,0:15:17.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那告诉我地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.54,0:15:39.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的确是从那里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.83,0:15:42.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被怪物追赶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.21,0:15:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后背上黑锅 被指控谋反
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.22,0:15:51.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪物？你看到那个了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.51,0:15:53.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪个？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.18,0:15:55.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.52,0:15:57.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.56,0:16:05.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是从他们生存的地方生出的恶魔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.50,0:16:21.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本该是不死之身的阿姆利塔细胞居然死灭了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.67,0:16:22.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得是怎么回事？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.30,0:16:28.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不带回实验室研究一下 什么都不好说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.22,0:16:31.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本来就知道？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.89,0:16:37.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好把在这里看到的东西都忘掉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.77,0:16:40.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是Proxy吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.85,0:16:47.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有另一个杀掉这个怪物的怪物存在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.95,0:16:53.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该还活在某个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.91,0:16:54.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把它…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.95,0:16:55.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉露
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.99,0:16:57.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的吧 迪达尔斯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.29,0:17:02.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 这是不能说的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.96,0:17:04.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.08,0:17:05.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用再说了 迪达尔斯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.54,0:17:08.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像给你惹麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.97,0:17:13.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能把下面的事情交给我处理吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.39,0:17:16.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以请你答应我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.64,0:17:18.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这里什么都没发现
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.02,0:17:22.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 何止呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.39,0:17:24.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都没来过这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.61,0:17:26.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.48,0:17:29.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.36,0:17:31.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调查有结果了 总结一下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.78,0:17:32.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次我再来问你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.82,0:17:34.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.74,0:17:39.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过吧 我要自己调查
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.99,0:17:43.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有只有感染奥特雷才知道的逃跑路径
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.96,0:17:45.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去那里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.21,0:17:47.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉露
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.56,0:18:09.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是移民吧 是不是不习惯罗姆德的感觉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.86,0:18:10.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.03,0:18:15.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很欢迎你来 你爱呆多久就呆多久
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.70,0:18:16.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是自由的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.87,0:18:21.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们离开了那里 才获得真正的自由
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.75,0:18:24.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.00,0:18:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在城市里不需要的东西会被扔掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.46,0:18:30.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但都是还能用的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.92,0:18:32.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我捡到一个这个
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.98,0:18:49.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里的人都是因为种种原因而离开罗姆德
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.86,0:18:51.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者是被驱逐出那里的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.40,0:18:55.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以很多人对罗姆德有敌意
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.86,0:18:59.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也并非没人想回去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.78,0:19:02.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有人说是绝对回不去的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.04,0:19:04.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁说的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.70,0:19:06.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边碰到的一个女的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.96,0:19:08.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是库因吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.25,0:19:09.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个贱人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.83,0:19:11.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来老头说过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.50,0:19:14.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是最新型的高级货
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.38,0:19:18.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那些市民级的人用过的贵重东西吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.68,0:19:22.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定会有人来把你捡回去的 小妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.47,0:19:25.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文斯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.27,0:19:33.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑的 谁愿意回那种鬼地方去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.48,0:19:34.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.32,0:19:35.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.82,0:19:36.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.82,0:19:44.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是哦 是哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.80,0:19:59.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从今开始 我…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.76,0:20:04.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是和皮诺一起来的那个人？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.89,0:20:09.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是库因
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.65,0:20:13.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从海里捞些掉下来的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.07,0:20:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是好地方呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.57,0:20:18.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗姆德发出的热量使得海湾很暖和
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.57,0:20:19.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.74,0:20:20.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.03,0:20:22.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是奥特雷的中枢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.24,0:20:24.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还是防水型奥特雷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.95,0:20:27.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以用来做兔子的传动系统的替代品
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.41,0:20:28.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兔子？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.54,0:20:33.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啊 我可没软弱到想永远呆在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.88,0:20:39.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像觉得我和第一次见面的人就絮絮叨叨的 脸皮很厚吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.51,0:20:40.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没这么想啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.22,0:20:44.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许胡迪和你提起过 我是一个怪人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.18,0:20:47.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过在我看来
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.14,0:20:53.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些成天嚷嚷着自由的人才更怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.28,0:21:02.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想一辈子作为罗姆德的寄生虫生活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.57,0:21:03.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好记住哦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.49,0:21:06.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.66,0:21:10.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种地方唉声叹气 眼泪汪汪的做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.12,0:21:12.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.21,0:21:15.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮诺比你成熟多了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.38,0:21:16.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.71,0:21:20.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快就会习惯这里的生活的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.55,0:21:23.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢想想该怎么做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.51,0:21:25.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不妙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.01,0:21:26.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.68,0:21:28.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.22,0:21:29.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,定期侦察机
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.31,0:21:31.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.70,0:21:45.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,定期侦察机
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.28,0:21:47.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗姆德的无人侦察机
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.95,0:21:52.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天准时以固定线路侦察
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.37,0:21:55.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要是什么都没发现也就不会来搜索了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.25,0:22:00.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对罗姆德来说我们的存在仅此而已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.26,0:22:03.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮诺那个傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.13,0:22:05.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 奥特雷…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.28,0:22:31.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮诺 趴下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.26,0:22:49.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,定期侦察机不是不会攻击奥特雷吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.14,0:22:52.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望别带来麻烦就好
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.11,0:23:05.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个男人？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.65,0:23:06.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文森特·罗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.28,0:23:08.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您打算怎么处置
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.03,0:23:10.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为什么还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.24,0:23:13.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要向长官汇报吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.66,0:23:15.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 长官应该没什么兴趣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.29,0:23:19.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先去增派巡查机
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.67,0:23:21.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经在待命了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.84,0:23:22.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.71,0:23:27.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让相关各局出动
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.93,0:23:31.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 实验体的行踪还不明
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.85,0:23:37.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧 反正那个男人那里会有答案的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.77,0:23:40.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在的我 是知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.86,0:23:41.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真少见
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.94,0:23:46.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是指您说话居然会带感情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.44,0:23:49.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己也很惊讶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.95,0:23:55.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仿佛感染了“我思”病毒似的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.91,0:23:58.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说 这个笑话不好笑
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.09,0:25:32.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁在细语
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.63,0:25:35.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当看到本不能看的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.72,0:25:38.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能再做回以前的自己
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.39,0:25:40.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使这样也无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.14,0:25:42.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这也仍旧是我的话
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.46,0:25:44.96,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(85,18)\fad(400,300)\be1}省察        召还
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.46,0:25:44.96,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,370)\fad(400,300)\be1}冥想Ⅴ  TASOGARE
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.49,0:02:14.23,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\an3}You complete my fate
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.50,0:02:20.00,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\an3}The world unwinds inside of me
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.06,0:02:24.69,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\an3}You complete my fate
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.06,0:02:30.07,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\an3}The halo crawls away
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.50,0:02:36.22,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\an3}You refill my place
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.02,0:02:45.77,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)\an3}You refill my place
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.08,0:02:58.15,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,800)\an3}Come and save me
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.58,0:03:09.59,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,800)\an3}Come and save me
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.09,0:03:19.40,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,800)\an3}Come and save me
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.52,0:03:30.60,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,800)\an3}Come and save me
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.98,0:03:34.41,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,800)\an3}Come and save me
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.60,0:24:27.79,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}Please could you stop the noise,I'm trying get some rest
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.92,0:24:46.81,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,300)}From all the unborn chicken,Voices in my head
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.19,0:24:57.82,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,800)}What's that
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.99,0:25:05.02,OPED,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(300,800)}What's that...
