[Script Info]

Title: When_They_Cry #23
Original Script: HKG&X2
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:864
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;=== When_They_Cry 寒蟬鳴泣之時 DVDRip作品 ASS字幕外掛發佈訊息 ===
;字幕版本使用HKG字幕組&X2字幕組TV連載字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈 謝謝
;參與製作人員
;翻譯&校對    影
;時間軸       JK & Klaus
;特傚         怕输
;DVDRip&後期  ZilcH「力」
;
Style: Default,simhei,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H300000A0,&HF00000D0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05T,34,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H500000B0,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhushi,simhei,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H300000A0,&HF00000D0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: logo,fzxingkai-s04t,35,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,5,10,10,20,1
Style: op_jap,mikachan-pb,28,&H20EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H80454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,15,1
Style: op_chi,经典繁颜体,26,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,8,1
Style: op_chi2,经典繁颜体,26,&H200F2FF2,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,8,1
Style: ed_jap,s2gmemo,30,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: warning,simhei,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,5,5,5,1
Style: staff,dfkai-sb,25,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,1,10,10,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.00,0:00:42.06,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罪\h\h\h\h篇    其之二 {\fn方正大标宋_GBK}歸所
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.00,0:00:42.06,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(342,471)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\1c&Hff&\be1\b0\fs36}滅
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.53,0:00:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律子 你在雏见泽的男人怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.15,0:00:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能榨多少钱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.46,0:00:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个啊 听说和他离婚的前妻给了很多赡养费
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.57,0:00:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备怎么骗过来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.74,0:00:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打算利用你来骗分手费
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.93,0:02:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}临时有急事要出去不用准备我的晚饭了 父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.49,0:02:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都愿意给我买哦 什么都愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.86,0:02:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs28}危险危险
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.13,0:02:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 日子过于和平真无聊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.33,0:03:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗? 礼奈我就很喜欢和平又无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.92,0:03:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈每天都这么幸福真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.51,0:03:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 这方面被人羡慕也很困扰哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.70,0:03:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有每天都能幸福度过的窍门的话请告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.08,0:03:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很简单啊 只需要察觉到就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.91,0:03:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,察觉到什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.69,0:03:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸福的日子是有限的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.38,0:03:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没用没用 礼奈的哲学小圭又怎么会懂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.58,0:03:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.81,0:03:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住口 别把别人当作一点感性都没有的野蛮人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.01,0:03:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 野蛮人先生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.63,0:03:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么 给我站住
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.42,0:03:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.83,0:03:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸福的日子 是有限的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.31,0:03:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 欢迎回来 礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.98,0:03:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下午好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.62,0:04:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天白天和你爸爸一起去了家咖喱非常好吃的店
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.02,0:04:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就打包买了回来给你当礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.92,0:04:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一会记得吃吃看哦 很好吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.88,0:04:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是值得期待 谢谢您了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.37,0:04:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 礼奈 我希望我们三个人一起谈一谈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.78,0:04:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.41,0:04:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友在等我 要先出去一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.02,0:04:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 又去垃圾山寻宝吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.27,0:04:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我下次也去看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.18,0:04:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.66,0:04:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.18,0:04:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理奈小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.84,0:04:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈你听力不太好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.94,0:04:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.48,0:04:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个人吗 你朋友呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.19,0:05:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一个人在玩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.00,0:05:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 以这个年纪来看挺阴沉的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.53,0:05:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.83,0:05:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.13,0:05:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺漂亮的嘛 像秘密基地一样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.03,0:05:19.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是只属于我的秘密隐匿处
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.02,0:05:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁都不会来这里 也不会让别人听到任何声音
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.48,0:05:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只属于礼奈的秘密隐匿处
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.80,0:05:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴呢 居然能到这样的地方来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.40,0:05:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有件事我之前就想问礼奈你了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.26,0:05:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.72,0:05:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈你喜欢我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.48,0:05:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然之间怎么这么问
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.40,0:05:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是和你的父亲在交往吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.17,0:05:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我们讨论了不少
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.75,0:05:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认真的讨论了将来的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.45,0:05:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将来的生活 还有各种各样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.14,0:06:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈你也喜欢秋人叔叔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.97,0:06:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以妈妈我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.17,0:06:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不允许再婚
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.68,0:06:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要和父亲怎么交往我无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.90,0:06:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再婚是绝不允许的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.35,0:06:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜想可能也会有点抗拒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.75,0:06:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过没想到会说的这么直接
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.19,0:06:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会察觉到我有所抗拒也让我很意外
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.32,0:06:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情当然会知道嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.45,0:06:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一和我见面马上就会逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.73,0:06:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当作是让我学习学习告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.98,0:06:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪里让你不满意了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.03,0:06:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从头到脚 化装和服饰 气味我也讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.46,0:06:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这倒正好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.33,0:06:52.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我也讨厌你  彼此彼此呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.28,0:06:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别小看我 小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.90,0:06:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让我破口大骂你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.69,0:06:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不要再来我们家了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.66,0:07:02.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再婚什么的 我决不允许
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.82,0:07:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让你父亲放弃再婚你就去试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.20,0:07:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情现在已经毫无意义了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.28,0:07:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊 已经怀孕了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.88,0:07:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈啊 已经怀孕了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.31,0:07:24.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.60,0:07:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是骗人 是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.61,0:07:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经听到了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.54,0:07:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和那个叫铁平的男人在咖啡店的谈话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.98,0:07:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你们把爸爸称为雏见泽那里的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.23,0:07:40.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想让他当冤大头
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.04,0:07:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仙人跳的事情我也 全都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.48,0:07:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.17,0:07:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是秘密的隐匿处吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.58,0:07:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁都不知道的秘密地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.05,0:08:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶的小鬼 居然小看我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.34,0:08:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差一点就有五千万送上门来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.08,0:08:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这种节骨眼上真是碍事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.16,0:08:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.56,0:08:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我不太想杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.91,0:08:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过可能再也遇不到这么好的肥羊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.63,0:08:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正拿了钱我也打算人间蒸发的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.13,0:08:36.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.10,0:08:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 这是
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.51,0:08:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.08,0:08:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.50,0:08:56.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.92,0:08:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.49,0:09:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.35,0:09:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这混帐 居然敢碰我的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.89,0:09:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为可以就这么算了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.76,0:09:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了 我明天还会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.34,0:09:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我凑齐钱等着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.34,0:09:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.67,0:09:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.28,0:10:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 我是龙宫家的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.29,0:10:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.65,0:10:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实是 理奈小姐说如果铁平先生来了让我带你过去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.64,0:10:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎? 律子她有什么事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.29,0:10:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是有什么话要说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.73,0:10:21.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 为什么律子会在这种地方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.89,0:10:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说是无论如何都想和你单独谈谈
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.00,0:10:27.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.52,0:10:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 那傻女人在想什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.94,0:10:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 对不起 可能是电池接触不良了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.36,0:10:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.04,0:10:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 快一点哦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.60,0:10:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有打火机
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.89,0:10:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.13,0:11:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小魅 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.92,0:11:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天也有点事 必须早点回去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.67,0:11:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.91,0:11:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了嘛 礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.37,0:11:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么早就回去了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.93,0:11:33.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 看不到圭一难看的败姿 实在是可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.74,0:11:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真遗憾
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.35,0:11:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.04,0:11:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天不也是家里有事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.89,0:11:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出什么事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.70,0:11:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微 有些事情
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.96,0:12:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么嘛什么嘛 还差好多牌呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.39,0:12:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样子麻将是打不成了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.99,0:12:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 谁有提议吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.18,0:12:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当作是寻宝去找遗失的麻将牌怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.04,0:12:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得太小家子气了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.73,0:12:29.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我们就再搞大规模些的寻宝怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.72,0:12:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻宝?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.20,0:12:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.98,0:12:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起寻宝就是礼奈的拿手好戏了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.88,0:12:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 大坝建设现场的垃圾山吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.85,0:12:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里会出现分尸杀人事件的幽灵
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.46,0:12:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好还是不要接近
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.20,0:12:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得是发生了分尸杀人 主犯依然在逃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.29,0:12:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙藏的一只手好像还没找到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.95,0:12:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大坝战争之后还喜欢进出那里的也只有礼奈了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.07,0:13:01.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 那今天就去垃圾山寻宝吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.06,0:13:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到幽灵的话就是胜者
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.36,0:13:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到被藏起来的右手的就是第二名
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.68,0:13:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着是找到礼奈可能会喜欢的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.19,0:13:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让礼奈看看 给我们分个胜负怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.71,0:13:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赞成
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.79,0:13:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.61,0:13:26.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些就是全部了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.39,0:13:31.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才我去了高地那里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.49,0:13:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想找能埋这些袋子的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.09,0:13:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过找不到什么好地方呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.64,0:13:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.33,0:13:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.12,0:13:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不和我们商量一下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.59,0:13:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商量?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.49,0:13:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 我们不是朋友吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.78,0:13:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友就是无论发生什么都能无条件的帮助自己
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.22,0:13:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道不是和家人一样的存在吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.38,0:14:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果和我们商量的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.54,0:14:04.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我们可以帮上些忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.45,0:14:11.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话 礼奈也许就不用成为凶手了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.13,0:14:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.02,0:14:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算像圭一君所说的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.18,0:14:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向大家说明了爸爸和那个女人的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.35,0:14:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 你们要怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.99,0:14:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.73,0:14:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先怎么样…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.02,0:14:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.75,0:14:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭一你什么都做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.83,0:14:41.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家也是一样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.11,0:14:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都做不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.19,0:14:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.94,0:14:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友只是一起度过愉快的无谓时光的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.25,0:14:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正痛苦的时候 是不会帮你的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.37,0:14:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.48,0:14:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前开始就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.93,0:15:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搬去的地方也是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.22,0:15:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我决定不再向朋友表白了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.31,0:15:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 反正也不会有人来帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.79,0:15:15.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没法帮我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.63,0:15:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.64,0:15:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你不愿意相信我们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.36,0:15:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.12,0:15:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确 即使和我们商量
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.12,0:15:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能也想不到礼奈你心想的最好的解决方法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.55,0:15:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 即使这样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.90,0:15:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信一定也可以创造比现在更好的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.41,0:15:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比现在更好的未来?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.83,0:15:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有那种东西的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.16,0:15:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是…这就是最好的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.09,0:15:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.06,0:15:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为 作为证据
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.81,0:15:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈你从刚才开始就一直在哭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.49,0:16:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 谁? 我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.83,0:16:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么时候流过泪了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.75,0:16:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在 你不是一直在流泪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.53,0:16:08.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道你自己不知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.29,0:16:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈你做的事是最差劲的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.67,0:16:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.82,0:16:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我作为朋友可以接受礼奈的所作所为
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.48,0:16:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以接受这是别无他法\N苦恼之后得出的最后手段
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.93,0:16:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我想要理解礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.33,0:16:42.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道这些麻烦的袋子的事情的只有我们几个
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.83,0:16:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我们所有人都当它是秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.83,0:16:46.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情就结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.51,0:16:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈不用担心什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.80,0:16:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.11,0:17:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.29,0:17:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.85,0:17:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.01,0:17:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和梨花也都失去了双亲孤单一人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.50,0:17:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但们从没有为此悲叹过
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.38,0:17:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们有大家 名为朋友的家人在
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.95,0:17:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名为朋友的家人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.30,0:17:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以沙都子而言是不错的比喻了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.88,0:17:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诉说朋友的重要性
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.30,0:17:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是身为部长的我的职责
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.94,0:17:37.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 我也失去做部长的资格了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.40,0:17:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.55,0:17:43.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我在开玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.40,0:17:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没能察觉到礼奈的境遇
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.86,0:17:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为朋友 作为部长我觉得很可耻
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.37,0:17:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你们原谅我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.04,0:17:56.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然 礼奈没有和我们商量的事情也可以原谅
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.80,0:18:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为我们不值得她表白
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.42,0:18:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这份不成熟是我们的责任
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.97,0:18:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不会责怪礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.90,0:18:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈是凶手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.00,0:18:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会给大家添麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.97,0:18:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是梦也不是幻觉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.66,0:18:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也更不是什么不可挽回的事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.45,0:18:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈还有可以选择的选项
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.71,0:18:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以选吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.77,0:18:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还来得及 过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.52,0:19:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.81,0:19:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.48,0:19:37.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈 今天回去后好好休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.46,0:19:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 我会这么做的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.62,0:19:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈 不能责怪自己哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.09,0:19:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然和大家说的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.33,0:19:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.95,0:19:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我果然骗不了自己
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.12,0:20:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何理解自己行为的合理性
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.79,0:20:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我心里还是畏惧于自己的暴行
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.91,0:20:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然大家帮我走到了这一步
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.24,0:20:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却还是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.40,0:20:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没有见到大家一个人整理完了一切
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.84,0:20:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定承受不了自己的罪孽深重
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.77,0:20:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许已经被压垮了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.66,0:20:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从明天开始
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.33,0:20:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得大家一起忘了今天的事比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.72,0:20:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们怎么看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.42,0:20:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 这对礼奈来说是最好的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.16,0:20:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈是很坚强的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.59,0:20:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我们这样表现 她也会配合的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.92,0:20:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表现的久了也就会成为真实了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.18,0:21:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直不谈论 总有一天我们也会忘记
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.42,0:21:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而完全忘记的那一天 就是我们的目标吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.71,0:21:14.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕这一天就是花上一生的时间也不知会不会到来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.78,0:21:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.29,0:21:27.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.33,0:21:29.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太慢了啦 礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.14,0:21:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.58,0:21:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我们先去哪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.89,0:21:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肚子饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.30,0:21:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就先吃炒面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.35,0:21:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.39,0:21:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.66,0:23:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所驰骋的 是平日的归路
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.15,0:23:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所蠢动的 是不幸的通知
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.79,0:23:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被打开的 是欺骗的剪报
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.70,0:23:29.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒蝉鸣泣之时
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.79,0:23:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 能相信吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.79,0:23:34.70,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,0)}罪\h\h\h\h篇    其之三  {\fs32\fn方正大标宋_GBK}34號文書
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.79,0:23:34.70,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,0)}{\pos(312,471)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\1c&Hff&\be1\b0\fs36}滅
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo & Staff↓
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.50,0:00:49.15,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(87,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord2}{\alpha&H20&}翻譯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.50,0:00:49.15,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(209,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord2}{\alpha&H20&}影
Dialogue: 1,0:00:46.50,0:00:49.15,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(87,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord0}翻譯
Dialogue: 1,0:00:46.50,0:00:49.15,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(209,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord0}影
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.85,0:01:08.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(185,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}時間
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.85,0:01:08.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(295,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}Klaus
Dialogue: 1,0:01:04.85,0:01:08.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(185,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}時間
Dialogue: 1,0:01:04.85,0:01:08.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(295,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}Klaus
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.57,0:01:11.52,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(534,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}特效
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.57,0:01:11.52,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(645,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}怕输囧
Dialogue: 1,0:01:08.57,0:01:11.52,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(534,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}特效
Dialogue: 1,0:01:08.57,0:01:11.52,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(645,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}怕输囧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.70,0:01:16.80,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(150,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}後 期
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.70,0:01:16.80,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(270,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp-2}{\alpha&H20&}ZilcH「力」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.70,0:01:16.80,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(150,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}後 期
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.70,0:01:16.80,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(270,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp-2}ZilcH「力」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.90,0:01:02.81,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\3c&H454041&}{\bord3}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2135be&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Dialogue: 2,0:00:55.90,0:01:02.81,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\bord1}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2826ef&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Dialogue: 3,0:00:55.90,0:01:02.81,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2826ef&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Comment: 0,0:00:00.05,0:00:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.05,0:00:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.07,0:01:17.66,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}振り{\1c&H0f2ff2&}向{\1c&Heaf2f1&}いたその後ろの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.36,0:01:22.40,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}正面{\1c&H0f2ff2&}だ{\1c&Heaf2f1&}ぁれ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.21,0:01:27.18,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}暗{\1c&H0f2ff2&}闇{\1c&Heaf2f1&}に爪を立てて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.23,0:01:30.98,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}夜を引き{\1c&H0f2ff2&}裂{\1c&Heaf2f1&}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.09,0:01:36.68,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}雨だれは{\1c&H0f2ff2&}血{\1c&Heaf2f1&}のしずくとなって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.83,0:01:40.35,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}頬をつたい{\1c&H0f2ff2&}落{\1c&Heaf2f1&}ちる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.57,0:01:50.28,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}もうどこにも帰る{\1c&H0f2ff2&}場所{\1c&Heaf2f1&}が無いなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.67,0:01:55.12,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}この指{\1c&H0f2ff2&}止{\1c&Heaf2f1&}まれ　私の指に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.19,0:01:59.56,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}その指ごと連れて{\1c&H0f2ff2&}っ{\1c&Heaf2f1&}てあげる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.79,0:02:04.23,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}ひぐらしが{\1c&H0f2ff2&}鳴{\1c&Heaf2f1&}く　開かずの{\1c&H0f2ff2&}森{\1c&Heaf2f1&}へ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.42,0:02:11.84,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}後{\1c&H0f2ff2&}戻{\1c&Heaf2f1&}りはもう出来ない
Dialogue: 10,0:01:14.07,0:01:17.66,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}回首望去 紧随身后
Dialogue: 10,0:01:18.36,0:01:22.40,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}正面 是谁?
Dialogue: 10,0:01:23.21,0:01:27.18,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}无尽黑暗 轻点脚尖
Dialogue: 10,0:01:27.23,0:01:30.98,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}黑夜撕裂
Dialogue: 10,0:01:31.09,0:01:36.68,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}雨水化为血滴
Dialogue: 10,0:01:36.83,0:01:40.35,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}从脸颊上流淌而下
Dialogue: 10,0:01:40.57,0:01:50.28,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,9000)}{\be1}既然哪里都已没有归所
Dialogue: 10,0:01:50.67,0:01:55.12,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}收回你的手指 抓住我的手指
Dialogue: 10,0:01:55.19,0:01:59.56,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}连你的手指一起带走
Dialogue: 10,0:01:59.79,0:02:04.23,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}蝉儿鸣叫 封闭之森
Dialogue: 10,0:02:04.42,0:02:11.84,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,6000)}{\be1}已经无法回头
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.07,0:01:17.66,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}回首望去 隐匿身后
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.36,0:01:22.40,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}血{\fn華康正顏楷體W7}髏{\r} 疾首
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.21,0:01:27.18,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}阴暗狂啸 举起双爪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.23,0:01:30.98,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}撕肝断肠
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.09,0:01:36.68,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}雨水化为血滴
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.83,0:01:40.35,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}蹂躏脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.57,0:01:50.28,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(9000,250)}{\be1}后悔撕破母胎失去容身之所
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.67,0:01:55.12,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}让我把你的手指都扭断吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.19,0:01:59.56,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}我会将你连骨头都啃碎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.79,0:02:04.23,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}寒蝉鸣泣 不归之森
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.42,0:02:11.84,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(6000,250)}{\be1}回头亦是绝路
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.14,0:22:09.05,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}To get my happiness I had done everything
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.34,0:22:16.15,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}But had done nothing to be blamed and accused of
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.36,0:22:23.13,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}The sound of footsteps became louder every day
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.20,0:22:30.00,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Then I noticed the fact there was no time
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.44,0:22:38.42,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}I was a believer in life to be myself always
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.49,0:22:45.00,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}And was asking whether I would be alive
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.59,0:22:52.53,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}give me a reason why not to adopt in this way
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.64,0:22:59.70,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Or judge me to be guilty to my incurable sins
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.81,0:23:06.61,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Tell me why or why not Complaining way too much
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.72,0:23:14.18,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Maybe I overlooked something fatal for me


