[Script Info]
; This is a Sub Station Alpha v4 script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;
; Script created by cySub 1.4.0 Release Build 1203
;
Title: When_They_Cry #01
Original Script: HKG&X2
Script Type: V4.00+
ScriptType: V4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 864
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.000
WrapStyle: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;
;=== When_They_Cry 寒蟬鳴泣之時 DVDRip作品 ASS字幕外掛發佈訊息 ===
;字幕版本使用HKG字幕組&X2字幕組TV連載字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈 謝謝
;參與製作人員
;翻譯&校對    影
;時間軸       JK & Klaus
;特傚         怕输
;DVDRip&後期  ZilcH「力」
;
Style: Default,simhei,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H300000A0,&HF00000D0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05T,34,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H500000B0,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhushi,simhei,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H300000A0,&HF00000D0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: logo,fzxingkai-s04t,35,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,5,10,10,20,1
Style: op_jap,mikachan-pb,28,&H20EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H80454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,15,1
Style: op_chi,经典繁颜体,26,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,8,1
Style: op_chi2,经典繁颜体,26,&H200F2FF2,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,8,1
Style: ed_jap,s2gmemo,30,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: warning,simhei,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,5,5,5,1
Style: staff,dfkai-sb,25,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.99,0:00:32.97,title,,0000,0000,0000,,鬼\h\h\h\h篇    其之一  起始
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.99,0:00:32.97,title,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(340,472)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\1c&Hff&\be1\b0\fs36}隱
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.32,0:02:18.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.65,0:02:20.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.40,0:02:22.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.50,0:02:27.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對了 圭一 替我謝謝礼奈給的醬菜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.38,0:02:27.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.32,0:02:34.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,搬來雛見澤這裡已經有一個月了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.35,0:02:38.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次認識到了原來空氣也有味道
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.43,0:02:42.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.18,0:02:44.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你還是那麼早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.44,0:02:47.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾悠閒的睡個懶覺也沒關係嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.79,0:02:51.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,睡懶覺的話不是就要讓圭一君等我了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.20,0:02:53.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那樣我肯定丟下你先走
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.47,0:02:55.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君真冷淡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.11,0:02:58.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人家一直都有等你的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.85,0:03:01.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,乾乾脆脆的丟下你  利利落落的丟下你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.50,0:03:05.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼這麼冷淡呢 呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.55,0:03:08.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,騙你的 我會等你的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.50,0:03:12.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.54,0:03:17.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個馬上就臉紅髮熱的怪傢伙叫龍宮礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.41,0:03:20.79,zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,對了 母親叫我傳話給你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.42,0:03:20.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然才認識了一個月不到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.10,0:03:24.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也深刻體會到她不僅是名字怪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.70,0:03:23.37,zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,說是謝謝你的醬菜
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.15,0:03:27.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用謝 別客氣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.56,0:03:29.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 來了來了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.72,0:03:32.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們兩個好遲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.73,0:03:34.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 小魅
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.92,0:03:36.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,平時都是你比較遲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.82,0:03:41.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小圭 好久不見 多少年沒見了?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.10,0:03:43.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才請了兩天假而已吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.18,0:03:48.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,與礼奈的乖巧相反 是個我行我素的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.44,0:03:49.64,zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎 上次見你的時候還那麼可愛呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.50,0:03:50.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙叫園崎魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.01,0:03:50.95,zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.34,0:03:53.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,算是我的學姐 在班上算是首腦級的人物
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.35,0:03:54.01,zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.35,0:03:55.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事隔許久重回大都市的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.28,0:04:00.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我只是去參加葬禮而已 只覺得匆匆忙忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.59,0:04:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對了 幫我找了嗎 我拜託你找的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.90,0:04:06.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說啊 我是去參加葬禮的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.93,0:04:12.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雛見澤是個小村莊 別說學校 班級也只有一個
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.66,0:04:16.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而這個班上的學生的年齡和學級也各不相同
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.63,0:04:20.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是個全部學生加起來也不知有沒有15人的窮鄉僻壤
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.37,0:04:22.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,教師也只有一個
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.90,0:04:26.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為學年不同要教的內容也不同 真是辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.36,0:04:32.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有時候 會由我代替老師 來教礼奈和魅音學習
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.19,0:04:41.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君很擅長教人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.69,0:04:42.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很容易懂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.14,0:04:45.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,站在「教」的立場上我都快失去信心了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.50,0:04:49.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為知道了自己認識的淺薄啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.72,0:04:53.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,俗話說想要教人自己必須有三倍的理解嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.32,0:04:57.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 你的學年要比我大一年吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.80,0:04:58.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要我教你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.34,0:05:00.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別在意這種細節嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.47,0:05:02.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個 圭一君
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.07,0:05:06.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天你有什麼安排嗎 嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.85,0:05:12.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小圭你還不怎麼熟悉雛見澤這裡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.85,0:05:13.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.29,0:05:16.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除了去城裡和去學校的路線以外
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.96,0:05:18.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都沒什麼自信呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.59,0:05:19.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是呢是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.88,0:05:20.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.93,0:05:28.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天小魅和礼奈一邊散步一邊帶圭一君參觀一下雛見澤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.22,0:05:31.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈會做便當帶去的 怎麼樣?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.32,0:05:33.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你當然會去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.89,0:05:34.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有空的話就去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.20,0:05:38.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你這是什麼態度 可是女孩子在邀請你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.06,0:05:40.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有空的話就去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.09,0:05:45.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君 你沒空嗎 嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.81,0:05:46.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有空
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.61,0:05:48.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.95,0:05:53.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對待魅音小姐和礼奈小姐的態度好像有很大的溫度差嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.80,0:05:54.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怒
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.96,0:05:57.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈 明天就我們兩個出去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.78,0:05:59.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果圭一君覺得這樣比較好的話
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.67,0:06:03.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等 提出要帶他參觀的是我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.81,0:06:09.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裡叫作古手神社
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.95,0:06:12.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能是附近景致最好的地方了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.73,0:06:16.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下一個休息日在這裡會舉辦祭典
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.20,0:06:24.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鏘鏘 礼奈的特製便當Special Version喲
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.35,0:06:27.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好驚人的量
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.07,0:06:29.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,午安
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.34,0:06:31.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦 來了來了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.43,0:06:33.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子和梨花?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.11,0:06:39.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這兩位是與我同班的北條沙都子和古手梨花
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.81,0:06:42.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話雖如此 學年當然比我要低
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.76,0:06:46.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這究竟是什麼騷動
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.80,0:06:51.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一看就知道吧 正要品嚐礼奈親手做的便當呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.66,0:06:55.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種事情當然一目瞭然
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.59,0:06:59.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要在別人家的後院裡鋪草蓆啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.79,0:07:03.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神社可是公共場所 不要隨便就想獨佔了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.81,0:07:08.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一說的沒錯 應該當作大家的後院
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.34,0:07:11.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,梨花果然是乖孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.27,0:07:14.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,坐在那吧 我們一起吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.93,0:07:17.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真沒轍呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.86,0:07:21.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難得的機會 我就坐下來陪你們一起好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.85,0:07:24.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有地方給你坐 也沒有東西給你吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.33,0:07:26.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.17,0:07:33.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係的 也有沙都子的一份的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.05,0:07:36.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 沙都子的那一份也由我來吃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.98,0:07:39.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不會允許你這麼做的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.87,0:07:41.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來 筷子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.45,0:07:44.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要開動了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.56,0:07:46.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也開動了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.68,0:07:50.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀呀 年輕真好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.68,0:07:54.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多吃一點哦 大家都有份
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.82,0:07:56.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,漢堡肉 我收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.89,0:07:59.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這漢堡肉不會交給你的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.83,0:08:03.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用手肘是犯規的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.88,0:08:06.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦 有規則的嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.68,0:08:10.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家吃便當真快樂 真快樂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.29,0:08:12.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈的便當真好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.50,0:08:17.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 今天就此解散吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.55,0:08:20.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈還有小圭 明天見
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.98,0:08:24.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魅音 今天多謝你了 我玩的很高興
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.53,0:08:25.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天見
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.00,0:08:32.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也謝謝圭一君你今天陪著我們
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.91,0:08:33.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高興嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.45,0:08:36.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 很高興
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.86,0:08:39.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,高興到覺得現在回家有些可惜呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.46,0:08:45.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我們 稍微繞一下路好嗎 好嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.50,0:08:47.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,繞路? 遠不遠?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.02,0:08:50.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雖然要走一段路 不過很快就到了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.55,0:08:51.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這邊這邊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.60,0:09:00.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久沒來了 今天會有什麼呢 會有什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.05,0:09:02.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久沒來是指...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.85,0:09:06.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈你來 就是為了這座垃圾山啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.22,0:09:11.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這才不是垃圾呢 對礼奈來說這是藏寶山
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.85,0:09:16.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,新的寶山 真讓人興奮 興奮
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.89,0:09:18.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.25,0:09:21.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,痛痛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.18,0:09:24.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 圭一君就呆在那吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.99,0:09:26.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,馬上就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.00,0:09:28.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是鄉下出身的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.17,0:09:30.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比不過啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.13,0:09:45.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嚇了我一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.18,0:09:47.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這句話應該我說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.24,0:09:51.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉 我並不想嚇你的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.36,0:09:54.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是雛見澤本地的人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.61,0:09:59.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫富竹 是個自由攝影師
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.23,0:10:02.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾會來雛見澤拍攝
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.13,0:10:07.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拍照應該要先經過對方同意才算有禮貌吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.45,0:10:11.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉抱歉 因為我主要是拍攝野鳥的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.99,0:10:14.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還從沒機會讓它們同意呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.01,0:10:19.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.81,0:10:24.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉讓你久等了 馬上就結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.19,0:10:26.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來你有同伴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.38,0:10:30.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她在那種地方幹什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.90,0:10:31.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,天知道
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.56,0:10:36.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也許是在找過去被分屍後埋起來的屍體吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.07,0:10:41.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是個令人討厭的事件呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.39,0:10:44.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有一隻手沒找到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.88,0:10:49.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.13,0:10:53.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君 久等了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.70,0:10:57.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 在被馬踢之前我就先告辭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.70,0:10:57.80,zhushi,,0000,0000,0000,,日本有「妨礙別人戀愛者會被馬踢」的俗語
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.32,0:11:01.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉讓你受驚了 圭一君
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.59,0:11:09.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,久等了嗎久等了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.89,0:11:13.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.62,0:11:17.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 結果怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.94,0:11:19.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找到什麼出乎意料的好東西嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.59,0:11:22.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 聽我說聽我說
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.85,0:11:24.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個 我找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.31,0:11:25.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,健太君人偶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.14,0:11:28.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,健太君人偶?  那個嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.55,0:11:32.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,必定擺放在健太君炸雞店前的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.35,0:11:34.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個等身大的人偶?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.15,0:11:38.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 就是健太君
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.89,0:11:42.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好可愛 真想帶回家去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.08,0:11:48.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個是廢品了吧 想帶回家就帶回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.11,0:11:52.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,健太君被垃圾山壓在底下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.47,0:11:55.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不太容易挖出來呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.07,0:11:58.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天我也來幫忙挖吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.57,0:12:01.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,當作是報答你的便當
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.73,0:12:03.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.20,0:12:09.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君會來幫忙 可以把健太君帶回家了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.88,0:12:12.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說 礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.04,0:12:15.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這裡以前出過什麼事嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.24,0:12:18.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,似乎是建過大壩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.21,0:12:21.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不清楚詳細情況
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.94,0:12:22.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,建設大壩?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.36,0:12:27.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是說如果 在建設過程中是不是出了什麼事?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.66,0:12:29.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,意外事故什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.47,0:12:30.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.60,0:12:35.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈到去年為止都住在外頭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.30,0:12:38.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈也是轉校生嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.51,0:12:40.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我還以為你是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.20,0:12:44.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不太清楚來這以前的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.75,0:12:46.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.81,0:12:48.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.14,0:12:49.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.08,0:13:05.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天見
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.82,0:13:08.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.06,0:13:12.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天就遵照會則 詢問各位成員的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.18,0:13:18.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想把他 前原圭一\N作為我們社團的新成員吸收進我們的社團活動中來
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.21,0:13:19.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位意下如何
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.97,0:13:21.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈沒有異議
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.71,0:13:26.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,區區平民能當我的對手嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.39,0:13:30.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我和沙都子都贊成
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.28,0:13:33.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全員一致通過 恭喜你 前原圭一君
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.41,0:13:35.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我批准你加入我們社團
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.65,0:13:38.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂 給我按順序說明 究竟是什麼社團活動
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.87,0:13:41.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且我還沒說過要參加吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.44,0:13:45.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們社團呢 是為了對應複雜化的社會
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.91,0:13:48.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,學習在活動中提供的各種條件下
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.45,0:13:51.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能是順境 也可能是逆境下要如何...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.23,0:13:54.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是大家一起玩遊戲的社團活動
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.89,0:13:56.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我終於明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.43,0:14:00.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我事先跟你說清楚了 這可不是像過家家那種程度的遊戲哦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.79,0:14:02.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你最好還是認真應付
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.48,0:14:06.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要玩的高興就好了嘛 別這樣嚇我嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.73,0:14:07.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太天真了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.22,0:14:10.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會則第一條 唯一的目標就是爭第一
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.06,0:14:13.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不允許抱有只不過是遊戲的想法而隨便敷衍
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.13,0:14:19.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會則第二條 為了達到目的有義務用盡一切可能的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.59,0:14:20.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白了明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.60,0:14:25.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那 太難的遊戲對小圭不利
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.01,0:14:28.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天就選誰都會玩的遊戲吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.71,0:14:32.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,標準的撲克牌抽鬼牌怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.90,0:14:33.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從容應戰
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.29,0:14:38.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,懲罰遊戲就由第一名給倒數第一下一個命令
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.56,0:14:40.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.90,0:14:42.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.04,0:14:45.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就先洗牌
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.48,0:14:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拿走其中一張
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.89,0:14:52.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這副撲克牌上有很多劃傷呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.76,0:14:57.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家該不會可以憑這些傷知道是什麼牌吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.99,0:15:02.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等 等等 怎麼能這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.16,0:15:07.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,會則第二條 為了獲勝有義務用盡一切可能的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.77,0:15:09.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有一些牌的特徵非常明顯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.29,0:15:12.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君馬上也會記住的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.29,0:15:17.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 別以為這種程度就能讓我不利
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.18,0:15:28.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我從右邊開始念小圭的牌嘍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.07,0:15:31.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,3 4 9 J Q
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.01,0:15:36.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,順便告訴你鬼牌是方塊J
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.81,0:15:40.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無論你怎麼換牌還是顯而易見
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.12,0:15:43.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我沒牌了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.20,0:15:49.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惡魔 你們是惡魔
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.87,0:15:52.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈不是惡魔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.41,0:15:57.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 圭一 這張是紅心3吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.18,0:15:58.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒牌了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.00,0:16:14.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是得用乾淨的新牌 否則對圭一君不公平呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.15,0:16:16.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.72,0:16:20.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小圭也是男人嘛 這種程度的逆境有辦法克服的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.14,0:16:23.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.07,0:16:28.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小圭 不要藏了不要藏了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.08,0:16:32.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這傷痕應該是方塊2吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.97,0:16:33.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.92,0:16:38.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小魅會搞錯牌很少見呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.23,0:16:39.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.91,0:16:42.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小圭 難道你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.35,0:16:49.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上當了吧 園崎魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.94,0:16:52.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難道說他偽造了方塊2嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.34,0:16:55.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用了巧妙的花招呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.97,0:16:58.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一 還以顏色了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.83,0:17:01.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,成功了呢 圭一君
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.81,0:17:03.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贏的漂亮 漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.83,0:17:06.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是我看中的成員呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.31,0:17:08.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟然會想到這種手段
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.46,0:17:11.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是小圭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.29,0:17:15.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話雖如此 不過已經為時已晚了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.05,0:17:18.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最後一名反正確定是我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.81,0:17:22.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能在最後從魅音手上討到便宜 我也滿足了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.60,0:17:27.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就對最後一名的小圭實施懲罰吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.61,0:17:32.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天是社團活動的第一天 就從輕鬆的開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.15,0:17:36.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是搞得你突然拒絕來校了我也很困擾呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.59,0:17:39.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.69,0:17:50.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.71,0:17:55.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,健太君人偶?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.46,0:18:00.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此 難怪礼奈那傢伙飛奔回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.17,0:18:05.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,居然覺得那種東西可愛 礼奈也真是奇怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.15,0:18:06.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,趣味雖然也很奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.88,0:18:12.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,更可怕的是礼奈她一旦進入了可愛模式 就不顧一切後果了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.55,0:18:16.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那裡 大壩的工地
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.02,0:18:20.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,發生過什麼事吧 以前
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.44,0:18:26.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,發生過 突然說要建大壩 公務員們單方面逼我們搬離
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.33,0:18:28.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,單方面?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.38,0:18:32.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以就跟他們開戰了 村裡的大家們
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.57,0:18:37.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是沒有開戰的話 現在村子已經因為大壩完全淹沒了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.69,0:18:41.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真虧你們能贏啊  對手可是國家啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.97,0:18:48.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,村長和村裡有權勢的人們向各方面請願 也去了東京
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.38,0:18:51.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還去疏通了不少政治家
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.23,0:18:54.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣做著做著 計劃就被撤消了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.95,0:18:57.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我們的完勝
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.76,0:19:04.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有衍生出什麼暴力事件嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.18,0:19:07.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,傷害事件什麼的 殺人...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.83,0:19:11.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.89,0:19:16.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼明天見
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.86,0:19:20.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小圭 這個在回家之前都不能擦掉哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.98,0:19:24.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道了啦 我不會擦的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.48,0:19:41.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈  真努力呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.85,0:19:47.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君 你怎麼到這種地方來了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.82,0:19:50.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我接到了發生事故的緊急消息 特地趕來
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.32,0:19:53.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,負傷者在哪裡?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.68,0:19:55.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事故是指?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.15,0:20:00.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接到通知說健太君人偶被垃圾山活埋了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.07,0:20:06.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 嚇了我一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.46,0:20:09.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在哪呢 健太君
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.09,0:20:12.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 這裡這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.39,0:20:16.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瞧 能從這縫隙裡看見吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.75,0:20:19.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這還真是 被活埋了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.13,0:20:23.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真要做的話 可能需要斧子或是鋸子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.87,0:20:26.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等我一下 好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.77,0:20:29.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.67,0:20:45.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是令人討厭的事件呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.98,0:20:49.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還有一隻手沒有找到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.69,0:20:52.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.75,0:20:56.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雛見澤大壩發生的有如噩夢的慘劇
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.93,0:20:58.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,私刑分屍殺人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.26,0:21:03.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,犯人們用柴刀和鐵鎬肆意毆打將被害者慘殺
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.53,0:21:08.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還用斧子將遺體的頭部 雙手 雙腳 與身體分成了六份
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.83,0:21:12.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,犯人之一目前依然在逃
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.90,0:21:14.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.57,0:21:16.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.21,0:21:21.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然...是有的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.50,0:21:27.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那時候 叫的令人厭煩的蟬兒們
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.69,0:21:36.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,現在回想起來 也許是想將今後發生的所有一切告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.64,0:21:40.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今後發生的 所有一切
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.26,0:23:20.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能相信嗎? 所看見的事實
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.28,0:23:24.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能相信嗎? 所發現的事實
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.97,0:23:27.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能相信嗎? 我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.03,0:23:30.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,寒蟬鳴泣之時
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.04,0:23:33.84,title,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,0)}鬼\h\h\h\h篇    其之二  秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.04,0:23:33.84,title,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,0)}{\pos(340,472)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\1c&Hff&\be1\b0\fs36}隱
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.85,0:23:37.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你 能相信嗎?
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo & Staff↓
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.50,0:00:40.15,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(87,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord2}{\alpha&H20&}翻譯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.50,0:00:40.15,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(209,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord2}{\alpha&H20&}影
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.50,0:00:40.15,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(87,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord0}翻譯
Dialogue: 1,0:00:37.50,0:00:40.15,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(209,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord0}影
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.90,0:00:59.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(185,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}時間
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.90,0:00:59.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(295,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}JK
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.90,0:00:59.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(185,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}時間
Dialogue: 1,0:00:55.90,0:00:59.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(295,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}JK
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.57,0:01:02.52,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(534,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}特效
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.57,0:01:02.52,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(645,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}怕输囧
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.57,0:01:02.52,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(534,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}特效
Dialogue: 1,0:00:59.57,0:01:02.52,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(645,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}怕输囧

Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.75,0:01:07.80,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(150,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}後 期
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.75,0:01:07.80,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(270,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp-2}{\alpha&H20&}ZilcH「力」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.75,0:01:07.80,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(150,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}後 期
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.75,0:01:07.80,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(270,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp-2}ZilcH「力」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.04,0:01:11.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(485,332)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp35}{\alpha&H20&}片源
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.04,0:01:11.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(660,335)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}tct66
Dialogue: 1,0:01:08.04,0:01:11.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(485,332)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp35}片源
Dialogue: 1,0:01:08.04,0:01:11.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(660,335)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}tct66
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.00,0:00:53.81,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\3c&H454041&}{\bord3}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2135be&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Dialogue: 2,0:00:47.00,0:00:53.81,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\bord1}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2826ef&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Dialogue: 3,0:00:47.00,0:00:53.81,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2826ef&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.12,0:01:08.71,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}振り{\1c&H0f2ff2&}向{\1c&Heaf2f1&}いたその後ろの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.41,0:01:13.45,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}正面{\1c&H0f2ff2&}だ{\1c&Heaf2f1&}ぁれ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.26,0:01:18.23,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}暗{\1c&H0f2ff2&}闇{\1c&Heaf2f1&}に爪を立てて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.28,0:01:22.03,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}夜を引き{\1c&H0f2ff2&}裂{\1c&Heaf2f1&}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.14,0:01:27.73,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}雨だれは{\1c&H0f2ff2&}血{\1c&Heaf2f1&}のしずくとなって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.88,0:01:31.40,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}頬をつたい{\1c&H0f2ff2&}落{\1c&Heaf2f1&}ちる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.62,0:01:41.33,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}もうどこにも帰る{\1c&H0f2ff2&}場所{\1c&Heaf2f1&}が無いなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.72,0:01:46.17,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}この指{\1c&H0f2ff2&}止{\1c&Heaf2f1&}まれ　私の指に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.24,0:01:50.61,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}その指ごと連れて{\1c&H0f2ff2&}っ{\1c&Heaf2f1&}てあげる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.84,0:01:55.28,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}ひぐらしが{\1c&H0f2ff2&}鳴{\1c&Heaf2f1&}く　開かずの{\1c&H0f2ff2&}森{\1c&Heaf2f1&}へ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.47,0:02:02.89,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}後{\1c&H0f2ff2&}戻{\1c&Heaf2f1&}りはもう出来ない
Dialogue: 10,0:01:05.12,0:01:08.71,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}回首望去 紧随身后
Dialogue: 10,0:01:09.41,0:01:13.45,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}正面 是谁?
Dialogue: 10,0:01:14.26,0:01:18.23,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}无尽黑暗 轻点脚尖
Dialogue: 10,0:01:18.28,0:01:22.03,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}黑夜撕裂
Dialogue: 10,0:01:22.14,0:01:27.73,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}雨水化为血滴
Dialogue: 10,0:01:27.88,0:01:31.40,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}从脸颊上流淌而下
Dialogue: 10,0:01:31.62,0:01:41.33,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,9000)}{\be1}既然哪里都已没有归所
Dialogue: 10,0:01:41.72,0:01:46.17,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}收回你的手指 抓住我的手指
Dialogue: 10,0:01:46.24,0:01:50.61,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}连你的手指一起带走
Dialogue: 10,0:01:50.84,0:01:55.28,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}蝉儿鸣叫 封闭之森
Dialogue: 10,0:01:55.47,0:02:02.89,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,6000)}{\be1}已经无法回头
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.12,0:01:08.71,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}回首望去 隐匿身后
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.41,0:01:13.45,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}血{\fn華康正顏楷體W7}髏{\r} 疾首
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.26,0:01:18.23,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}阴暗狂啸 举起双爪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.28,0:01:22.03,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}撕肝断肠
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.14,0:01:27.73,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}雨水化为血滴
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.88,0:01:31.40,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}蹂躏脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.62,0:01:41.33,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(9000,250)}{\be1}后悔撕破母胎失去容身之所
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.72,0:01:46.17,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}让我把你的手指都扭断吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.24,0:01:50.61,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}我会将你连骨头都啃碎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.84,0:01:55.28,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}寒蝉鸣泣 不归之森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.47,0:02:02.89,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(6000,250)}{\be1}回头亦是绝路
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.00,0:22:08.91,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}To get my happiness I had done everything
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.20,0:22:16.01,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}But had done nothing to be blamed and accused of
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.22,0:22:22.99,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}The sound of footsteps became louder every day
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.06,0:22:29.86,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Then I noticed the fact there was no time
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.30,0:22:38.28,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}I was a believer in life to be myself always
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.35,0:22:44.86,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}And was asking whether I would be alive
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.45,0:22:52.39,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}give me a reason why not to adopt in this way
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.50,0:22:59.56,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Or judge me to be guilty to my incurable sins
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.67,0:23:06.47,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Tell me why or why not Complaining way too much
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.58,0:23:14.04,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Maybe I overlooked something fatal for me
