[Script Info]

Title: When_They_Cry #16
Original Script: HKG&X2
Script Type: V4.00+
ScriptType: V4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 864
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.000
WrapStyle: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;
;=== When_They_Cry 寒蟬鳴泣之時 DVDRip作品 ASS字幕外掛發佈訊息 ===
;字幕版本使用HKG字幕組&X2字幕組TV連載字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈 謝謝
;參與製作人員
;翻譯&校對    影
;時間軸       JK & Klaus
;特傚         怕输
;DVDRip&後期  ZilcH「力」
;
Style: Default,simhei,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H300000A0,&HF00000D0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05T,34,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H500000B0,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhushi,simhei,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H300000A0,&HF00000D0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: logo,fzxingkai-s04t,35,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,5,10,10,20,1
Style: op_jap,mikachan-pb,28,&H20EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H80454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,15,1
Style: op_chi,经典繁颜体,26,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,8,1
Style: op_chi2,经典繁颜体,26,&H200F2FF2,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,8,1
Style: ed_jap,s2gmemo,30,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: warning,simhei,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,5,5,5,1
Style: staff,dfkai-sb,25,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.84,0:00:20.91,title,,0000,0000,0000,,明\h\h\h篇    其之一  {\fn方正大标宋_GBK}初戀
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.84,0:00:20.91,title,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(339,471)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\1c&Hff&\be1\b0\fs36}目
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.75,0:02:11.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,万事辛苦了 詩音小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.20,0:02:13.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好久沒有呼吸過外頭的空氣了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.45,0:02:23.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐還精神嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.99,0:02:25.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想應該挺精神
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.91,0:02:28.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 姐姐現在已經不在老家了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.57,0:02:31.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在雛見澤的鬼婆那吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.03,0:02:36.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 和詩音小姐進學院同時
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.42,0:02:37.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她轉去了本家那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.59,0:02:46.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我和魅音是雙胞胎 從頭到腳都是對方的完美複製
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.57,0:02:51.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我卻被幽閉在遠方的學校裡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.77,0:02:55.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐則是作為園崎家的繼承人被撫養長大
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.06,0:03:01.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,原本詩音這個存在對園崎家而言就是惹人厭的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.93,0:03:04.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本家的繼承人如果有兩位的話
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.05,0:03:07.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,由于將會成為往後带来災禍的種子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.89,0:03:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,按照本家的慣例
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.40,0:03:10.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果產下雙胞胎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.91,0:03:14.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在嬰兒第一次洗澡之前就應該掐死
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.40,0:03:16.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還真是够厉害的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.88,0:03:21.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果回到興宮市的話 一定會被一些親戚看到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.62,0:03:25.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最後始終會被本家的人知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.62,0:03:30.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這個嘛 的確會很糟糕呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.12,0:03:40.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要開動了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.90,0:03:42.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等一會告诉我需要些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.62,0:03:45.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我會盡量為你湊齊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.05,0:03:49.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝了 但是我想著要去打工呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.49,0:03:52.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,生活費還是得自己賺才好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.52,0:03:54.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.59,0:03:56.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為了不被發現我已經有些考量了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.52,0:04:01.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好 這裡是園崎家
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.37,0:04:04.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 葛西先生 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.44,0:04:06.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.43,0:04:08.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂喂
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.50,0:04:12.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道我是誰嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.22,0:04:16.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這聲音是…你該不會從學校裡逃了出來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.08,0:04:24.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那樣死板的地方 怎麼可能一直呆下去嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.99,0:04:27.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後就逃走了? 真行啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.02,0:04:34.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,久违了的姐姐的聲音令人懷念
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.23,0:04:39.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 如果沒有園崎家的事的話
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.48,0:04:41.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們是一对很要好的姐妹
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.20,0:04:42.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\a6\fs23}所以想要姐姐幫一个小忙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.19,0:04:45.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 好的 那麼之後我再聯繫你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.04,0:04:49.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最後談的怎麼樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.83,0:04:53.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,義郎叔父不是一直很疼我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.59,0:04:56.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想去叔父的某家店裡打工
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.39,0:04:58.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那樣會被人看到的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.24,0:05:01.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為此才需要姐姐幫忙嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.33,0:05:09.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說  我打工時只要說是魅音就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.53,0:05:13.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明白了 這樣的話就交給我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.96,0:05:16.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 還真是辛苦吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.29,0:05:21.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被關在那種地方近两年
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.93,0:05:23.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我原本就是反對的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.00,0:05:24.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.57,0:05:29.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是園崎本家的家主又那麼頑固
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.92,0:05:33.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為了能讓詩音安心工作
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.76,0:05:35.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也會盡量合作的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.93,0:05:37.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就多多指教了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.57,0:05:41.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 這兩年以來有什麼變化嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.12,0:05:44.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也沒什麼太大的變化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.67,0:05:47.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,御社神大人作祟的事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.03,0:05:49.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,犯人抓到了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.51,0:05:53.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個大壩監督被分屍的事件嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.68,0:05:57.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有 犯人應該還沒抓到吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.03,0:06:00.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第二年的案子更是毫無頭緒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.58,0:06:05.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,贊成大壩計劃的男人和他的妻子摔死的那件事?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.12,0:06:07.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叫什麼北條的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.90,0:06:10.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且又是在綿流的晚上
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.85,0:06:14.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,「只可能是作祟了」 當時吵的很厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.46,0:06:20.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其實在詩音去學校後沒多久又發生過
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.78,0:06:22.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又發生過是…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.30,0:06:24.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,連續三年?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.16,0:06:26.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.91,0:06:31.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,古手神社 那裡的神主在祭典的晚上突然就…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.27,0:06:36.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听说似乎是死於原因不明的怪病
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.82,0:06:40.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他老婆也在當天晚上跳入沼澤了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.22,0:06:43.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是第三年的事件
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.98,0:06:52.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 怪病什麼的可能是夸大其词 突然死亡是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.94,0:06:58.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想應該是急性心力衰竭之類的常見病吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.60,0:07:01.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 發生在綿流那天就显得異常了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.86,0:07:06.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且三年連續 死者又都是些感覺有可能遭遇作祟的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.51,0:07:06.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.76,0:07:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,神主記得也被人討厭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.86,0:07:12.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被反對大壩的人們討厭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.74,0:07:16.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 因為他替北條家說過話嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.62,0:07:20.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,表明接受大壩計劃的北條夫妻
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.86,0:07:22.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被當作村子的叛徒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.69,0:07:25.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,受到了八成以上的村民的指責
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.72,0:07:29.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都以冰冷的眼神在背后骂着他们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.14,0:07:34.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而村中唯一一個沒有敵視北條夫妻的就是神主
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.44,0:07:38.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對於想以北條家為替罪羊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.11,0:07:41.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,進一步增強村民團結的御三家來說
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.43,0:07:44.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同是御三家的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.73,0:07:48.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,並且還是祭祀著反大壩的象徵的御社神大人的神社的神主
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.97,0:07:50.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,卻容忍了他們
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.24,0:07:53.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這一定非常不痛快吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.31,0:07:57.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 現在回想起來
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.77,0:08:01.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要保持中立的神主先生 挺成熟的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.08,0:08:04.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果真的成熟的話
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.58,0:08:07.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想那時就應該順應周圍的形勢進行協調了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.97,0:08:10.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,應該作為雛見澤的榜樣的御三家的人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.21,0:08:14.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,卻自己破壞了團結 這究竟能否算成熟呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.57,0:08:16.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得很難理解呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.87,0:08:22.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐不知不覺也像下任家主的樣子了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.02,0:08:25.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底是學過帝王學了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.31,0:08:28.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才沒學那種東西啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.86,0:08:31.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是在想要怎樣才能像婆婆一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.71,0:08:33.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,詩音也能做到的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.61,0:08:36.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我才不想幹那種事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.98,0:08:40.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,鬼婆的保姆就交給魅音去做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.79,0:08:43.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,總之在保重身體的前提下加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.02,0:08:45.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但…但是 詩音
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.38,0:08:51.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 我從來沒有憎恨過你或是自己的出生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.31,0:08:54.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不用覺得有什麼愧疚的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.49,0:08:56.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,加油吧 魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.92,0:08:58.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也會加油做我的詩音
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.97,0:09:00.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你 詩音
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.46,0:09:03.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.88,0:09:06.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已經暴露了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.45,0:09:08.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,婆婆很生氣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.47,0:09:10.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說是一找到就立刻帶到自己跟前來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.54,0:09:14.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真可怕 有什麼事的話再聯繫我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.26,0:09:19.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果事情真的不妙了 我打算離開這個城市
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.57,0:09:24.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只有詩音你遭受這樣不自由的待遇不公平啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.29,0:09:27.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝 你有這份心我就很高興了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.37,0:09:30.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想出門的時候就告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.20,0:09:34.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我隨時會幫你 讓詩音能成為魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.10,0:09:37.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其實這點才是最有幫助的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.99,0:09:40.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為暫時還是不要出門比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.61,0:09:42.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前想多買點東西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.20,0:09:53.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個 這個也買了 那個也買了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.90,0:09:54.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 接著就只剩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.45,0:10:04.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 別停在這種地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.68,0:10:13.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 下一處下一處
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.18,0:10:27.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你搞什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.56,0:10:29.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,信不信我們廢了你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.40,0:10:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你有在聽嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.00,0:10:35.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 實在翻譯不出了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.10,0:10:38.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.07,0:10:47.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你們適可而止吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.58,0:10:49.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.76,0:10:57.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,巡警先生 是這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.41,0:10:58.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.27,0:11:02.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你給我記住
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.44,0:11:05.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.63,0:11:08.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧 魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.31,0:11:10.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.00,0:11:13.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事就太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.70,0:11:20.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是 與悟史的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.63,0:11:35.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那應該是悟史吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.51,0:11:40.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,外表也好 還有摸別人頭的習慣 應該不會錯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.72,0:11:43.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他叫悟史啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.68,0:11:46.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不過平時他呆呆的哎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.29,0:11:49.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹倒比他能幹多了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.53,0:11:50.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他有妹妹嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.73,0:11:52.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的 叫沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.27,0:11:56.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最近發生了不少事 精神不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.87,0:11:59.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,悟史就是那北條夫妻的兒子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.26,0:12:05.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雙親去世之後就和妹妹一起被叔父叔母收養了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.52,0:12:09.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但近一年叔母和沙都子的關係不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.20,0:12:12.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,難道是被虐待了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.61,0:12:13.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子已經快累垮了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.82,0:12:17.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,單單只是大壩贊成派的北條家的親戚
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.10,0:12:20.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,叔父夫婦應該就已經受到不少人的排擠了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.83,0:12:23.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又被強加了兩個孩子到頭上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.32,0:12:27.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自然是只有憎恨沒有憐愛了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.28,0:12:31.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 悟史平時也會很累吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.11,0:12:36.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼說呢 一直呆呆的看不太出來啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.80,0:12:41.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 悟史他一定會袒護妹妹的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.21,0:12:44.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就像袒護了我一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.71,0:12:48.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說 姐姐 再告訴我一些有關悟史的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.22,0:12:51.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下午好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.82,0:12:55.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來送慰勞品嗎 真是謝謝了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.54,0:12:57.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是我們隊的經理人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.28,0:13:00.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要隨便把人當作經理人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.24,0:13:02.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是不行嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.96,0:13:08.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幹得好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.55,0:13:11.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要介意不要介意
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.14,0:13:14.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很厲害嘛 悟史他
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.69,0:13:17.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吧 只要集中精神打棒球的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.27,0:13:20.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他的安打率可以達到3成哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.19,0:13:24.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他實在是個太纖細的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.52,0:13:27.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不運動運動 出一身汗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.98,0:13:32.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,短時間也好忘記家裡的事 轉換一下心情的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.60,0:13:34.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能真的會垮掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.14,0:13:38.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,悟史他是會忍耐的類型
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.74,0:13:42.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最近好像身體狀況又很差了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.80,0:13:48.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為叔母對沙都子欺負的更厲害了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.90,0:13:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為了袒護她悟史也很辛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.27,0:13:57.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事實上最近他還說想離隊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.59,0:13:59.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.24,0:14:01.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說是因為累了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.20,0:14:08.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,實際上是想增加一些時間陪沙都子吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.40,0:14:10.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,果然袒護了妹妹嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.00,0:14:12.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快冲快冲
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.31,0:14:16.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,出局
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.42,0:14:18.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後 悟史他
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.33,0:14:25.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,從那天以後 就沒有再出現在賽場上了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.57,0:14:30.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小魅 下午好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.91,0:14:34.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.52,0:14:40.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好大的雨
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.95,0:14:47.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小魅喜歡悟史嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.82,0:14:49.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.80,0:14:51.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就笑吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.34,0:14:58.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想小魅的笑容一定能分些活力給悟史的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.60,0:15:02.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他也一定會回來參加棒球的訓練的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.53,0:15:03.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等打工結束後
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.11,0:15:04.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打工?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.27,0:15:06.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幾時會結束呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.20,0:15:09.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,說是要等湊夠錢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.92,0:15:13.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無論多晚 在沙都子的生日之前也會結束吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.72,0:15:15.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,又是沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.15,0:15:20.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子會讓悟史得病
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.83,0:15:23.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子會奪走悟史的自由
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.09,0:15:26.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小魅
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.06,0:15:32.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子太粘悟史了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.93,0:15:34.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果沙都子再振作一點的話
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.28,0:15:37.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,悟史也不會被逼到這個地步
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.22,0:15:40.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你說的真直接
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.25,0:15:44.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,悟史可能也多少有一點這種想法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.88,0:15:48.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這件事應該是要保密的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.18,0:15:50.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小魅聽了也要保密哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.14,0:15:54.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其實昨天 悟史這麼說過
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.18,0:15:58.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對於作為哥哥被依靠一事感覺到痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.31,0:16:00.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還說這種想法是有罪的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.15,0:16:04.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,悟史很信任礼奈呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.46,0:16:07.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,並不是信任啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.67,0:16:11.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想是因為我是過來人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.46,0:16:13.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,過來人?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.91,0:16:16.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啪嗒啪嗒的 腳步聲一直緊隨著
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.87,0:16:22.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚上一直跟到枕邊上 被人俯視的經驗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.44,0:16:35.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,悟史所經歷的 全都是御社神大人作祟的前兆
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.37,0:16:38.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,御社神大人…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.87,0:16:41.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼人一直在遠方窺伺著
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.83,0:16:44.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼人一直跟在身後
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.24,0:16:48.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有什麼人一直在身後望著自己
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.99,0:16:51.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最後腳步聲總是和自己的腳步聲錯開
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.96,0:16:54.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,聽起來像多了一聲腳步聲
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.95,0:16:57.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,並且 即使鑽進被窩關上燈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.38,0:17:00.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,還是會在枕边一直俯視著你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.56,0:17:03.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一句話也不說 只是默默俯視著
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.25,0:17:06.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,直到你承認自己的罪行為止
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.64,0:17:09.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會 悟史有什麼罪行
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.34,0:17:15.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 悟史身在雛見澤還是受了作祟
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.05,0:17:17.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,理由只有一個
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.76,0:17:21.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為悟史想要捨棄這裡逃往遠方
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.18,0:17:25.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這種想法 御社神大人不能原諒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.48,0:17:31.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 讓我去學校
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.67,0:17:36.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 悟史
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.73,0:17:44.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那…那個 你還好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.26,0:17:47.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好 為什麼這麼問
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.73,0:17:50.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因為你打工很辛苦嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.65,0:17:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想是不是累了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.61,0:17:53.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就這些話要說?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.75,0:17:55.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.42,0:17:59.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,監督說想讓你再去訓練
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.70,0:18:02.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我已經告訴監督了 我不會回去的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.83,0:18:07.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾 去運動一下流點汗也不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.01,0:18:08.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒興趣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.59,0:18:12.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不吃嗎 小魅
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.79,0:18:14.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,悟史 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.36,0:18:20.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起吃飯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.92,0:18:25.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我說了多少次了 午休就讓我一個人靜靜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.51,0:18:42.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 我們分給你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.04,0:18:43.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一起吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.34,0:18:48.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幫幫我 幫幫我  兄兄
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.88,0:19:00.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼 知道為什麼你會遭受這样的待遇嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.91,0:19:05.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,救救我 救救我 兄兄
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.39,0:19:10.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兄兄
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.79,0:19:12.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是因為你這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.08,0:19:15.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想哭你就哭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.55,0:19:18.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 哭是不能解決問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.14,0:19:22.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼要哭 因為哭了就會有人來幫你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.80,0:19:27.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你根本無法想像這個來幫你的人代替你受了多少傷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.49,0:19:30.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你明白嗎 你的罪行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.88,0:19:34.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你這種人不在就好 如果辛苦的話就去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.72,0:19:36.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要讓悟史也一起痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.41,0:19:39.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一個人痛苦 隨便去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.97,0:19:42.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,像你這樣的人 去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.49,0:19:45.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兄兄
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.94,0:19:50.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別以為哭就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.95,0:19:52.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別以為向悟史求救就沒事了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.16,0:19:56.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只要你 只要沒有你的話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.73,0:20:00.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,別欺負沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.00,0:20:04.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子這麼可憐 不能欺負她
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.34,0:20:10.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我啊 是在矫正她這軟弱的品性
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.01,0:20:13.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是敢妨礙就从你的头上…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.39,0:20:16.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,小魅 住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.61,0:20:24.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兄兄 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.46,0:20:26.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兄兄 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.73,0:20:29.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,兄兄
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.34,0:20:32.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這是怎麼回事 魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.01,0:20:34.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.94,0:20:36.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子究竟做錯什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.06,0:20:38.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我們究竟做錯了什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.38,0:20:42.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼總是要欺負我們
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.41,0:20:47.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,全村人將爸爸和媽媽逼上絕路
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.33,0:20:49.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想盡辦法欺負他們
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.14,0:20:52.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然後現在又輪到我們
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.89,0:20:55.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這就是園崎家的做法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.07,0:21:03.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,詩音 你也為我想想嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.03,0:21:04.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.96,0:21:07.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.36,0:21:12.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,实际上 悟史很恨園崎家吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.56,0:21:14.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想是的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.92,0:21:16.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那為什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.06,0:21:18.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼到現在才…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.34,0:21:20.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話索性一開始就…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.73,0:21:28.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 如果第一次見面時就用拒絕的眼神看著我的話
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.70,0:21:32.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不會想要接近悟史
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.45,0:21:37.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我祈禱著
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.28,0:21:42.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今年的作祟讓叔母和沙都子消失掉就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.62,0:23:18.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所失去的 是平日的歸路
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.88,0:23:22.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無法守護的 是與你的約定
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.76,0:23:26.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,無法消去的 是我的回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.09,0:23:29.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,寒蟬鳴泣之時
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.23,0:23:36.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你 能相信嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.05,0:23:34.03,title,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,0)}明\h\h\h篇    其之二  了{\fn方正大标宋_GBK}斷
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.05,0:23:34.03,title,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,0)}{\pos(339,471)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\1c&Hff&\be1\b0\fs36}目
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo & Staff↓
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:28.12,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(87,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord2}{\alpha&H20&}翻譯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.47,0:00:28.12,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(209,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord2}{\alpha&H20&}影
Dialogue: 1,0:00:25.47,0:00:28.12,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(87,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord0}翻譯
Dialogue: 1,0:00:25.47,0:00:28.12,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(209,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord0}影
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.82,0:00:46.97,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(185,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}時間
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.82,0:00:46.97,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(295,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}Klaus
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.82,0:00:46.97,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(185,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}時間
Dialogue: 1,0:00:43.82,0:00:46.97,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(295,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}Klaus
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.54,0:00:50.49,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(534,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}特效
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.54,0:00:50.49,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(645,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}怕输囧
Dialogue: 1,0:00:47.54,0:00:50.49,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(534,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}特效
Dialogue: 1,0:00:47.54,0:00:50.49,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(645,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}怕输囧

Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.67,0:00:55.77,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(150,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}後 期
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.67,0:00:55.77,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(270,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp-2}{\alpha&H20&}ZilcH「力」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.67,0:00:55.77,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(150,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}後 期
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.67,0:00:55.77,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(270,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp-2}ZilcH「力」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.87,0:00:41.78,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\3c&H454041&}{\bord3}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2135be&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Dialogue: 2,0:00:34.87,0:00:41.78,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\bord1}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2826ef&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Dialogue: 3,0:00:34.87,0:00:41.78,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2826ef&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.04,0:00:56.63,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}振り{\1c&H0f2ff2&}向{\1c&Heaf2f1&}いたその後ろの
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.33,0:01:01.37,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}正面{\1c&H0f2ff2&}だ{\1c&Heaf2f1&}ぁれ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.18,0:01:06.15,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}暗{\1c&H0f2ff2&}闇{\1c&Heaf2f1&}に爪を立てて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.20,0:01:09.95,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}夜を引き{\1c&H0f2ff2&}裂{\1c&Heaf2f1&}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.06,0:01:15.65,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}雨だれは{\1c&H0f2ff2&}血{\1c&Heaf2f1&}のしずくとなって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.80,0:01:19.32,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}頬をつたい{\1c&H0f2ff2&}落{\1c&Heaf2f1&}ちる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.54,0:01:29.25,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}もうどこにも帰る{\1c&H0f2ff2&}場所{\1c&Heaf2f1&}が無いなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.64,0:01:34.09,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}この指{\1c&H0f2ff2&}止{\1c&Heaf2f1&}まれ　私の指に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.16,0:01:38.53,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}その指ごと連れて{\1c&H0f2ff2&}っ{\1c&Heaf2f1&}てあげる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.76,0:01:43.20,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}ひぐらしが{\1c&H0f2ff2&}鳴{\1c&Heaf2f1&}く　開かずの{\1c&H0f2ff2&}森{\1c&Heaf2f1&}へ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.39,0:01:50.81,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}後{\1c&H0f2ff2&}戻{\1c&Heaf2f1&}りはもう出来ない
Dialogue: 10,0:00:53.04,0:00:56.63,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}回首望去 紧随身后
Dialogue: 10,0:00:57.33,0:01:01.37,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}正面 是谁?
Dialogue: 10,0:01:02.18,0:01:06.15,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}无尽黑暗 轻点脚尖
Dialogue: 10,0:01:06.20,0:01:09.95,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}黑夜撕裂
Dialogue: 10,0:01:10.06,0:01:15.65,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}雨水化为血滴
Dialogue: 10,0:01:15.80,0:01:19.32,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}从脸颊上流淌而下
Dialogue: 10,0:01:19.54,0:01:29.25,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,9000)}{\be1}既然哪里都已没有归所
Dialogue: 10,0:01:29.64,0:01:34.09,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}收回你的手指 抓住我的手指
Dialogue: 10,0:01:34.16,0:01:38.53,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}连你的手指一起带走
Dialogue: 10,0:01:38.76,0:01:43.20,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}蝉儿鸣叫 封闭之森
Dialogue: 10,0:01:43.39,0:01:50.81,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,6000)}{\be1}已经无法回头
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.04,0:00:56.63,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}回首望去 隐匿身后
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.33,0:01:01.37,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}血{\fn華康正顏楷體W7}髏{\r} 疾首
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.18,0:01:06.15,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}阴暗狂啸 举起双爪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.20,0:01:09.95,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}撕肝断肠
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.06,0:01:15.65,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}雨水化为血滴
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.80,0:01:19.32,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}蹂躏脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.54,0:01:29.25,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(9000,250)}{\be1}后悔撕破母胎失去容身之所
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.64,0:01:34.09,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}让我把你的手指都扭断吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.16,0:01:38.53,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}我会将你连骨头都啃碎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.76,0:01:43.20,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}寒蝉鸣泣 不归之森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.39,0:01:50.81,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(6000,250)}{\be1}回头亦是绝路
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.14,0:22:09.05,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}To get my happiness I had done everything
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.34,0:22:16.15,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}But had done nothing to be blamed and accused of
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.36,0:22:23.13,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}The sound of footsteps became louder every day
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.20,0:22:30.00,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Then I noticed the fact there was no time
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.44,0:22:38.42,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}I was a believer in life to be myself always
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.49,0:22:45.00,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}And was asking whether I would be alive
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.59,0:22:52.53,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}give me a reason why not to adopt in this way
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.64,0:22:59.70,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Or judge me to be guilty to my incurable sins
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.81,0:23:06.61,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Tell me why or why not Complaining way too much
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.72,0:23:14.18,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Maybe I overlooked something fatal for me







