[Script Info]
; This is a Sub Station Alpha v4 script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;
; Script created by cySub 1.4.0 Release Build 1203
;
Title: When_They_Cry #07
Original Script: HKG&X2
Script Type: V4.00+
ScriptType: V4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 864
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.000
WrapStyle: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;
;=== When_They_Cry 寒蟬鳴泣之時 DVDRip作品 ASS字幕外掛發佈訊息 ===
;字幕版本使用HKG字幕組&X2字幕組TV連載字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈 謝謝
;參與製作人員
;翻譯&校對    影
;時間軸       JK & Klaus
;特傚         怕输
;DVDRip&後期  ZilcH「力」
;片源         TCT66
;
Style: Default,simhei,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H300000A0,&HF00000D0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05T,34,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H500000B0,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhushi,simhei,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H300000A0,&HF00000D0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: logo,fzxingkai-s04t,35,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,5,10,10,20,1
Style: op_jap,mikachan-pb,28,&H20EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H80454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,15,1
Style: op_chi,经典繁颜体,26,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,8,1
Style: op_chi2,经典繁颜体,26,&H200F2FF2,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,8,1
Style: ed_jap,s2gmemo,30,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: warning,simhei,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,5,5,5,1
Style: staff,dfkai-sb,25,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.00,0:01:04.06,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正大标宋_GBK}綿{\r}\h\h\h\h篇    其之三  {\fn方正大标宋_GBK}謊言
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.00,0:01:04.06,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(339,471)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\1c&Hff&\be1\b0\fs36}流
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.55,0:00:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定是和我一樣 在什麼地方迷路了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.91,0:00:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迷...迷路真好 真想帶回家去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.22,0:00:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是個老爺爺吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.67,0:00:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許只是有些癡呆 在到處徘徊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.29,0:00:25.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村長先生可是個教大家習字和劍道的精力充沛的人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.76,0:00:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是怎麼了 難道說是受御社神大人作祟
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.00,0:00:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天午後 村長先生為了聚會前往了神社的集會所
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.44,0:00:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而快天黑的時候 聚會結束了 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.55,0:00:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那以後 就再沒有人見過村長先生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.89,0:02:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣一來就是連續五年發生御社神大人作祟事件了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.59,0:02:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你相信作祟嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.18,0:02:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是人為的話 雛見澤的某人就是犯人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.39,0:02:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果要作祟的話 目標應該是進入祭具殿的我和詩音啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.67,0:03:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 梨花啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.95,0:03:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花 摔倒了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.36,0:03:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 不是的 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.93,0:03:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟發生了什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.89,0:03:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒什麼關係
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.93,0:03:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起這個
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.92,0:03:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祭典那天晚上你有沒有做過什麼壞事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.40,0:03:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭一
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.77,0:03:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉問你奇怪的問題
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.98,0:03:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請忘了它吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.49,0:03:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.62,0:04:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想告訴你 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.70,0:04:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是梨花你是那個神社的巫女
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.40,0:04:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是最不能饒恕別人打破禁忌的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.82,0:04:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祭典那一晚 似乎有只小貓進入了神社祭具殿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.10,0:04:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貓?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.00,0:04:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 小貓 喵喵的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.03,0:04:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓看了看裡面 大吃一驚 非常害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.37,0:04:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是一溜煙的跑掉了 喀嗒喀嗒噗嚕噗嚕喵喵
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.95,0:04:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很辛苦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.98,0:04:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那麼 這隻小貓 今後要怎麼做才好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.03,0:04:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.48,0:04:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貓抱著惡作劇的心態闖進去的一幕被小狗看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.65,0:04:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小狗們輪流來到小貓那裡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.97,0:04:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,質問它有沒有闖進去過
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.60,0:04:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 我會保護小貓的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.70,0:04:59.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.78,0:05:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想幾隻小狗一定只是誤會了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.79,0:05:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然有些辛苦 但我會加油的 fight on!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.58,0:05:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.62,0:05:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貓姐姐很生氣 因為貓妹妹做了壞事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.80,0:05:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以十分生氣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.29,0:05:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天開始不要參加社團活動了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.38,0:05:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你暫時讓貓姐姐靜一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.43,0:05:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貓姐姐是指魅音嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.70,0:05:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭一 如果发现因为誤會而咬了村長的小狗\n想咬小貓的話請通知我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.26,0:05:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這天晚上 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.79,0:06:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就為雖說用了比喻 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.43,0:06:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是將一切告訴梨花這件事而後悔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.83,0:06:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花說的話不可理解
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.18,0:06:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不止如此 簡直就像是當事人似的詳細訴說著
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.81,0:06:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭一  有你的電話
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.00,0:06:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,園崎小姐打來的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.84,0:06:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.53,0:06:21.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是詩音
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.58,0:06:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩音 那個 昨天對不起了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.14,0:06:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不覺就太興奮
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.12,0:06:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和詩音都是同樣的立場呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.07,0:06:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉單方面責備你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.79,0:06:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你知道後悔的話我就原諒你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.18,0:06:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從今以後我們互相察覺到什麼的話就向對方報告吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.32,0:06:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是命運共同體
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.76,0:06:47.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.51,0:06:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.29,0:06:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說公由爺爺失蹤了 這是真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.49,0:06:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公由? 哦 是說村長嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.67,0:07:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 似乎是這樣 詩音不知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.91,0:07:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 怎麼辦 我昨天把那個晚上的事情告訴給村長知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.35,0:07:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.37,0:07:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我害的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.22,0:07:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別這樣 不是詩音的錯啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.65,0:07:15.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是我的錯  
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.98,0:07:18.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我剛告訴他就...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.61,0:07:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天晚上立刻就消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.59,0:07:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我告訴了他才被殺的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.77,0:07:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我坦白了出來他才被殺的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.39,0:07:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我告訴了他才被殺的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.65,0:07:30.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他知道了才被殺的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.72,0:07:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為坦白了出來他才被殺 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.22,0:07:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也告訴梨花了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.23,0:07:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花?!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.90,0:07:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 礼奈 你的電話
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.51,0:07:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫圭一的打來的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.89,0:07:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再確認一次 你向梨花家打過電話了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.70,0:07:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後一直都沒人聽所以覺得擔心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.64,0:08:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我想響了有十分鐘了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.85,0:08:05.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花的家並不是非常大 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.75,0:08:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還有沙都子在 應該不會沒察覺到的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.66,0:08:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 礼奈 小圭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.87,0:08:17.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之去看看吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.30,0:08:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.21,0:08:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 真奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.10,0:08:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.43,0:08:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花和沙都子平時總是把自行車停在這裡的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.84,0:08:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花 沙都子 你們在嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.97,0:08:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花 沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.15,0:09:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鎖上了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.65,0:09:03.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二樓的窗戶什麼的呢 也許窗戶開著
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.66,0:09:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭 給你梯子 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.78,0:09:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.92,0:09:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去看看本家那邊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.33,0:09:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本家?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.64,0:09:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是指古手家的本家 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.54,0:09:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自從梨花的雙親去世之後 似乎就一直閒置著
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.99,0:09:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是哦 梨花的雙親是…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.98,0:09:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子也是一樣 因為御社神大人作祟
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.02,0:09:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雙親從懸崖上掉了下去 哥哥悟史也失蹤
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.49,0:09:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從那以後 梨花和沙都子就一起在這裡生活
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.31,0:09:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們兩個都很辛苦呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.08,0:09:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是被詛咒了 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.46,0:09:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說是被詛咒了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.16,0:09:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.10,0:09:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北條沙都子啊\n 是將御社神大人的詛咒集於一身的詛咒之子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.78,0:09:57.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悟史也為了他那麼唯一一個妹妹 不辭辛勞拚命努力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.50,0:09:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卻被抹消了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.34,0:10:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可憐的悟史君 得不到任何回報的悟史君 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.00,0:10:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子是詛咒之子 接近那孩子的話\N不是因作祟而死就是因作祟而消失
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.85,0:10:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子又怎麼可能有安穩的日子過
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.42,0:10:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花消失一定也是沙都子害的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.54,0:10:15.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 沒錯 沒錯 沒錯 沒錯

Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.98,0:10:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯沒錯沒錯沒錯沒錯…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.60,0:10:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 冷靜一點 魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.50,0:10:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小魅 圭一君 我把鑰匙借來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.75,0:10:30.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 幫大忙了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.54,0:10:33.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧 小圭 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.71,0:10:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一刻我第一次覺得\N可能還存在著與我所認識的魅音截然不同的魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.76,0:10:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子 梨花 在的話就回答我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.05,0:11:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,究竟去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.43,0:11:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與其說是去了哪裡…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.59,0:11:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我不想這麼想
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.50,0:11:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是村長昨天剛失蹤今天就… 恐怕不是沒有聯繫的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.53,0:11:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.81,0:11:33.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我害的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.65,0:11:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.87,0:11:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我不好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.59,0:11:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因為我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.55,0:11:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君 說是小孩已經可以回家去休息了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.08,0:11:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是因為我才消失的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.44,0:11:57.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你這麼想 這麼想
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.09,0:12:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道圭一君你很為夥伴著想
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.81,0:12:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是礼奈知道這不是圭一的錯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.70,0:12:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也知道圭一沒有錯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.76,0:12:14.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.97,0:12:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒有告訴過礼奈 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.54,0:12:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圭一君该不会是在想礼奈是不是也會消失吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.79,0:12:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就放心吧 礼奈不會消失的 絕對不會
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.68,0:12:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼能這麼自信的說自己不會消失
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.46,0:12:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.12,0:12:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小魅她 恐怕今天是起不來了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.50,0:12:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是哦 前天晚上也為了找村長一宿沒睡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.89,0:12:53.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.87,0:12:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花和沙都子究竟去哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.70,0:13:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽富田豆腐店的老婆婆她說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.30,0:13:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她記得昨天看到沙都子在回家路上到她的店裡買豆腐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.78,0:13:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豆腐?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.62,0:13:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.47,0:13:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天梨花家的煤氣灶上有著鍋子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.38,0:13:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面有醬湯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.01,0:13:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這又怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.12,0:13:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醬湯裡的豆腐是要在最後才放入鍋內的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.08,0:13:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是說正在做飯的梨花
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.45,0:13:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到即将開飯之前都站在那裡做著飯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.04,0:13:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也看了看電飯煲裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.41,0:13:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡頭剩著兩人份的米飯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.22,0:13:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冰箱裡還有幾樣沒碰過的小菜
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.06,0:13:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且全都被保鮮膜包住了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.91,0:13:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.30,0:13:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上保鮮膜應該是吃不完或吃剩時才这么做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.04,0:13:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得這是怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.65,0:13:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 那就是說不需要留在家吃飯了…吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.09,0:13:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還是突然之间 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.27,0:14:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果事先知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.85,0:14:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不會去做什麼飯了 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.39,0:14:03.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.56,0:14:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失蹤时间就是在晚飯剛做好时
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.78,0:14:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大約7點左右
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.78,0:14:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種時間了他們還跑去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.97,0:14:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還記得嗎 在飯桌的上頭放著倒醬油的小瓶
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.76,0:14:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裝醬油的小瓶是空的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.25,0:14:21.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再去水池子底下找了找 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.18,0:14:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都放在那兒的醬油大瓶也不見了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.99,0:14:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼意思……
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.66,0:14:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來的就是想像了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.82,0:14:34.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想應該是拿著醬油瓶去向附近的鄰居要醬油了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.51,0:14:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子因為梨花一直都沒有回來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.92,0:14:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就向她去要醬油的家裡打了電話
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.10,0:14:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花有沒有去拜訪你們
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.22,0:14:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想對方應該是這樣回答的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.41,0:14:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們家已經準備好了晚飯 沙都子也一起來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.64,0:14:58.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨花已經在吃了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.26,0:15:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 梨花究竟去哪裡要醬油了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.28,0:15:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈的推理就到此為止了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.42,0:15:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,始終只是想像而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.43,0:15:17.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前原先生 你好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.89,0:15:21.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼警察局的人要找圭一君
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.41,0:15:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是犯人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.30,0:15:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這我當然知道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.78,0:15:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先去吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.03,0:15:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 再見
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.00,0:15:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把我帶回警察局嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.44,0:15:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是不是 站著說話不太方便 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.20,0:15:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想叫你上車聊聊而已
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.90,0:15:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 搜查方面怎麼樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.11,0:15:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搜查 是哪件事? 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.82,0:15:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近要搜查的事情太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.29,0:15:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不知你說哪件
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.82,0:15:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我指全部
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.09,0:15:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊… 全部啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.24,0:16:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富竹先生和鷹野先生的事情 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.79,0:16:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可恥 沒有任何進展
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.60,0:16:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村長那邊怎麼樣 有什麼線索了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.83,0:16:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們掌握了他的一點行蹤 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.31,0:16:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在前天他失蹤之前 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.75,0:16:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一大清早就去了鹿骨市內的某大學病院肛門科就診
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.12,0:16:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肛門科?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.36,0:16:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 對他家人也好對任何人都保密 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.94,0:16:28.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是他的自尊心不允許吧 肛門科什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.58,0:16:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接著在回家的路上似乎遇到電車事故
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.89,0:16:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到家後立刻就匆匆趕往神社參加聚會了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.05,0:16:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 有什麼事讓你在意嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.75,0:16:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.03,0:16:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我昨天向公由爺爺坦白了 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.04,0:16:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼時候 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.94,0:16:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就说了 昨天富竹先生和鷹野小姐似乎死了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.15,0:16:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村長失蹤是在前天
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.11,0:17:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從詩音那裡聽說富竹先生與鷹野小姐的事也是前天早上
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.68,0:17:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是村長先生大清早就瞞著所有人去了醫院
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.09,0:17:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天我坦白了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.12,0:17:12.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩音是什麼時候坦白的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.06,0:17:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前原先生 前原先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.71,0:17:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽好了 我並不是認為你是犯人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.85,0:17:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道那天晚上你們四個人潛入了祭具殿
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.87,0:17:31.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為在第二天已經有人在傳了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.88,0:17:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這件事本身雖然也應該作為非法入侵而追究責任
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.96,0:17:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但問題不在這裡 而是那裡面有什麼東西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.56,0:17:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能讓闖進去的人一個一個犧牲的什麼東西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.52,0:17:50.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裡面收藏著很久以前使用的拷問道具
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.77,0:17:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有這些
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.15,0:17:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 只有這些
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.45,0:17:58.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有藏著什麼必須要殺人滅口的驚天動地的東西嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.73,0:18:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 真的沒其他什麼了 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.96,0:18:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 有沒有什麼只有你沒看到的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.59,0:18:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.11,0:18:11.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道的是為什麼只有你沒事 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.11,0:18:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他三人却都遭遇不測
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.58,0:18:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這其中究竟有什麼區別 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.29,0:18:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一等 「只有你沒事」是指…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.61,0:18:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另外三個人是什麼意思 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.26,0:18:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鷹野小姐和富竹先生還有誰
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.51,0:18:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是鷹野小姐和富竹先生死亡以及園崎詩音小姐失蹤了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.76,0:18:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你一直沒事活到今天
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.78,0:18:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩…詩音失蹤?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.31,0:19:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是鷹野小姐和富竹先生死亡以及園崎詩音小姐失蹤了嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.28,0:19:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.76,0:19:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是小圭嗎 是我 詩音
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.32,0:19:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你聽說了嗎 梨花和沙都子的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.62,0:19:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之後怎麼樣了 找到了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.18,0:19:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒找到
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.44,0:19:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭 請不要傷心 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.66,0:19:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽筒對面的這傢伙 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.58,0:19:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,越是像極詩音也就越令人感到恐怖
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.67,0:19:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙不是詩音
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.52,0:19:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙究竟是誰
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.74,0:19:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼…什麼時候坦白的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.85,0:19:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.97,0:19:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村長先生患有痔瘡 一直上醫院就診的事你知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.82,0:20:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道他有痔瘡 看他坐的時候經常很痛苦 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.56,0:20:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼你知道他在哪個醫院…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.73,0:20:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 這不太清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.22,0:20:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是小圭 這又怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.71,0:20:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩音不知道醫院在哪 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.93,0:20:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話 就不可能跑去醫院向他坦白
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.15,0:20:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村長先生回來時因為電車事故導致時間緊張
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.27,0:20:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了趕上聚會應該沒時間聽詩音坦白 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.34,0:20:36.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩音是什麼時候向村長先生坦白的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.67,0:20:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭 為什麼要問這種事情
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.12,0:20:43.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要在大清早拖住村長先生是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.18,0:20:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩音也參加了聚會嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.99,0:20:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 這也不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.58,0:20:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為 園崎詩音
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.23,0:20:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早就在綿流祭的翌日失蹤了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.48,0:21:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了 如果我說錯了請告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.68,0:21:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩音 求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.80,0:21:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詩音 你根本就沒見到村長
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.34,0:21:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果見到他的話 就只能在村長結束聚會後
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.17,0:21:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到他失蹤之前 或者說 他失蹤之後了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.93,0:23:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無法終結的 後悔
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.50,0:23:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無法致歉的 故事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.09,0:23:27.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,銘刻在那的是另一個我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.40,0:23:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒蟬鳴泣之時 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.24,0:23:34.70,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,0)}{\fn方正大标宋_GBK}綿{\r}\h\h\h\h篇    其之四  心{\fn方正大标宋_GBK}願
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.24,0:23:34.70,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,0)}{\pos(340,471)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\1c&Hff&\be1\b0\fs36}流
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.77,0:23:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 能相信嗎?


Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo & Staff↓
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.55,0:01:11.20,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(87,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord2}{\alpha&H20&}翻譯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.55,0:01:11.20,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(209,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord2}{\alpha&H20&}影
Dialogue: 1,0:01:08.55,0:01:11.20,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(87,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord0}翻譯
Dialogue: 1,0:01:08.55,0:01:11.20,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(209,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord0}影
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.90,0:01:30.05,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(185,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}時間
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.90,0:01:30.05,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(295,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}Klaus
Dialogue: 1,0:01:26.90,0:01:30.05,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(185,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}時間
Dialogue: 1,0:01:26.90,0:01:30.05,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(295,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}Klaus
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.62,0:01:33.57,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(534,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}特效
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.62,0:01:33.57,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(645,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}怕输囧
Dialogue: 1,0:01:30.62,0:01:33.57,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(534,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}特效
Dialogue: 1,0:01:30.62,0:01:33.57,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(645,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}怕输囧

Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.75,0:01:38.85,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(150,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}後 期
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.75,0:01:38.85,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(270,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp-2}{\alpha&H20&}ZilcH「力」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.75,0:01:38.85,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(150,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}後 期
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.75,0:01:38.85,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(270,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp-2}ZilcH「力」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.95,0:01:24.86,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\3c&H454041&}{\bord3}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2135be&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Dialogue: 2,0:01:17.95,0:01:24.86,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\bord1}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2826ef&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Dialogue: 3,0:01:17.95,0:01:24.86,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2826ef&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.12,0:01:39.71,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}振り{\1c&H0f2ff2&}向{\1c&Heaf2f1&}いたその後ろの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.41,0:01:44.45,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}正面{\1c&H0f2ff2&}だ{\1c&Heaf2f1&}ぁれ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.26,0:01:49.23,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}暗{\1c&H0f2ff2&}闇{\1c&Heaf2f1&}に爪を立てて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.28,0:01:53.03,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}夜を引き{\1c&H0f2ff2&}裂{\1c&Heaf2f1&}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.14,0:01:58.73,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}雨だれは{\1c&H0f2ff2&}血{\1c&Heaf2f1&}のしずくとなって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.88,0:02:02.40,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}頬をつたい{\1c&H0f2ff2&}落{\1c&Heaf2f1&}ちる
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.62,0:02:12.33,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}もうどこにも帰る{\1c&H0f2ff2&}場所{\1c&Heaf2f1&}が無いなら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.72,0:02:17.17,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}この指{\1c&H0f2ff2&}止{\1c&Heaf2f1&}まれ　私の指に
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.24,0:02:21.61,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}その指ごと連れて{\1c&H0f2ff2&}っ{\1c&Heaf2f1&}てあげる
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.84,0:02:26.28,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}ひぐらしが{\1c&H0f2ff2&}鳴{\1c&Heaf2f1&}く　開かずの{\1c&H0f2ff2&}森{\1c&Heaf2f1&}へ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.47,0:02:33.89,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}後{\1c&H0f2ff2&}戻{\1c&Heaf2f1&}りはもう出来ない
Dialogue: 10,0:01:36.12,0:01:39.71,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}回首望去 紧随身后
Dialogue: 10,0:01:40.41,0:01:44.45,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}正面 是谁?
Dialogue: 10,0:01:45.26,0:01:49.23,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}无尽黑暗 轻点脚尖
Dialogue: 10,0:01:49.28,0:01:53.03,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}黑夜撕裂
Dialogue: 10,0:01:53.14,0:01:58.73,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}雨水化为血滴
Dialogue: 10,0:01:58.88,0:02:02.40,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}从脸颊上流淌而下
Dialogue: 10,0:02:02.62,0:02:12.33,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,9000)}{\be1}既然哪里都已没有归所
Dialogue: 10,0:02:12.72,0:02:17.17,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}收回你的手指 抓住我的手指
Dialogue: 10,0:02:17.24,0:02:21.61,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}连你的手指一起带走
Dialogue: 10,0:02:21.84,0:02:26.28,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}蝉儿鸣叫 封闭之森
Dialogue: 10,0:02:26.47,0:02:33.89,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,6000)}{\be1}已经无法回头
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.12,0:01:39.71,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}回首望去 隐匿身后
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.41,0:01:44.45,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}血{\fn華康正顏楷體W7}髏{\r} 疾首
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.26,0:01:49.23,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}阴暗狂啸 举起双爪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.28,0:01:53.03,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}撕肝断肠
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.14,0:01:58.73,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}雨水化为血滴
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.88,0:02:02.40,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}蹂躏脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.62,0:02:12.33,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(9000,250)}{\be1}后悔撕破母胎失去容身之所
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.72,0:02:17.17,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}让我把你的手指都扭断吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.24,0:02:21.61,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}我会将你连骨头都啃碎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.84,0:02:26.28,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}寒蝉鸣泣 不归之森
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.47,0:02:33.89,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(6000,250)}{\be1}回头亦是绝路
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.10,0:22:09.01,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}To get my happiness I had done everything
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.30,0:22:16.11,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}But had done nothing to be blamed and accused of
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.32,0:22:23.09,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}The sound of footsteps became louder every day
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.16,0:22:29.96,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Then I noticed the fact there was no time
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.40,0:22:38.38,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}I was a believer in life to be myself always
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.45,0:22:44.96,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}And was asking whether I would be alive
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.55,0:22:52.49,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}give me a reason why not to adopt in this way
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.60,0:22:59.66,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Or judge me to be guilty to my incurable sins
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.77,0:23:06.57,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Tell me why or why not Complaining way too much
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.68,0:23:14.14,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Maybe I overlooked something fatal for me

