[Script Info]
; This is a Sub Station Alpha v4 script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
;
; Script created by cySub 1.4.0 Release Build 1203
;
Title: When_They_Cry #10
Original Script: HKG&X2
Script Type: V4.00+
ScriptType: V4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 864
PlayResY: 480
Timer: 100.000
WrapStyle: 0

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
;
;=== When_They_Cry 寒蟬鳴泣之時 DVDRip作品 ASS字幕外掛發佈訊息 ===
;字幕版本使用HKG字幕組&X2字幕組TV連載字幕
;其他團體請勿私自作為自己的作品發佈 謝謝
;參與製作人員
;翻譯&校對    影
;時間軸       JK & Klaus
;特傚         怕输
;DVDRip&後期  ZilcH「力」
;片源         TCT66
;
Style: Default,simhei,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H300000A0,&HF00000D0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title,FZXiaoBiaoSong-B05T,34,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H500000B0,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhushi,simhei,28,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H300000A0,&HF00000D0,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1.2,1,8,30,30,10,1
Style: logo,fzxingkai-s04t,35,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,5,10,10,20,1
Style: op_jap,mikachan-pb,28,&H20EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H80454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,15,1
Style: op_chi,经典繁颜体,26,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,8,1
Style: op_chi2,经典繁颜体,26,&H200F2FF2,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,8,10,10,8,1
Style: ed_jap,s2gmemo,30,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: warning,simhei,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,5,5,5,1
Style: staff,dfkai-sb,25,&H00EAF2F1,&H00000000,&H00131B14,&H00454041,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,1,10,10,20,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.01,0:00:30.01,title,,0000,0000,0000,,祟\h\h\h\h篇    其之二  {\fn方正大标宋_GBK}羈絆
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.01,0:00:30.01,title,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(339,471)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\1c&Hff&\be1\b0\fs36}殺
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.43,0:00:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子今天也沒來學校嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.52,0:00:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.30,0:00:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以感冒而言似乎時間長了些呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.00,0:00:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望能快一些好起來
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.09,0:00:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.40,0:00:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這時候的我根本無法想像
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.09,0:00:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正降臨到沙都子身上的事 
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.61,0:00:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及今後將要發生的所有事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.90,0:02:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是前原學長
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.80,0:02:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直日本第一
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.38,0:02:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別忘了我的這份恩情喲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.14,0:02:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 一輩子都不會忘的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.96,0:02:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還真是一群善於逢迎的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.06,0:02:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好 下午好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.83,0:02:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打擾你午休
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.37,0:02:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是從興宮警署來的大石
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.18,0:02:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是找職員辦公室的話 在那邊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.07,0:02:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是不是 不是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.20,0:02:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能替我叫北條沙都子小姐出來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.60,0:02:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,警察找沙都子有什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.91,0:02:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 也沒什麼大事 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.23,0:02:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不進行預約的話 就沒法見面嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.30,0:03:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩位同學 稍微佔用一下時間可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.02,0:03:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想請你們幫我叫北條沙都子同學出來
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.95,0:03:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北條同學今天在家休息
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.98,0:03:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家休息? 哎呀哎呀 運氣還真是不好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.62,0:03:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼能告訴我那邊的小哥叫什麼名字嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.32,0:03:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前原 圭一 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.14,0:03:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 難道你就是住在前原大宅裡的少爺 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.64,0:03:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說你父親是非常有名的藝術家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.49,0:03:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又…怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.86,0:03:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這片土地上 還是不要隨便樹敵比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.36,0:03:46.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否則的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.89,0:03:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为一些不经意的小事招來的怨恨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.52,0:03:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能會在你難以置信的地方引來報應
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.72,0:03:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此為止比較好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.89,0:04:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 這不是入江醫生嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.91,0:04:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正打算等一會去醫生那裡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.84,0:04:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您總是事務繁忙 都沒機會和你好好談談呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.32,0:04:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你最好準備好調查令
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.61,0:04:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為盤問和要求同行都是可以拒絕的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.56,0:04:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是名叫大石藏人的刑警
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.65,0:04:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大石
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.41,0:04:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明那麼痛 居然連一點痕跡都沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.89,0:04:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個男人對這種事情十分熟練
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.80,0:04:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙 說是找沙都子有事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.74,0:04:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.26,0:04:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是個纏人的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.24,0:04:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他經常去沙都子那裡嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.19,0:05:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關於御社神大人作祟與沙都子的事 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.46,0:05:03.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前原同學聽說過一些吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.05,0:05:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 沙都子的父母是大壩計劃的贊成派 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.67,0:05:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會因為墜落事故而死是御社神作祟的那件事?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.12,0:05:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父母雙亡之後 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.42,0:05:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子與她哥哥悟史 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.26,0:05:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寄住到了叔父叔母的家裡
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.78,0:05:24.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.63,0:05:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔父雖然是沙都子的父親的弟弟…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.15,0:05:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次聽說呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.82,0:05:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是 那之後的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.25,0:05:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說對沙都子兄妹來說是十分痛苦的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.69,0:05:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛苦的生活是指?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.83,0:05:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虐待
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.93,0:05:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 究竟是幸運還是不幸
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.62,0:05:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的叔母卻在去年祭典的晚上 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.31,0:05:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被興奮劑的慣用者活活打死
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.88,0:05:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這一突然死亡是否也非單純的殺人事件
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.74,0:05:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是御社神大人作祟呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.84,0:06:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣在村裡傳開了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.64,0:06:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叔父也害怕御社神大人作祟
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.44,0:06:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就躲了起來
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.11,0:06:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說 他住到了興宮的情婦家裡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.60,0:06:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後 沙都子就得到解放了?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.90,0:06:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.81,0:06:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 就像是繼承她叔父一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.20,0:06:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個男人就出現了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.44,0:06:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個男人?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.25,0:06:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大石啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.33,0:06:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 為什麼他要纏著沙都子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.37,0:06:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說了一些讓人在意的流言
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.57,0:06:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流言?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.61,0:06:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 似乎回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.16,0:06:50.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回來 什麼回來了?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.73,0:06:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北條大叔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.00,0:06:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他回來和沙都子缺席有什麼關係嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.63,0:07:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這我就不清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.50,0:07:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不清楚算什麼意思
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.79,0:07:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 對不起 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.19,0:07:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.58,0:07:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.52,0:07:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這間屋子…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.37,0:07:27.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,監督
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.49,0:07:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前原君 真沒想到會在這裡遇到你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.79,0:07:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.84,0:07:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,買東西回來的路上偶然遇到了監督
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.70,0:07:43.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說是要送我回來 就接受了他的好意
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.94,0:07:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自行車可運不了這麼多東西
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.57,0:07:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子 這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.16,0:08:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子 燙酒的煤氣都沒關你怎麼就跑出去了 廢物
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.18,0:08:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 因為你叫我趕快去買
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.88,0:08:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢貨
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.84,0:08:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 這不是入江醫生嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.41,0:08:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶然遇到了沙都子所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.64,0:08:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.24,0:08:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 阿鐵 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.14,0:08:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幹嘛啊 阿椿 你又聽牌了?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.26,0:08:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叔父的朋友從城裡來玩 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.50,0:08:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在打麻將
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.52,0:08:39.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這算什麼 自己只顧著玩
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.71,0:08:41.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓沙都子去買這麼多東西嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.90,0:08:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傷痕 這是怎麼回事 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.52,0:08:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個混蛋 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.38,0:08:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白你的心情 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.25,0:08:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是現在需要忍耐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.90,0:09:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你了 圭一 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.55,0:09:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.73,0:09:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才的圭一就像是真的兄兄一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.84,0:09:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真正的兄兄雖然不見了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.71,0:09:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是現在有圭一這個兄兄
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.76,0:09:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我絕對不會逃走的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.75,0:09:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子 快拿點下酒的零食來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.92,0:09:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悟史究竟去了哪裡
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.82,0:09:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能說是離家出走了 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.27,0:09:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然離家出走 為什麼不帶沙都子一起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.02,0:09:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被扔下的沙都子也抱有相同的疑问吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.07,0:10:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為自己是哥哥的包袱所以被扔下了

Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.24,0:10:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會這樣…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.51,0:10:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然在兒童保護法裡 存在著為了保障兒童的安全
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.30,0:10:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為緊急措施 將其與父母分開的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.24,0:10:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但沙都子自己卻並不希望這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.72,0:10:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子她?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.11,0:10:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她認為忍受叔叔的折磨是對她的試煉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.50,0:10:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要不依靠任何人只靠自己克服試煉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.89,0:10:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不磨練出這樣的能力的話 悟史就不會回來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.55,0:10:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這麼說沙都子她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.71,0:10:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不承認被虐待
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.92,0:10:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.75,0:10:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然 兒童顧問處如果覺得虐待是公然的事實的話
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.24,0:10:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使沙都子否定 也能強制保護她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.15,0:10:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 這對沙都子而言就等於是輸了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.00,0:11:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,變堅強等悟史回來 才是沙都子活著的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.22,0:11:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我 真的覺得沙都子有危險
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.79,0:11:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會毫不猶豫的舉報
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.75,0:11:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使這一結果 會導致沙都子恨我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.18,0:11:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼你 要做到這種地步…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.12,0:11:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 你是雛見澤的人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.06,0:11:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.19,0:11:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能請你告訴我從這裡怎麼去古手神社嗎?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.95,0:12:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不介意一起的話 我可以帶你去
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.85,0:12:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫富竹 是個自由攝影師 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.28,0:12:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫前原
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.00,0:12:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 這不是前原君嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.26,0:12:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下午好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.85,0:12:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 你們認識嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.01,0:12:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.18,0:12:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還想不起我是誰嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.47,0:12:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鷹野三四小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.80,0:12:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在村裡的診療所工作的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.35,0:12:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不奇怪 只是在路上有幾次擦肩而過罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.14,0:12:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.53,0:12:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你似乎是個名人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.33,0:12:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟是前原大宅的少爺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.24,0:12:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們兩位是都有攝影愛好的搭檔嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.68,0:12:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算不上是搭檔啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.05,0:12:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是富竹先生指導我這個外行人罷了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.48,0:12:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後天就是綿流祭了吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.03,0:13:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打算要拍攝明天籌備祭典的情形
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.90,0:13:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是為了感謝御社神大人的祭典吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.80,0:13:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 是為了感謝御社神大人的祭典 
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.14,0:13:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村子的敵人就會受其作祟的御社神大人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.19,0:13:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果今年也有的話 究竟會是誰呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.47,0:13:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一系列的事件嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.54,0:13:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.82,0:13:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人真的會因為作祟什麼的而死嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.73,0:13:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 事件的確是發生了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.68,0:13:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是 有人仿照作祟的形式在殺人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.03,0:13:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鷹野小姐知道些什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.36,0:13:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴你也沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.29,0:13:54.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連圭一也缺席 我實在是很擔心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.60,0:14:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子聯絡說感冒還沒有康復
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.01,0:14:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為很可憐 所以大家正在商量要不要去看她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.26,0:14:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼呢 梨花 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.17,0:14:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都知道沙都子沒有感冒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.85,0:14:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別再說這種顯而易見的慌話了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.00,0:14:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你聽誰說的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.67,0:14:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天我去看過她了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.11,0:14:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不光是圭一 大家都很難過
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.50,0:14:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.03,0:14:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起立 敬礼 再見
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.10,0:14:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭 回去吧 你也沒興趣參加社團活動了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.73,0:14:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魅音 今天能去你家打擾一下嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.88,0:14:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想一口氣多借一些漫畫
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.17,0:14:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 好的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.57,0:15:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 有什麼事 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.06,0:15:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭有什麼話要說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.53,0:15:09.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.65,0:15:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是很認真的話題
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.03,0:15:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為事出突然 也許你會覺得疑惑 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.98,0:15:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我希望你聽我說
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.34,0:15:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼淵村御三家現在居於統率地位的一家的下一任家主
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.25,0:15:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,園崎魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.48,0:15:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你從哪聽說的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.81,0:15:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事情無所謂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.57,0:15:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來你好像知道些關於我的或有或無的事情嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.20,0:15:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼 你要對我說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.60,0:15:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御社神大人作祟一事 是有的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.15,0:15:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果今年作祟的對象不是沙都子的叔父的話
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.82,0:15:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼請換成沙都子的叔父
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.02,0:15:58.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說了 御社神大人作祟是…那個
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.90,0:16:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由園崎家主導 御三家所發起的全村所為的事件吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.38,0:16:11.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我並不是對魅音是否與此事有關什麼的感興趣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.00,0:16:17.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是 如果你能與決定作祟對象的人溝通的話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.84,0:16:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你告訴他們選沙都子的叔父
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.05,0:16:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜託你了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.52,0:16:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小圭你把我當成劊子手了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.24,0:16:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魅音是連續殺人事件的主犯也好 毫無關係也好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.80,0:16:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都無所謂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.81,0:16:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想幫沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.25,0:16:37.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以今年的作祟對象請把沙都子的叔父
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.73,0:16:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住口吧 我差不多該準備晚飯了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.16,0:16:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天你就先這樣回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.81,0:16:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.55,0:16:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很明白小圭的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.12,0:16:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我真像小圭說的一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.31,0:16:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,操縱著御三家 處於能夠選擇每年的犧牲者的立場的話
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.42,0:17:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定會實現小圭的願望的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.35,0:17:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魅音
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.48,0:17:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 現實並非如此
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.93,0:17:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是園崎魅音而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.52,0:17:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,園崎家的確是從各種意義上有許多不好的傳言的一族
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.82,0:17:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是像殺人這樣大逆不道的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.00,0:17:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是絕對不會做的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.64,0:17:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.23,0:17:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子的鞋子在呢 呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.93,0:17:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的哎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.13,0:17:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是來學校的話還是不清楚到底情況如何吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.54,0:17:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.78,0:17:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.95,0:17:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 大清早就吵吵鬧鬧的  
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.25,0:17:46.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.48,0:17:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保護司
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.85,0:17:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是誰打電話叫來的 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.29,0:17:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 搞出一場大騷動
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.06,0:17:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保護司 來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.37,0:17:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然衝到我家裡來 
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.06,0:18:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我和叔父都添了很大的麻煩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.97,0:18:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.40,0:18:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叔父怎麼樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.39,0:18:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承認當中有一些誤會 我們兩個都道歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.60,0:18:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.16,0:18:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 梨花
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.46,0:18:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子對保護司說什麼事都沒有把他趕走了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.95,0:18:20.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是誰叫來的 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.90,0:18:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知惠老師
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.67,0:18:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她知道這件事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.40,0:18:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別看她那樣子 也是班主任嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.22,0:18:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己把他趕回去了嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.41,0:18:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.43,0:18:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 無論沙都子如何否定 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.58,0:18:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虐待也是事實吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.79,0:18:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這已經是第三次了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.59,0:18:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子關於虐待兒童的舉報
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.73,0:18:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過去也有過兩次
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.96,0:18:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過去?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.85,0:18:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.43,0:18:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經死去的父親還在世的時候也是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.05,0:19:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經死去的父親也不是沙都子的親生父親
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.84,0:19:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子的母親再婚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.28,0:19:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子和悟史是她媽媽的帶入新家庭的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.03,0:19:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和父親並沒有血緣關係
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.71,0:19:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子在寄住在叔父叔母那裡之前  
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.26,0:19:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與家人的關係也不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.72,0:19:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子以陷害養父為目的 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.97,0:19:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,編造了受虐待的謊言 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.39,0:19:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己播打了虐待SOS電話
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.72,0:19:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這事被保護司知道了 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.16,0:19:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以這次也被當作是謊言嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.86,0:19:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就不清楚了 至少沒有採取緊急保護
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.80,0:19:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這算什麼意思
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.28,0:19:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是說因為沙都子可能說謊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.40,0:19:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以暫時先觀望嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.94,0:19:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.34,0:19:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.69,0:20:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 吃午飯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.88,0:20:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喵
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.30,0:20:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看啊看啊 今天是蛋包飯哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.44,0:20:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是礼奈
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.80,0:20:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的水平隨時去當新娘都不奇怪呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.46,0:20:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,礼奈當新娘?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.01,0:20:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.71,0:20:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄兄  
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.16,0:20:42.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子  
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.67,0:20:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 怎麼了 
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.30,0:21:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.45,0:21:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.79,0:21:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子 沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.41,0:21:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.93,0:21:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子 你怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.50,0:21:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 不要 我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.40,0:21:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 不要 不要
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.98,0:21:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.97,0:21:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.68,0:21:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 對不起 對不起 對不起 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.19,0:21:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 對不起 對不起 對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.05,0:21:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 對不起 對不起 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.28,0:21:42.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沙都子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.24,0:23:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所尋求的 是往昔所擁有的安睡
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.37,0:23:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所聽到的 是充斥著惡意的雨聲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.65,0:23:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所流入的 是通向黑暗的門扉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.87,0:23:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寒蟬鳴泣之時 
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.25,0:23:34.80,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,0)}祟\h\h\h\h篇    其之三  分界
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.25,0:23:34.80,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,0)}{\pos(340,471)\fn方正大标宋_GBK\1c&Hff&\be1\b0\fs36}殺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.26,0:23:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 能相信嗎?
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Logo & Staff↓
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.59,0:00:37.24,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(87,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord2}{\alpha&H20&}翻譯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.59,0:00:37.24,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(209,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord2}{\alpha&H20&}影
Dialogue: 1,0:00:34.59,0:00:37.24,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(87,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord0}翻譯
Dialogue: 1,0:00:34.59,0:00:37.24,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(209,230)}{\fad(0,0)}{\be1}{\fsp12}{\bord0}影
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.94,0:00:56.09,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(185,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}時間
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.94,0:00:56.09,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(295,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}Klaus
Dialogue: 1,0:00:52.94,0:00:56.09,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(185,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}時間
Dialogue: 1,0:00:52.94,0:00:56.09,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(295,185)}{\fad(0,250)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}Klaus
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:00:59.61,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(534,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}特效
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.66,0:00:59.61,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(645,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}怕输囧
Dialogue: 1,0:00:56.66,0:00:59.61,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(534,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}特效
Dialogue: 1,0:00:56.66,0:00:59.61,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs29}{\pos(645,433)}{\fad(250,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}怕输囧

Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.79,0:01:04.89,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(150,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp0}{\alpha&H20&}後 期
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.79,0:01:04.89,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(270,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord2}{\fsp-2}{\alpha&H20&}ZilcH「力」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.79,0:01:04.89,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(150,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp0}後 期
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.79,0:01:04.89,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs28}{\pos(270,293)}{\fad(0,400)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fsp-2}ZilcH「力」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.99,0:00:50.90,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\3c&H454041&}{\bord3}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2135be&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Dialogue: 2,0:00:43.99,0:00:50.90,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\bord1}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2826ef&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Dialogue: 3,0:00:43.99,0:00:50.90,logo,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,0)}{\be1}{\bord0}{\fscx120\fscy120)}{\pos(432,320)}ＨＫＧ{\1c&H2826ef&}＆{\1c&Heaf2f1&}Ｘ２字幕组联合制作
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓OP↓
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.18,0:01:05.77,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}振り{\1c&H0f2ff2&}向{\1c&Heaf2f1&}いたその後ろの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.47,0:01:10.51,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}正面{\1c&H0f2ff2&}だ{\1c&Heaf2f1&}ぁれ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.32,0:01:15.29,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}暗{\1c&H0f2ff2&}闇{\1c&Heaf2f1&}に爪を立てて
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.34,0:01:19.09,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}夜を引き{\1c&H0f2ff2&}裂{\1c&Heaf2f1&}いた
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.20,0:01:24.79,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}雨だれは{\1c&H0f2ff2&}血{\1c&Heaf2f1&}のしずくとなって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.94,0:01:28.46,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}頬をつたい{\1c&H0f2ff2&}落{\1c&Heaf2f1&}ちる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.68,0:01:38.39,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}もうどこにも帰る{\1c&H0f2ff2&}場所{\1c&Heaf2f1&}が無いなら
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.78,0:01:43.23,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}この指{\1c&H0f2ff2&}止{\1c&Heaf2f1&}まれ　私の指に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.30,0:01:47.67,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}その指ごと連れて{\1c&H0f2ff2&}っ{\1c&Heaf2f1&}てあげる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.90,0:01:52.34,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}ひぐらしが{\1c&H0f2ff2&}鳴{\1c&Heaf2f1&}く　開かずの{\1c&H0f2ff2&}森{\1c&Heaf2f1&}へ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.53,0:01:59.95,op_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,250)}{\be1}後{\1c&H0f2ff2&}戻{\1c&Heaf2f1&}りはもう出来ない
Dialogue: 10,0:01:02.18,0:01:05.77,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}回首望去 紧随身后
Dialogue: 10,0:01:06.47,0:01:10.51,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}正面 是谁?
Dialogue: 10,0:01:11.32,0:01:15.29,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}无尽黑暗 轻点脚尖
Dialogue: 10,0:01:15.34,0:01:19.09,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}黑夜撕裂
Dialogue: 10,0:01:19.20,0:01:24.79,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}雨水化为血滴
Dialogue: 10,0:01:24.94,0:01:28.46,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}从脸颊上流淌而下
Dialogue: 10,0:01:28.68,0:01:38.39,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,9000)}{\be1}既然哪里都已没有归所
Dialogue: 10,0:01:38.78,0:01:43.23,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}收回你的手指 抓住我的手指
Dialogue: 10,0:01:43.30,0:01:47.67,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}连你的手指一起带走
Dialogue: 10,0:01:47.90,0:01:52.34,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,4000)}{\be1}蝉儿鸣叫 封闭之森
Dialogue: 10,0:01:52.53,0:01:59.95,op_chi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(250,6000)}{\be1}已经无法回头
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.18,0:01:05.77,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}回首望去 隐匿身后
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.47,0:01:10.51,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}血{\fn華康正顏楷體W7}髏{\r} 疾首
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.32,0:01:15.29,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}阴暗狂啸 举起双爪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.34,0:01:19.09,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}撕肝断肠
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.20,0:01:24.79,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}雨水化为血滴
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.94,0:01:28.46,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}蹂躏脸庞
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.68,0:01:38.39,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(9000,250)}{\be1}后悔撕破母胎失去容身之所
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.78,0:01:43.23,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}让我把你的手指都扭断吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.30,0:01:47.67,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}我会将你连骨头都啃碎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.90,0:01:52.34,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(4000,250)}{\be1}寒蝉鸣泣 不归之森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.53,0:01:59.95,op_chi2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(6000,250)}{\be1}回头亦是绝路
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓Special Effect↓
Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,↓ED↓
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.26,0:22:09.17,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}To get my happiness I had done everything
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.46,0:22:16.27,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}But had done nothing to be blamed and accused of
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.48,0:22:23.25,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}The sound of footsteps became louder every day
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.32,0:22:30.12,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Then I noticed the fact there was no time
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.56,0:22:38.54,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}I was a believer in life to be myself always
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.61,0:22:45.12,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}And was asking whether I would be alive
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.71,0:22:52.65,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}give me a reason why not to adopt in this way
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.76,0:22:59.82,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Or judge me to be guilty to my incurable sins
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.93,0:23:06.73,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Tell me why or why not Complaining way too much
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.84,0:23:14.30,ed_jap,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(150,250)}{\be1}Maybe I overlooked something fatal for me

