[Script Info]

Title:K-ON
Original Script:华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H0027415C,&H9027415C,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,13,1
Style: Default_JP,DFGMaruGothic-Md,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H0027415C,&H9027415C,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,35,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小律的「拍到了哦」系列
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.00,0:00:09.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其一  澪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.11,0:00:10.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪  笑一个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.94,0:00:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.04,0:00:17.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次回过头来笑一个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.79,0:00:18.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.75,0:00:21.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了啦  这是夏天的回忆～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.64,0:00:22.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.37,0:00:27.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  稍微弯下腰  紧簇胸部
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.35,0:00:28.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.80,0:00:31.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我一生…一生的愿望…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.68,0:00:36.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.52,0:00:40.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  把这些卖掉赚取社团费用
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.47,0:00:41.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算卖啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.78,0:00:45.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会删掉的…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.02,0:00:54.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小律的「拍到了哦」系列
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.02,0:00:58.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其二  唯··澪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.09,0:01:00.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乐呵呵～
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.28,0:01:02.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.32,0:01:06.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和检查身体的时候没什么区别嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.91,0:01:28.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作假！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.85,0:01:32.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊！啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.94,0:01:35.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种地方不要拍！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.65,0:01:38.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会删掉的…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.08,0:01:47.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小律的「拍到了哦」系列
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.08,0:01:51.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其三  唯
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.84,0:01:54.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  晒得很黑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.78,0:01:56.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  茄子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.33,0:01:56.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.28,0:01:58.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Peace  Peace
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.00,0:02:06.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  茄子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.25,0:02:08.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,气死～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.81,0:02:12.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.02,0:02:14.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Peace  Peace
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.32,0:02:18.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你倒是害羞点啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.62,0:02:29.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完


Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.11,0:00:10.67,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,み～お  笑って～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.94,0:00:11.91,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,え～ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.04,0:00:17.41,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はいッ  今度は振り向いて  にこッ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.79,0:00:18.62,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,え～ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.75,0:00:21.06,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お願い  夏の思い出に～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.64,0:00:22.59,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ん～…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.37,0:00:27.08,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はいッ  ちゃっとかがんで～  胸をムギュッ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.35,0:00:28.31,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,え～ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.80,0:00:31.63,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一生の…一生のお願い  うう～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.68,0:00:36.36,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ん～…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.52,0:00:40.23,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よ～しッ  これを売って部費がせぐぞ～！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.47,0:00:41.49,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,売るんかいッ！
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.78,0:00:45.13,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消去します…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.09,0:01:00.24,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほいほい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.28,0:01:02.60,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よいしょッ  と～
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.32,0:01:06.12,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身体測定の時と  変わんないや～
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.91,0:01:28.79,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偽装だーッ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.85,0:01:32.57,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はぁッ！  はぁ～ッ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.94,0:01:35.18,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなこと  とるなッ！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.65,0:01:38.25,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消去します…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.84,0:01:54.55,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ！  結構  焼けてる～
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.78,0:01:56.08,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はいッ  チーズ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.33,0:01:56.92,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.28,0:01:58.59,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ピース  ピースゥ～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.00,0:02:06.54,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はいッ  チーズ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.25,0:02:08.45,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちぃ～ず
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.81,0:02:12.58,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あ？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.02,0:02:14.63,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ピース  ピースゥ～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.32,0:02:18.92,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちっよは  恥じらえ～