[Script Info]

Title:K-ON
Original Script:华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,52,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H0027415C,&H9027415C,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,13,1
Style: Default_JP,DFGMaruGothic-Md,28,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H0027415C,&H9027415C,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,35,1
Style: reference,方正准圆_GBK,38,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H0027415C,&H9027415C,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,15,15,12,1
Style: OPJ,MS Gothic,35,&H00FEFEFE,&H0000FFFF,&H11222222,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,85,85,11,1
Style: OPC,方正黑体_GBK,39,&H00FEFEFE,&H0000FFFF,&H11222222,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,76,76,8,1
Style: EDJ,MS Gothic,35,&H00FEFEFE,&H0000FFFF,&H11222222,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,85,85,11,1
Style: EDC,方正黑体_GBK,39,&H00FEFEFE,&H0000FFFF,&H11222222,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,76,76,8,1
Style: EDJ1,MS Gothic,35,&H00010101,&H0000FFFF,&H11EEEEEE,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,85,85,11,1
Style: EDC1,方正黑体_GBK,39,&H00010101,&H0000FFFF,&H11EEEEEE,&H11222222,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,76,76,8,1
Style: title,方正卡通简体,42,&H00000000,&H0000FFFF,&H0027415C,&H9027415C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,280,1
Style: title1,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,5,2,21,30,200,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.86,0:00:13.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好  我是平泽忧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.53,0:00:17.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是我和小梓第一次一起出门
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.41,0:00:20.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.03,0:00:22.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  小梓
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.80,0:00:25.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.27,0:00:29.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衣服好可爱啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.31,0:00:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  这次轻音部也要去合宿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.89,0:00:37.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  去四天三夜
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:41.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年呢  姐姐说非常开心哦
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.00,0:00:43.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开心？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.53,0:00:48.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  那是指练习得很充实吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.84,0:00:50.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？嗯…嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.13,0:00:52.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.98,0:00:54.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  忧～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.35,0:00:56.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可爱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.34,0:00:58.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.65,0:01:01.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家可是奏出那么动听音乐的前辈呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.65,0:01:04.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合宿这种程度的事…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.17,0:01:07.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.26,0:02:45.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐在轻音部里是怎样的呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.10,0:02:47.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.84,0:02:49.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微有点那个啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.16,0:02:49.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.38,0:02:54.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不练习  还取奇怪的外号
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.32,0:02:57.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动不动就在我身上蹭来蹭去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.50,0:02:58.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,70)\fs38}梓喵  好软好软～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.20,0:03:00.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐她很暖很舒服吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.12,0:03:03.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是那个意思…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.53,0:03:04.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.86,0:03:07.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天唯前辈在干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.33,0:03:08.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里蹲着呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.58,0:03:12.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐很怕热  但又讨厌空调
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.58,0:03:12.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,70)\fs38}啊～  好热好热～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.02,0:03:15.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能看见她懒塌塌的样子了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.52,0:03:18.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近每天都是精疲力尽的样子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.59,0:03:20.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不像样子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.55,0:03:24.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  滚来滚去的姐姐好可爱哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.56,0:03:26.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忧～  忧～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.67,0:03:28.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.73,0:03:31.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和忧这感觉的差别
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.66,0:03:36.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比较希望有个像澪前辈这样的姐姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.50,0:03:39.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪学姐又温柔又帅气哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.37,0:03:41.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律学姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.61,0:03:43.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.47,0:03:46.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人马马虎虎且粗枝大叶的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.03,0:03:48.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忽略掉…吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.56,0:03:49.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.64,0:03:51.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说谁粗枝大叶啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.31,0:03:53.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.15,0:03:58.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,70)\fs38}对不起…对不起…对不起…对不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.90,0:03:55.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律学姐好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.33,0:03:56.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀呵～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.34,0:03:58.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在外面看见你们就进来了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.50,0:04:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就一个人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.37,0:04:02.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  澪参加暑期讲学去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.41,0:04:05.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律前辈你不去也行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.06,0:04:09.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  我么？ 暑期讲学？为啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.80,0:04:12.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.12,0:04:16.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  说起来有件事我一直很在意
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.50,0:04:17.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.52,0:04:22.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈又是自己带茶具  又有别墅
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.50,0:04:24.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个很有钱的大小姐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.64,0:04:27.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对哦  她家里还有管家
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.65,0:04:30.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放长假经常去外国的哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.87,0:04:31.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗？！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.15,0:04:33.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样就很有趣了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.36,0:04:36.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瞎说的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.96,0:04:40.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  现在打个电话找去家里玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.31,0:04:42.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗  这么突然…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.72,0:04:49.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  不接电话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.09,0:04:51.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打她家里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.25,0:04:58.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.36,0:05:00.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打通了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.60,0:05:02.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  请问是同学的父亲吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.26,0:05:06.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是琴吹家的管家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.97,0:05:08.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有管家啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.66,0:05:12.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那个  同学在家吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.37,0:05:13.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈  冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.09,0:05:18.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大小姐现在正在芬兰避暑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.10,0:05:21.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.58,0:05:22.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我先挂了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.94,0:05:27.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  我说得没错吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.54,0:05:28.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.26,0:05:32.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…感觉好累啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.70,0:05:35.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要来我家转一圈吗  有西瓜哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.68,0:05:36.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.41,0:05:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.06,0:05:39.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.30,0:05:41.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西瓜…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.20,0:05:43.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律学姐和小梓来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.40,0:05:47.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢～迎～回～来～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.83,0:05:52.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一看她我真放心啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.92,0:05:54.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人如其闻啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.71,0:05:55.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,70)\fs38}哈～  好可爱～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.81,0:05:58.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰了～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.73,0:06:00.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  她在她在
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.95,0:06:04.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是暑假  但真够辛苦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.16,0:06:07.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,研修什么的都撞在一起了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.07,0:06:09.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们也要练习吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.80,0:06:10.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.65,0:06:11.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.75,0:06:13.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轻音部要搞合宿
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.23,0:06:16.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想问问老师你要不要来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.90,0:06:18.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合宿啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.64,0:06:21.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔哈哈…一副麻烦死了的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.39,0:06:24.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算了  我们自己去好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.67,0:06:26.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不跟你打招呼就生气
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.44,0:06:27.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你说了又这副样子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.08,0:06:30.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又能游泳又能烧烤呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.03,0:06:33.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  真是好期待啊  合宿
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.21,0:06:38.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好～
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.08,0:06:41.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好久没聚在一起了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.51,0:06:43.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起去为合宿购物吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.88,0:06:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来  要买点什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.34,0:06:49.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新的器材吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.25,0:06:51.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.92,0:06:52.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳装哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.84,0:06:53.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩心十足啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.24,0:06:56.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我想也是这么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.92,0:06:58.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是一直都玩嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.13,0:07:00.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁上你的当啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.64,0:07:01.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.36,0:07:03.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  休息也是必要的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.01,0:07:04.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.85,0:07:08.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗…也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.82,0:07:12.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这份孤独感是什么呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.46,0:07:16.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦哦哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.52,0:07:18.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这又强大了一级啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.91,0:07:22.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是去年说的没借到的别墅吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.51,0:07:23.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.61,0:07:26.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个别墅今年也不行
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.72,0:07:29.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多少有点挤  请大家忍耐下
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.84,0:07:31.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有更大的啊！？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.33,0:07:34.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  去玩喽！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.78,0:07:36.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦～！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.39,0:07:38.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂—！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.29,0:07:40.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我练完再去玩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.40,0:07:41.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.31,0:07:42.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家想玩！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.08,0:07:44.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么投票决定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.20,0:07:46.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要先练习
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.76,0:07:47.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.74,0:07:48.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,练习比较好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.05,0:07:52.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想玩～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.81,0:07:54.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意料之外的背叛！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.72,0:07:55.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.95,0:07:56.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.10,0:08:00.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,70)\fs38}真是的  把玩也算进前期事项的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.83,0:08:01.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  前辈的玩难道是…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.24,0:08:05.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,I am flying！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.81,0:08:07.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Yes，Yes Yes！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.58,0:08:10.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.11,0:08:18.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过不要的嘛！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.51,0:08:20.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把海滨的东西收拾掉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.10,0:08:22.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游艇也不要！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.59,0:08:23.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.36,0:08:24.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.23,0:08:26.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看招～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.71,0:08:28.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈哈哈～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.29,0:08:31.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.39,0:08:33.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈哈哈…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.59,0:08:35.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿咻  嘿咻～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.11,0:08:38.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能好好练习吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.74,0:08:39.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梓喵～
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.82,0:08:43.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梓喵也来一起玩吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.10,0:08:44.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.87,0:08:47.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道说你不擅长运动？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.19,0:08:50.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没…没有这回事！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.67,0:08:51.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩给你看！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.25,0:09:02.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小梓已经和大家相处得很好了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.79,0:09:03.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.13,0:09:08.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小律博士  请看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.97,0:09:09.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪前辈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.07,0:09:10.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.56,0:09:14.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道藤壶的故事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.26,0:09:18.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前有位因藤壶而划破腿的少年…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.05,0:09:20.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊…那个…澪前…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.36,0:09:23.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…辈？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.35,0:09:27.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没到没到还在前面哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.97,0:09:28.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.61,0:09:29.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上啊上啊～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.41,0:09:31.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.48,0:09:36.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我来一口
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.46,0:09:37.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.39,0:09:39.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.22,0:09:43.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈哈哈哈  我这个人啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.96,0:09:58.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.03,0:10:01.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无人岛…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.11,0:10:07.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小律
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.03,0:10:11.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.64,0:10:17.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯…唯！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.94,0:10:19.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小律
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.24,0:10:23.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于到了…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.75,0:10:25.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新大陆啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.30,0:10:27.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Zipangu！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.47,0:10:29.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黄金之岛～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.77,0:10:28.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,70)\fs38}你们在干什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.21,0:10:31.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.52,0:10:32.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩爽了玩爽了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.33,0:10:35.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多吃个饭洗洗睡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.84,0:10:37.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,练习怎么办呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.51,0:10:41.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然应该不玩先练习才对
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.12,0:10:44.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梓才是玩得最欢的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.40,0:10:45.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都晒黑了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.31,0:10:48.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是会好好练习的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.51,0:10:49.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  练一整晚？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.69,0:10:52.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,练就练！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.20,0:10:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,K-ON!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.27,0:11:02.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,累死了～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.74,0:11:04.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饿死了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.26,0:11:05.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍忍吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.97,0:11:09.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.76,0:11:14.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确了不得
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.45,0:11:16.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还从没用过那样的扩音器
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.95,0:11:18.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪！快来练习吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.15,0:11:20.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这鼓竟然是全新的！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.71,0:11:21.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万恶的拜金主义者
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.11,0:11:26.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梓喵  那个是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.20,0:11:29.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  这个吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.44,0:11:30.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是个调音器
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.30,0:11:33.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎  这个叫调音器啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.44,0:11:33.96,reference,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（调音器（tuner）：校正音高或给予标准音高的工具）
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.21,0:11:36.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是用这个来调音的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.69,0:11:39.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯前辈你不知道调音器的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.71,0:11:41.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  头一次见
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.94,0:11:43.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你以前都是怎么调音的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.88,0:11:47.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,适当的…你看
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.22,0:11:50.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝…绝对音感！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.07,0:11:53.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不知道这个人是废柴还是强人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.19,0:11:56.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们来吧！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.87,0:11:58.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,one two three four
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.88,0:12:08.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才这曲感觉很好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.53,0:12:10.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很合拍呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.62,0:12:11.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,70)\fs38}太棒了  小唯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.22,0:12:13.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都是什么时候练习的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.60,0:12:13.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,70)\fs38}没啦没啦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.18,0:12:16.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律你的鼓点打得挺准的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.97,0:12:18.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己特训过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.60,0:12:24.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饿死我了…没劲儿了…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.42,0:12:27.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为肚子饿所以没有多余的力气乱敲了吗…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.65,0:12:30.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吃饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.01,0:12:33.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我吃饭～！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.06,0:12:35.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.44,0:12:37.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来啦～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.21,0:12:39.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.63,0:12:40.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.77,0:12:43.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小律！有肉有菜哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.18,0:12:45.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等好久啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.06,0:12:50.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圆圆的卷心菜！看我一口生吞下去！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.20,0:12:51.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我忍忍
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.61,0:12:54.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成天看她们在玩
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.28,0:12:56.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,70)\fs38}忍无可忍！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.84,0:12:57.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但演奏的时候为什么就那么顺畅呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.69,0:12:59.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松手！卷心菜之…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.06,0:13:02.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家分工合作马上就能做好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.50,0:13:03.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,70)\fs38}卷心菜之神要生气了！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.51,0:13:05.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我去看看炉火
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.53,0:13:09.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  学妹都率先表态了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.42,0:13:11.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.07,0:13:17.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼睛好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.62,0:13:19.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯  没事吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.09,0:13:21.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小律
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.75,0:13:22.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.57,0:13:24.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们死也要死在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.99,0:13:25.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.87,0:13:31.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那我们来做饭团吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.95,0:13:32.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.41,0:13:42.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差距竟然这么大…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.31,0:13:47.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是小澪的手太大了呀？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.74,0:13:48.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.57,0:14:08.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊～好好吃啊！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.32,0:14:10.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确很好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.78,0:14:12.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真赞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.51,0:14:14.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们来放烟花吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.47,0:14:30.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.83,0:14:33.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后要烧完的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.32,0:14:35.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心里总会念着让它再加把劲再加把劲这样吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.46,0:14:38.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加把劲～  再加把劲～
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.91,0:14:39.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.33,0:14:43.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  再来一根
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.74,0:14:46.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加把劲  再加把劲
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.64,0:14:52.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.05,0:14:55.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小律  要灭啦…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.91,0:14:58.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题！这种时候就要进行合体巨大化！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.90,0:15:02.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合体！ 线香花火人！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.38,0:15:03.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不带这样的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.16,0:15:05.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.79,0:15:06.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重不重？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.94,0:15:07.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.38,0:15:09.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来开试胆大会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.84,0:15:10.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.95,0:15:12.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没完没了了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.73,0:15:13.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.76,0:15:15.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说到夏天和合宿的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.69,0:15:16.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可以没有试胆大会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.07,0:15:18.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不参加
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.44,0:15:20.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对啦～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.41,0:15:22.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪怕鬼故事呢～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.50,0:15:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.16,0:15:26.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来就来谁怕你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.74,0:15:30.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前不让我好好吃饭的仇
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.66,0:15:31.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这回要让你一次还清
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.27,0:15:43.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都…都是高中生了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.47,0:15:45.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还搞什么试胆大会啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.08,0:15:48.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…我的手很疼…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.15,0:15:53.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那是什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.72,0:15:55.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一…一…一…一定…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.60,0:15:57.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是律…律…律在搞鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.04,0:16:10.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小澪…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.86,0:16:14.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,70)\fs38}好怕！  好可怕！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.67,0:16:14.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈！前辈！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.80,0:16:15.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请保持镇定！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.41,0:16:19.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老…老师？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.06,0:16:21.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.83,0:16:23.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终…终于见到你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.46,0:16:26.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？ 小佐和老师？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.65,0:16:27.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.79,0:16:29.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说来你怎么在这里？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.85,0:16:35.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本打算晚点和大家汇合  吓你们一跳的…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.03,0:16:37.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果迷路了…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.15,0:16:42.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我看吓人这个目的倒是达到了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.70,0:16:45.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小澪！没事了！小澪！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.93,0:16:49.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪前辈原来这么怕的啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.69,0:16:57.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么没人来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.12,0:17:03.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是吓死人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.81,0:17:04.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算啦算啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.67,0:17:05.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪～澪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.25,0:17:14.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梓  你怕热吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.66,0:17:16.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  倒也不是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.10,0:17:20.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梓喵  这时候最好要一口气沉下去啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.27,0:17:23.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.28,0:17:25.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被太阳晒的很疼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.58,0:17:28.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯你瘦了点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.93,0:17:31.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  以前也说过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.64,0:17:34.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管吃多少都长不胖的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.83,0:17:35.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羡慕死你了！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.15,0:17:38.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  连小佐和老师也？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.08,0:17:40.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.08,0:17:45.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一摘下眼镜就分不太清楚你们两个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.47,0:17:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用胸部大小来判断不就行了嘛～
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.34,0:17:53.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊哈★
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.41,0:18:07.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稠状的…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.11,0:18:10.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卷心菜真好吃～
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.05,0:18:33.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  让你来陪我练习
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.75,0:18:35.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请不用放在心上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.06,0:18:40.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也想和唯前辈在一起多多练习
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.98,0:18:42.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.79,0:18:43.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.39,0:19:01.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梓喵你好厉害哦～
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.20,0:19:03.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么了不得的啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.06,0:19:07.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那下来轮到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.11,0:19:16.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这块很难啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.80,0:19:19.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始先用慢速来弹就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.29,0:19:21.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.33,0:19:38.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弹出来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.76,0:19:41.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,认识梓喵太好啦！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.48,0:19:45.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梓喵～
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.84,0:19:49.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  梓喵
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.48,0:20:06.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好  我是平泽忧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.14,0:20:09.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也和小梓一起出门
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.29,0:20:11.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.66,0:20:16.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.83,0:20:18.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  好慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.72,0:20:19.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦…谁啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.14,0:20:25.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没能怎么练习吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.42,0:20:27.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是没有练…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.18,0:20:30.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想要再特训下的…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.22,0:20:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可却跑去游泳啊试胆大会啊什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.44,0:20:34.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几乎一直在玩
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.16,0:20:37.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是想多练习的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.43,0:20:39.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.88,0:20:42.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是姐姐完全没有晒黑啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.24,0:20:45.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么晒成这样呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.67,0:20:47.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这个…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.94,0:20:50.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我就是玩得最欢的那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.41,0:20:55.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.02,0:21:00.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是觉得能去合宿真的挺好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.16,0:21:05.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还了解了不少前辈她们的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.12,0:21:08.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  什么样的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.59,0:21:12.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯…澪前辈其实挺胆小的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.03,0:21:14.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.68,0:21:15.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律学姐呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.22,0:21:18.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然还是挺粗枝大叶的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.68,0:21:20.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过和澪前辈的感情挺不错的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.35,0:21:22.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学姐呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.89,0:21:24.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前辈啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.02,0:21:27.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管平时很照顾大家
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.63,0:21:29.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想不到也有很孩子气的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.80,0:21:30.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个很可爱的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.43,0:21:32.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯～
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.90,0:21:34.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我姐姐呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.26,0:21:37.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯前辈呢…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.08,0:21:41.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在好好练习了！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.11,0:21:43.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧～
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.88,0:21:54.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.52,0:22:02.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还是会冲上来抱着我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.71,0:22:04.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐暖暖的对不对
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.59,0:22:08.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿…算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.12,0:23:44.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唔…琴弦都生锈了嘛！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.48,0:23:47.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上次换弦是什么时候？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.27,0:23:50.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诶？弦能换的吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.23,0:23:52.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什…什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.95,0:23:55.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个…是经典吉他吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.60,0:23:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起…就是脏了点…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.58,0:24:00.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才刚买了一年
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.65,0:24:03.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她真就这么走掉的话
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.94,0:24:08.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学园祭的演出  要怎么办呢


Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.87,0:02:42.90,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2}#10　　又是合宿!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.17,0:24:09.70,title1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,0)}#11　　危机!


Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.64,0:01:16.04,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}Chatting Now
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.12,0:01:18.86,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}ガチでカシマシ　Never Ending Girls' Talk
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.99,0:01:21.69,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}終業チャイムまで待てない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.79,0:01:24.49,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}遅刻はしても早退はNon Non Non!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.64,0:01:28.96,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}精一杯Study After School
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.10,0:01:38.49,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}ドキドキが止まんない　フルスロットルな脳内
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.84,0:01:44.11,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}希望{\rOPC}·{\r}欲望{\rOPC}·{\r}煩悩　リボンかけて包装
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.42,0:01:49.60,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}ネタどっさり持ち寄り　New{\fscx50}　{\r}Type{\fscx50}　{\r}Version打ち込み
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.09,0:01:55.35,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}男子禁制のプリ帳　恋綴った日記帳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.59,0:02:01.11,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}スカート丈2cm　詰めたら跳ぶよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.44,0:02:07.22,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}昨日より遠く　おとといよりオクターブ高く
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.59,0:02:08.16,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}Jumping Now
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.24,0:02:11.07,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}ガチでウルワシ　Never Ending Girls' Life
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.21,0:02:13.87,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}日々マジ　ライブだし待ったなし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.95,0:02:16.75,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}早起きしても早寝はNon Non Non!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.92,0:02:19.67,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}目一杯Shouting　わっしょい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.75,0:02:22.33,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}ガチでスバラシ　Never Ending Girls' Song
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.54,0:02:25.20,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}午後ティータイムには持ってこい
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.29,0:02:28.04,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}片思いでも玉砕でHere we go!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.23,0:02:32.42,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}歌えばShining After School


Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.64,0:01:16.04,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}Chatting Now
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.12,0:01:18.86,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}总是吵闹　Never Ending Girls' Talk
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.99,0:01:21.69,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}直到下课铃响前都不会等待
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.79,0:01:24.49,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}迟到难免早退Non Non Non!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.64,0:01:28.96,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}竭尽全力Study After School
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.10,0:01:38.49,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}心跳不已　脑内堆满
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.84,0:01:44.11,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}希望·欲望·烦恼　用礼带包装起来
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.42,0:01:49.60,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}带来诸多NETA　贯注New Type Version
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.09,0:01:55.35,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}男子禁止的大头贴手册　汇集爱的日记本
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.59,0:02:01.11,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}裙子丈2cm　完成后就跳起来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.44,0:02:07.22,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}比昨日更远　比前日音阶更高
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.59,0:02:08.16,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}Jumping Now
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.24,0:02:11.07,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}总是尽兴　Never Ending Girls' Life
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.21,0:02:13.87,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}日日演奏　永不终结
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.95,0:02:16.75,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}早起难免早睡Non Non Non!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.92,0:02:19.67,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}放眼纵然Shouting　嘿哟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.75,0:02:22.33,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}绝佳绝佳　Never Ending Girls' Song
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.54,0:02:25.20,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}在下午茶时间带来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.29,0:02:28.04,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}单相思也要玉碎Here we go!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.23,0:02:32.42,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}歌唱吧　Shining After School


Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.74,0:22:14.10,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}Please don't say「You are lazy」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.33,0:22:16.73,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}だって本当はcrazy
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.98,0:22:22.02,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}白鳥たちはそう　見えないとこでバタ足するんです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.31,0:22:27.33,EDJ1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}本能に従順 忠実　翻弄も重々承知
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.64,0:22:32.81,EDJ1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}前途洋々だし…だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.77,0:22:43.53,EDJ1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}近道あればそれが王道　はしょれる翼もあれば上等
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.23,0:22:53.27,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}ヤバ 爪割れた　グルーで補修した
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.48,0:22:58.60,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}それだけでなんか達成感
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.78,0:23:03.90,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}大事なのは自分　かわいがること
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.07,0:23:09.88,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}自分を愛さなきゃ　他人も愛せない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.47,0:23:13.07,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}Please don't say「You are lazy」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.36,0:23:15.68,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}だって本当はcrazy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.95,0:23:21.04,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}能ある鷹はそう　見えないとこにピック隠すんです
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.26,0:23:26.34,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}想像に一生懸命　現実は絶体絶命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.63,0:23:32.06,EDJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}発展途中だし…だから不意にピッチ外れるんです


Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.74,0:22:14.10,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}Please don't say「You are lazy」
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.33,0:22:16.73,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}因为其实是crazy
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.98,0:22:22.02,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}白鸟们在暗处浅打水
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.31,0:22:27.33,EDC1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}忠实顺从本能　明知重重颠簸
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.64,0:22:32.81,EDC1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}前途光明…所以稍事休息吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.77,0:22:43.53,EDC1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}近道即王道　折翼更上等
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.23,0:22:53.27,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}利爪破裂　以胶修补
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.48,0:22:58.60,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}如此就有成就感
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.78,0:23:03.90,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}怜惜自己很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.07,0:23:09.88,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}不爱自己何谈爱他人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.47,0:23:13.07,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}Please don't say「You are lazy」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.36,0:23:15.68,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}因为其实是crazy
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.95,0:23:21.04,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}能乐者敛其锋芒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.26,0:23:26.34,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}拼命想象　现实却一筹莫展
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.63,0:23:32.06,EDC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\be1\fad(300,300)}还在发展途中…所以会意外地走音


Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.86,0:00:13.96,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんにちは 平沢憂です
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.53,0:00:17.77,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日は 梓ちゃんと初めてのお出かけです
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.41,0:00:20.17,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お～い
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.03,0:00:22.62,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ 梓ちゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.80,0:00:25.72,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめ～ん
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.27,0:00:29.64,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,服 カワイイ～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.31,0:00:34.50,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ 今度 軽音部で合宿行くんだよね
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.89,0:00:37.05,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん ３泊４日だって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.48,0:00:41.59,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去年はね お姉ちゃんがすっごく楽しかったって言ってたよ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.00,0:00:43.24,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,楽しかった？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.53,0:00:48.70,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ それって 練習が充実してたってことかなあ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.84,0:00:50.73,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えッ… うッ うん
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.13,0:00:52.54,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだと思う…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.98,0:00:54.57,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ 憂～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.35,0:00:56.95,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,カワイイでしょ～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.34,0:00:58.32,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そっか～
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.65,0:01:01.87,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,みなさん あんないい演奏する先輩だもんね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.65,0:01:04.41,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合宿ぐらいは…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.17,0:01:07.68,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丈夫かな…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.26,0:02:45.80,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お姉ちゃん 軽音部で どんな感じ？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.10,0:02:47.29,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うッ うん…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.84,0:02:49.03,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっと あれかな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.16,0:02:49.89,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何 何？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.38,0:02:54.87,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全然 練習しないし 変なあだ名つけてくるし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.32,0:02:57.55,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やたらスキンシップしてくるし
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.50,0:02:58.01,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,25)\fs20}あずにゃん～　ぷにぷに～
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.20,0:03:00.82,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お姉ちゃんて あったかくて 気持ちいいよね
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.12,0:03:03.31,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや そういう話じゃなくて
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.53,0:03:04.37,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほえ？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.86,0:03:07.07,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日 唯先輩は 何してるの？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.33,0:03:08.23,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家にいるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.58,0:03:12.74,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お姉ちゃん 暑いの苦手だから 冷房も嫌いだし
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.58,0:03:12.73,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,25)\fs20}ああ～  熱い熱い～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.02,0:03:15.15,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ダレてる姿が 目に浮かぶ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.52,0:03:18.03,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近は 一日中 ぐったりしてるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.59,0:03:20.28,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だらしないわねえ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.55,0:03:24.29,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも ゴロゴロしてるお姉ちゃん カワイイよ～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.56,0:03:26.72,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憂 憂～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.67,0:03:28.50,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だろう
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.73,0:03:31.03,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この私と 憂の感覚の違いは
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.66,0:03:36.22,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私 澪先輩みたいなお姉ちゃんだったら ほしいなあ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.50,0:03:39.16,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪さん 優しくて カッコイイもんね
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.37,0:03:41.43,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律さんは？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.61,0:03:43.16,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,う～ん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.47,0:03:46.81,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの人はいい加減で おおざっぱだから
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.03,0:03:48.44,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,パス… かな
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.56,0:03:49.38,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほ～お
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.64,0:03:51.21,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰が おおざっぱだって？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.31,0:03:53.02,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああーッ！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.15,0:03:58.11,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,25)\fs20}ごめんなさい…ごめんなさい…ごめんなさい…ごめんなさい…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.90,0:03:55.13,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんにちは 律さん
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.33,0:03:56.16,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ヤッホ～
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.34,0:03:58.07,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外から見えたから 来ちゃったあ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.50,0:04:00.00,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日は １人なんですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.37,0:04:02.88,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん 澪は夏期講習行ってるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.41,0:04:05.74,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律先輩は行かなくていいんですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.06,0:04:09.43,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えッ 私が？夏期講習 何で？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.80,0:04:12.17,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ですよねえ…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.12,0:04:16.14,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ ところで ずっと気になってたんですけど
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.50,0:04:17.10,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えッ？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.52,0:04:22.22,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ムギ先輩って 自前のティーセット持ってきたり 別荘持ってたり
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.50,0:04:24.26,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すごい お嬢様なんですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.64,0:04:27.43,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだぞ～ 家には 執事さんがいて
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.65,0:04:30.54,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,長期休暇には 外国行ったりしてるんだぞ～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.87,0:04:31.84,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当ですか！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.15,0:04:33.94,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だったら 面白いよね～
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.36,0:04:36.16,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知らないんじゃないですか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.96,0:04:40.15,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ 今から電話して ムギんち遊びに行こうぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.31,0:04:42.48,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいんですか？そんないきなり
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.72,0:04:49.44,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれ？ 携帯に出ないなあ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.09,0:04:51.81,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家電にかけてみるか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.25,0:04:58.65,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい もしもし
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.36,0:05:00.15,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,つながった
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.60,0:05:02.89,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ 紬さんのお父さんですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.26,0:05:06.82,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いえ 私 琴吹家の執事でございます
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.97,0:05:08.45,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当に執事 いたーッ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.66,0:05:12.22,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えッ ええと 紬さんはいらっしゃいますかしら？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.37,0:05:13.71,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先輩 落ち着いて
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.09,0:05:18.48,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紬お嬢様はただいま フィンランドで避暑中でございます
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.10,0:05:21.36,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうですか ありがとうございます
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.58,0:05:22.78,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼しました
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.94,0:05:27.31,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほらみろ 私の言ったとおりだろ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.54,0:05:28.97,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほお～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.26,0:05:32.48,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ～ 何か疲れた
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.70,0:05:35.42,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ウチ寄っていきます？スイカありますよ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.68,0:05:36.34,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行く！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.41,0:05:38.59,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ただいま～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.06,0:05:39.95,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お姉ちゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.30,0:05:41.12,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,スイカ…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.20,0:05:43.42,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律さんと梓ちゃんが来たよ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.40,0:05:47.51,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お～か～え～り～
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.83,0:05:52.61,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か ホッとするな
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.92,0:05:54.40,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聞いてたとおりだ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.71,0:05:55.17,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,25)\fs20}は～　あれ　かわいいですか
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.81,0:05:58.46,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失礼しま～す
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.73,0:06:00.33,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ いたいた
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.95,0:06:04.64,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏休みなのに 大変ですねえ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.16,0:06:07.54,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,研修とか いろいろあってねえ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.07,0:06:09.60,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あなた達も練習？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.80,0:06:10.37,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.65,0:06:11.47,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何か用？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.75,0:06:13.97,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,軽音部で合宿するんだけど
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.23,0:06:16.42,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生も 来るかなあと思って
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.90,0:06:18.51,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合宿ねえ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.64,0:06:21.01,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,う～はは…めんどくさそうな顔
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.39,0:06:24.44,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ いいよ 私達だけで行くから
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.67,0:06:26.36,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声かけなかったら怒るのに
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.44,0:06:27.92,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声かけたら これだ～
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.08,0:06:30.82,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泳いだり バーベキューしたり できるのにね
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.03,0:06:33.34,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わあ～楽しみだねえ 合宿
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.21,0:06:38.22,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おーし
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.08,0:06:41.37,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久しぶりに みんな そろったことだし
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.51,0:06:43.21,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合宿の買い物に 行くか！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.88,0:06:48.00,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ところで 何を買いに行くんですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.34,0:06:49.85,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新しい機材とか？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.25,0:06:51.82,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,え～と
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.92,0:06:52.66,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水着だよ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.84,0:06:53.86,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遊ぶ気 マンマン
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.24,0:06:56.59,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうせ こんなことだろうと思いました
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.92,0:06:58.96,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別に ずっと遊ぶわけじゃないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.13,0:07:00.47,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信用できないです！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.64,0:07:01.22,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何で!?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.36,0:07:03.55,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まあ 息抜きも必要だから
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.01,0:07:04.66,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なッ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.85,0:07:08.47,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そっか… そうですよね
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.82,0:07:12.85,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この寂しさは 何だろう
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.46,0:07:16.30,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おおーッ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.52,0:07:18.45,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こりゃまた一段と すげえな～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.91,0:07:22.20,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これが 去年言ってた 借りれなかった別荘だね？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.51,0:07:23.36,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめんなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.61,0:07:26.31,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その別荘は 今年もダメだったの
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.72,0:07:29.62,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多少狭いと思うけど ガマンしてね
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.84,0:07:31.67,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだ上があるのか!?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.33,0:07:34.59,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし あっそぶぞ～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.78,0:07:36.25,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オーッ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.39,0:07:38.06,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うお～～～い！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.29,0:07:40.07,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遊ぶのは練習してから！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.40,0:07:41.01,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,え～ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.31,0:07:42.59,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遊びた～い
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.08,0:07:44.91,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それじゃ 多数決にしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.20,0:07:46.58,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私は 練習が先
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.76,0:07:47.46,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遊ぶ！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.74,0:07:48.93,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,練習がいいです
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.05,0:07:52.64,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遊びたいで～す
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.81,0:07:54.27,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まさかの裏切り
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.72,0:07:55.78,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早く～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.95,0:07:56.66,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待てよ～
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.10,0:08:00.96,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,25)\fs20}まったく 遊ぶも前期のことなら…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.83,0:08:01.76,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも ムギ先輩の遊びって もしかして…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.24,0:08:05.73,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アイム フライング！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.81,0:08:07.68,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,イエース イエスイエス！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.58,0:08:10.67,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まさかね
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.11,0:08:18.15,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いらないって 言っておいたでしょ！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.51,0:08:20.88,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浜辺にあるものを すぐに片づけて
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.10,0:08:22.51,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お船もいらない！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.59,0:08:23.17,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ムギ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.36,0:08:24.12,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先輩
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.23,0:08:26.50,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そ～れッ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.71,0:08:28.01,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アハハハハ…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.29,0:08:31.26,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アハハハハ…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.39,0:08:33.30,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アハハハハ…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.59,0:08:35.78,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よいしょ よいしょ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.11,0:08:38.20,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちゃんと練習できるのかなあ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.74,0:08:39.72,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あずにゃ～ん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.82,0:08:43.86,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あずにゃんも 一緒に遊ぼうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.10,0:08:44.90,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結構です
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.87,0:08:47.96,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さては スポーツとか苦手な人？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.19,0:08:50.47,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう そんなことありません！
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.67,0:08:51.65,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やってやるです
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.25,0:09:02.12,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梓ちゃんも すっかり みんなと仲よくなったね
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.79,0:09:03.76,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうかな…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.13,0:09:08.72,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,りっちゃん博士 これを見てくだされ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.97,0:09:09.77,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪先輩
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.07,0:09:10.55,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.56,0:09:14.42,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フジツボの話って 知ってます？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.26,0:09:18.14,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昔 フジツボで足を切った少年が…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.05,0:09:20.78,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ あの 澪先…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.36,0:09:23.19,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…パイ？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.35,0:09:27.78,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだまだ 前だよ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.97,0:09:28.54,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう ちょっと
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.61,0:09:29.66,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いけいけ～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.41,0:09:31.49,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっちゃた～
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.48,0:09:36.36,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょうだい
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.46,0:09:37.08,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ダメです
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.39,0:09:39.00,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.22,0:09:43.33,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アハハハハ 私としたことが…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.96,0:09:58.05,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここは？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.03,0:10:01.20,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無人島…
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.11,0:10:07.07,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,りっちゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.03,0:10:11.28,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゆ… い？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.64,0:10:17.65,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゆッ 唯！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.94,0:10:19.84,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,りっちゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.24,0:10:23.34,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ついに 来たんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.75,0:10:25.86,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新大陸だーッ！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.30,0:10:27.35,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ジパング！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.47,0:10:29.03,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黄金の島～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.77,0:10:28.87,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,25)\fs20}何 やってんすか？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.21,0:10:31.30,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふは～
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.52,0:10:32.96,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遊んだ 遊んだ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.33,0:10:35.65,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう ご飯食べて 寝ようよ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.84,0:10:37.14,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,練習はどうした？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.51,0:10:41.49,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり 遊ばずに先に 練習した方がよかったんじゃないですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.12,0:10:44.19,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梓が一番 遊んでたじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.40,0:10:45.32,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真っ黒んなって
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.31,0:10:48.29,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私は ちゃんと練習もするもん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.51,0:10:49.72,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ 一晩中？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.69,0:10:52.89,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,するもん！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.20,0:10:58.34,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,けいおん！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.27,0:11:02.54,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疲れた～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.74,0:11:04.13,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おなかすいた
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.26,0:11:05.17,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ガマンしろ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.97,0:11:09.48,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すごーい
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.76,0:11:14.14,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確かに すごいな
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.45,0:11:16.73,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あんなアンプ 使ったことないです
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.95,0:11:18.96,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪 早く練習しようぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.15,0:11:20.50,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,スネアが新品だ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.71,0:11:21.96,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現金なヤツ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.11,0:11:26.97,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あずにゃん それ な～に？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.20,0:11:29.12,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい これですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.44,0:11:30.97,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ただのチューナーですけど
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.30,0:11:33.96,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へえ～ チューナーって言うんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.21,0:11:36.10,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これで チューニングするんですけど
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.69,0:11:39.31,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯先輩 チューナー 知らないんですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.71,0:11:41.45,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん 初めて見た
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.94,0:11:43.97,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ どうやってチューニングを？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.88,0:11:47.71,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,適当に… ほら
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.22,0:11:50.71,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ぜッ 絶対音感！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.07,0:11:53.82,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すごいのか すごくないのか 分からない人だ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.19,0:11:56.21,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ いくよ～
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.87,0:11:58.37,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ワン ツー スリー フォー
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.88,0:12:08.08,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今のすごく いい感じでしたよね
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.53,0:12:10.03,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ピッタリ合ったね
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.62,0:12:11.80,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,25)\fs20}素敵 唯ちゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.22,0:12:13.85,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,みんな いつの間に練習してたんだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.60,0:12:13.93,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,25)\fs20}いやいやいや
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.18,0:12:16.70,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律も ちゃんとリズムキープできてたなあ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.97,0:12:18.60,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特訓でもしたのか？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.60,0:12:24.13,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おなかが すいて 力が出ない
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.42,0:12:27.79,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おなかすいてるから ムダな力抜けたのね～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.65,0:12:30.55,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう ご飯にしよう
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.01,0:12:33.32,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,メシ 食わせろ～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.06,0:12:35.25,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私も
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.44,0:12:37.90,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戻ったよ～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.21,0:12:39.42,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おっかえり～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.63,0:12:40.44,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ただいま
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.77,0:12:43.89,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,りっちゃん お肉だよ お野菜だよ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.18,0:12:45.45,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待ってました～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.06,0:12:50.12,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丸ごとキャベツ 生でも食ってやる～
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.20,0:12:51.70,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっとは ガマンしろ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.61,0:12:54.43,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつも遊んでばかりなのに
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.28,0:12:56.26,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,25)\fs20}…できない ガマンできない
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.84,0:12:57.42,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,演奏すると 何か いいんだよなあ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.69,0:12:59.98,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離せ～ キャベツの…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.06,0:13:02.98,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,みんなで手分けしてやったら すぐできるから
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.50,0:13:03.17,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,25)\fs20}キャベツのカミサマがお怒りじゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.51,0:13:05.87,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ 私 コンロの火を見ます
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.53,0:13:09.77,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほら 後輩が率先して 頑張ってるんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.42,0:13:11.60,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分かったよ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.07,0:13:17.15,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目が痛い～
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.62,0:13:19.21,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯 大丈夫か？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.09,0:13:21.01,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,りっちゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.75,0:13:22.44,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.57,0:13:24.45,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死ぬときは 一緒だよ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.99,0:13:25.63,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.87,0:13:31.73,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし じゃあ おにぎりでも作るか
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.95,0:13:32.60,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.41,0:13:42.92,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんなに違いが…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.31,0:13:47.50,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪ちゃんの手が 大きいのかしら
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.74,0:13:48.47,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うるさい！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.57,0:14:08.71,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ～ おいしかったあ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.32,0:14:10.53,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おいしかったです
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.78,0:14:12.10,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最高だあ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.51,0:14:14.79,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ 花火やろう
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.47,0:14:30.66,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終わっちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.83,0:14:33.06,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最後 消えるときって
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.32,0:14:35.93,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もうちょっと頑張れ 頑張れってなるよなあ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.46,0:14:38.80,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頑張れ 頑張れ…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.91,0:14:39.70,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.33,0:14:43.34,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし もう１本
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.74,0:14:46.36,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,頑張れ 頑張れ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.64,0:14:52.16,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,また 落ちちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.05,0:14:55.71,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,りっちゃん 消えちゃうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.91,0:14:58.64,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よ～し そんなときは合体で大きくするんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.90,0:15:02.06,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合体！ 線香花火マン
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.38,0:15:03.81,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あッ ズルイ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.16,0:15:05.10,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アホ…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.79,0:15:06.72,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重くない？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.94,0:15:07.94,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丈夫です
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.38,0:15:09.56,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肝試しを やろう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.84,0:15:10.63,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オーッ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.95,0:15:12.50,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次から次へと
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.73,0:15:13.52,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.76,0:15:15.46,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり 夏で合宿といえば
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.69,0:15:16.67,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肝試しだよね！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.07,0:15:18.33,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私は やらないぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.44,0:15:20.16,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そっか～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.41,0:15:22.35,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪は 怖いの苦手だもんね
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.50,0:15:24.95,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ぜんっぜん 余裕よ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.16,0:15:26.41,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やってやろうじゃないの
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.74,0:15:30.49,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なかなか ご飯 食べさせてもらえなかった恨み
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.66,0:15:31.77,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晴らさせてもらうぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.27,0:15:43.27,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こッ 高校生にもなって
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.47,0:15:45.61,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肝試しもないよな～
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.08,0:15:48.62,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの 手が痛いんですけど
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.15,0:15:53.36,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なッ 何でしょうか…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.72,0:15:55.37,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,き き き きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.60,0:15:57.89,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,り り 律の仕業だよ～
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.04,0:16:10.72,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪ちゃ～ん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.86,0:16:14.32,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,25)\fs20}うわー　怖いよ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.67,0:16:14.60,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先輩 先輩
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.80,0:16:15.93,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気を確かに
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.41,0:16:19.56,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,せッ 先生!?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.06,0:16:21.16,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうしたんですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.83,0:16:23.99,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よ… ようやく会えた
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.46,0:16:26.41,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれッ さわちゃん先生？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.65,0:16:27.54,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうしたの？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.79,0:16:29.16,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ていうか 何でいるの？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.85,0:16:35.58,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後から合流して みんなを驚かせようと思ったんだけど
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.03,0:16:37.64,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道に迷って
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.15,0:16:42.37,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驚かせようっていう目標は達成できたみたいですけど
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.70,0:16:45.61,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪ちゃん 大丈夫だから 澪ちゃん！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.93,0:16:49.04,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪先輩って こんなに怖がりだったんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.69,0:16:57.52,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰も こねえ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.12,0:17:03.66,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひどい目にあった
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.81,0:17:04.53,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まあまあ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.67,0:17:05.84,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪 澪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.25,0:17:14.13,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梓 熱いのダメなの？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.66,0:17:16.79,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや そうじゃないんですけど
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.10,0:17:20.96,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あずにゃん こういうのは勢いよく入った方が いいんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.27,0:17:23.46,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,痛いッ！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.28,0:17:25.94,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日焼けで痛かったのか
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.58,0:17:28.04,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯ちゃん 少しやせた？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.93,0:17:31.42,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ううん 前にも言ったと思うけど
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.64,0:17:34.56,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私 いくら食べても 体重増えないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.83,0:17:35.95,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うらやまし過ぎる！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.15,0:17:38.48,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えッ さわちゃん先生まで!?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.08,0:17:40.45,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しっかし
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.08,0:17:45.36,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,メガネとってると あんた達２人 見分けつかないわねえ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.47,0:17:52.84,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胸の大きさで判断すれば いいじゃない！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.34,0:17:53.90,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あは★
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.41,0:18:07.46,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゲル状…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.11,0:18:10.13,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キャベツ うめーッ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.05,0:18:33.28,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめんね 私の練習につきあわせて
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.75,0:18:35.54,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全然 気にしないでください
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.06,0:18:40.34,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私も唯先輩と もっと一緒に練習したいと思ってたんです
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.98,0:18:42.02,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ありがとう
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.79,0:18:43.88,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えっと
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.39,0:19:01.06,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あずにゃん うまいね
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.20,0:19:03.84,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなことないですよ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.06,0:19:07.08,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ 次 私ね
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.11,0:19:16.40,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここが難しいんだよね～
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.80,0:19:19.80,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初は スローテンポで弾いてみれば いいんですよ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.29,0:19:21.15,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こう？
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.33,0:19:38.72,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,できた～ッ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.76,0:19:41.91,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あずにゃんに出会えて よかったよ！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.48,0:19:45.11,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あずにゃ～ん
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.84,0:19:49.69,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ありがとう あずにゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.48,0:20:06.55,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんにちは 平沢憂です
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.14,0:20:09.34,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日も 梓ちゃんとお出かけです
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.29,0:20:11.20,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お～い
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.66,0:20:16.52,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめん 遅れちゃった～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.83,0:20:18.48,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう 遅いよ～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.72,0:20:19.83,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…て 誰？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.14,0:20:25.41,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あんまり練習できなかったんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.42,0:20:27.73,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもないんだけど
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.18,0:20:30.94,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと 特訓するものだと思ってたのに
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.22,0:20:33.18,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海水浴とか 肝試しとか
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.44,0:20:34.69,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほとんど遊んでた
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.16,0:20:37.98,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もっと練習したかったのに
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.43,0:20:39.36,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そっか～
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.88,0:20:42.96,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも お姉ちゃんは 全然焼けてなかったけど
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.24,0:20:45.02,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何で そんなに日焼けしてるの？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.67,0:20:47.07,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そッ それは…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.94,0:20:50.30,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私が一番はしゃいでたから
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.41,0:20:55.24,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもね…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.02,0:21:00.91,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱり 行ってよかった
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.16,0:21:05.57,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先輩達のいろんなことが分かったもん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.12,0:21:08.02,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へえ～ どんなふうに？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.59,0:21:12.39,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,う～ん 澪先輩は意外と怖がりだった
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.03,0:21:14.10,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうなんだ～
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.68,0:21:15.51,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,律さんは？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.22,0:21:18.12,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっぱ おおざっぱだったけど
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.68,0:21:20.73,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,澪先輩とは いい感じだった
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.35,0:21:22.41,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紬さんは？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.89,0:21:24.57,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ムギ先輩はね
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.02,0:21:27.29,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,みんなのことを思いやってて優しいけど
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.63,0:21:29.61,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,案外 子供っぽいところもあって
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.80,0:21:30.91,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,カワイイ人だったよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.43,0:21:32.33,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふ～ん
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.90,0:21:34.63,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,で お姉ちゃんは？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.26,0:21:37.79,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯先輩は…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.08,0:21:41.54,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちゃんと練習してた
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.11,0:21:43.20,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.88,0:21:54.72,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.52,0:22:02.38,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相変わらず 抱きついてこられるんだけどね
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.71,0:22:04.89,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あったかいでしょ お姉ちゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.59,0:22:08.29,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へへ… そだね
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.12,0:23:44.02,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うッ…弦 さびてるじゃないですか
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.48,0:23:47.05,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これ いつ弦を交換したんですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.27,0:23:50.16,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えッ 弦って交換するものなの？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.23,0:23:52.75,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なッ 何!?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.95,0:23:55.13,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これ…ビンテージギターですか？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.60,0:23:58.35,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すいません ただ汚いだけです
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.58,0:24:00.28,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだ買って１年です
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.65,0:24:03.83,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もし このまま戻ってこなかったら
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.94,0:24:08.67,Default_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学園祭のライブ どうなるんでしょう