[Script Info]
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,simhei,24,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: Note,simhei,16,&H1EFFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,&H327F7F7F,&H80000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,0,0,10,134
Style: 画面文字1,方正细圆简体,30,&H141F1F1F,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: 标题1,方正细圆简体,27,&H0ACAF4ED,&HF0CAF4ED,&H00CAF4ED,&HF0CAF4ED,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OP_JP,DFPMaruGothic-Lt,21,&H1EFFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00037256,&HF0037256,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: ED_JP,麗流隷書,22,&H1EFFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00037256,&HF0037256,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,128
Style: OP_CH,方正细圆简体,24,&H1EFFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00037256,&HF0037256,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ED_CH,方正隶变_GBK,26,&H1EFFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00037256,&HF0037256,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: NEXT,simhei,25,&H00CEDA67,&HF0000000,&H00CEDA67,&HF0CEDA67,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: 预告标题,simhei,25,&H1EBBF0F7,&HF0000000,&H00BBF0F7,&HF0BBF0F7,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.39,0:01:46.32,画面文字1,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,260)\fad(500,200)}奇诺为何要持续旅行呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.33,0:01:49.52,画面文字1,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,260)\fad(500,200)}都遇到了这种事情…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.90,0:01:53.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然是不知不觉的…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.13,0:01:55.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知不觉？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.41,0:01:57.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.47,0:02:01.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔会想自己是否是个无可救药、愚蠢而又矮小的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.41,0:02:04.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是否是个非常肮脏的人？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.01,0:02:06.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.81,0:02:08.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但有时会这么觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.15,0:02:14.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是 在那时我一定会认为
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.92,0:02:18.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,世界中的一切都是美丽且令人怜惜的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.53,0:02:22.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以 即便发生这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.13,0:02:26.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也仍会想去寻觅下一次邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.07,0:02:28.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,能明白吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.73,0:02:30.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说实话我不太懂
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.14,0:02:32.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那样就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.77,0:02:33.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.41,0:02:36.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许连我自己也不太了解
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.18,0:02:38.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,自己也正在迷惘着
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.85,0:02:43.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也可能是为了让自己更了解这件事才持续着旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.59,0:02:50.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.69,0:02:51.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.56,0:02:54.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明天还要跑好长一段路
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.83,0:02:55.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 艾尔梅斯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.16,0:02:57.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,晚安 奇诺
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.47,0:03:09.08,标题1,,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(320,250)\fad(500,100)}「和平之国」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.78,0:03:20.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么？奇诺
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.92,0:03:23.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不认得人类的尸体吗 艾尔梅斯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.66,0:03:24.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是这个意思啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.22,0:03:29.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想问的是为何这儿散落着这么多的木乃伊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.46,0:03:34.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若是墓地也太粗暴了吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.10,0:03:40.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到维尔迪鲁巴鲁{ヴェルデルヴァル}
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.77,0:03:41.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,旅行者
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.94,0:03:44.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫奇诺 这是我的同伴艾尔梅斯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.71,0:03:47.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请准许我们入国观光与补给
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.21,0:03:48.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您预定待几天？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.98,0:03:49.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.98,0:03:51.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,后天我就出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.15,0:03:54.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,滞留三天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.69,0:03:55.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,办妥了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.86,0:03:56.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请通过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.82,0:03:59.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,入国的审查真简单呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.49,0:04:00.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.63,0:04:02.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为本国目前很和平
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.10,0:04:04.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 奇诺
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.93,0:04:07.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您有无携带枪械呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.63,0:04:08.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.64,0:04:15.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莫非禁止携带枪械入境吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.94,0:04:18.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你带着这么棒的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.21,0:04:19.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想必您的身手也…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.88,0:04:21.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇诺可是四段黑带哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.95,0:04:24.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,呀～真是佩服
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.62,0:04:25.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若作为护身用
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.75,0:04:28.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你直接带枪入境也无妨
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.15,0:04:30.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过我想也一定派不上用场
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.59,0:04:32.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个国家很安全
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.09,0:04:35.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,国民也热爱着和平安稳的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.16,0:04:39.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想奇诺也一定会喜欢这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.31,0:04:47.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是个颇有历史的物品
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.71,0:04:50.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们就这么摆在这儿当作装饰了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.88,0:04:52.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 奇诺
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.14,0:04:52.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若你去观光的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.05,0:04:56.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请务必参观一下历史博物馆
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.22,0:04:58.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那里记录着本国所历经的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.09,0:05:00.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.35,0:05:01.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会前去造访
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.00,0:05:13.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,感觉也不像是很安稳的国家呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.64,0:05:17.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不见得是这样哦 艾尔梅斯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.27,0:05:19.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些都是过去使用的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.57,0:05:22.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,目前似乎已经毫无用处了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.74,0:05:25.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为何会变成那样呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.01,0:05:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这点我虽然不清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.85,0:05:30.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但也不像是历经了重大战争的国家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.66,0:05:38.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.16,0:05:38.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么声音？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.09,0:05:41.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是军队在演习
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.99,0:05:42.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.80,0:05:45.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好 下一排
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.77,0:05:46.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瞄准
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.34,0:05:57.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为明天要发动战争了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.71,0:05:58.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咦？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.78,0:06:00.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇诺所说的话一点也信不得呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.95,0:06:04.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下一排
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.72,0:06:07.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瞄准
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.92,0:06:08.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,开枪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.29,0:06:16.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看我的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.00,0:06:17.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快住手
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.86,0:06:20.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.27,0:06:25.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这里就是历史博物馆吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.33,0:06:29.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.40,0:06:32.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽说是战争 但那并不会危及旅行者
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.18,0:06:34.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以请尽管放心
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.11,0:06:38.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那并非是像上个时代那样的战争
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.72,0:06:39.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,此话怎讲？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.09,0:06:42.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你若想获知详情…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.35,0:06:43.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想想看…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.69,0:06:46.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你去历史博物馆看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.66,0:06:47.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想那儿的馆长
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.96,0:06:51.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一定会亲切地向你一一道来的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.27,0:07:02.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.34,0:07:09.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎莅临我们的历史博物馆
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.72,0:07:11.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是馆长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.72,0:07:20.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}当人们首次在这片荒芜的土地生活时
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.96,0:07:24.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}这里不过是仅有数十人的小部落
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.16,0:07:28.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}我们的祖先开渠引水、开垦农田
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.95,0:07:31.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}使城镇取得了翻天覆地的发展
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.04,0:07:34.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}此后商业进一步发展
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.24,0:07:37.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}城墙的壁垒也随之日益扩大
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.74,0:07:40.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}我国一直延续至今的发展基础
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.81,0:07:42.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1}也正是在这个时代中得以成型
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.25,0:07:48.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想要在空无一物的地方立国
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.42,0:07:50.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认为是非常辛苦的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.36,0:07:56.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们的国家就是因祖先的努力而得以成立的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.80,0:07:58.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可是…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.76,0:08:02.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,国家强大之后 所迎来的也未必都是好事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.27,0:08:03.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,旅行者
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.11,0:08:09.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,国家要变得强大
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.78,0:08:12.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就必须与他国接触
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.28,0:08:15.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那其中也有不幸的邂逅
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.28,0:08:17.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.35,0:08:20.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这边开始就是近代史的区域
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.86,0:08:29.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们同邻国雷尔斯米亚{レルスミア}最初的战争
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.53,0:08:32.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,发生于距今192年前
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.30,0:08:39.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,两国间逐渐展开的以丘陵地领土权\N为中心的争执即是战争的根源
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.27,0:08:41.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若此事属实
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.94,0:08:45.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,或许本该是能用外交手段来解决的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.88,0:08:47.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过…
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.81,0:08:51.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当人种、语言、宗教、生活习惯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.59,0:08:55.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他一切都和本国不同的民族与自己国家为邻时
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.59,0:08:59.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,彼此的敌视是一触即发的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.53,0:09:02.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战争愈演愈烈
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.23,0:09:05.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与此同时 新型武器也被开发了出来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.53,0:09:08.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,众多的人因此而亡
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.27,0:09:12.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,两国间时常会开启战端
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.04,0:09:14.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,国力也日渐衰退
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.07,0:09:17.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在不知哪方会取得胜利的情况下
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.94,0:09:21.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反覆进行着休战的动作
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.18,0:09:24.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,直到距今15年前为止都是如此…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.19,0:09:28.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您说距今15年前都是那样的吧？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.05,0:09:29.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.26,0:09:34.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在看起来 这个国家非常和平安定
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.36,0:09:37.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与邻国间的纷争已经消失了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.40,0:09:41.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,目前我们已不再相互残杀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.27,0:09:44.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在突然达成和平的15年前
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.84,0:09:45.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究竟发生了什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.34,0:09:49.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这将会在下个展区中说明…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.04,0:09:53.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但遗憾的是 今天已经没有时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.38,0:10:01.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇诺你们会滞留多久呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.55,0:10:02.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,后天会出发
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.06,0:10:04.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前我随时都有空
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.89,0:10:09.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然如此 明天我会向您揭晓那个答案
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.90,0:10:13.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们是如何努力地建立并维护着和平
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.10,0:10:16.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就请您亲自前往参观见习吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.60,0:10:17.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,参观什么呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.54,0:10:20.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,参观「战争」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.59,0:10:43.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是奇诺和艾尔梅斯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.16,0:10:47.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我从馆长那儿听说了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.50,0:10:50.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天由我为两位带路
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.14,0:10:52.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请坐上这辆「浮游车」
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.14,0:10:55.51,Note,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(200,300)}浮游车：原文“ホヴィー”（Hovi），“Hover Vehicles”的略称，指浮游车辆。
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.20,0:10:56.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那片凹凸不平的土地 普通车辆是无法行驶的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.38,0:10:58.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来 请上乘
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.58,0:11:39.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们是雷尔斯米亚的国防军
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.09,0:11:46.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,雷尔斯米亚就是跟你们打了近200年战争的邻国吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.32,0:11:47.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.59,0:11:49.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等会他们就要「打仗」了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.26,0:11:51.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊 不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.80,0:11:53.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不会有半个士兵死亡的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.37,0:11:56.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这和以前的战争不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.75,0:12:12.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在开始
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.50,0:12:18.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第185次雷尔斯米亚·维尔迪鲁巴鲁战争
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.24,0:12:33.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是这一带的部族
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.64,0:12:34.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,塔塔达人{タタタ人}
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.01,0:12:36.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请看
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.48,0:12:46.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从那条线划分的这一端 属于我军
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.55,0:12:49.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而对面则是雷尔斯米亚的战场
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.56,0:12:52.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哦！开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.49,0:14:03.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,时间到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.69,0:14:05.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,战争结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.01,0:14:20.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在开始发表统计结果
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.45,0:14:24.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,10比9
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.42,0:14:26.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,胜利国 维尔迪鲁巴鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.85,0:14:29.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.79,0:14:30.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们赢了！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.59,0:14:31.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇诺 艾尔梅斯
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.29,0:14:34.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,回国后 大家一定会非常喜庆的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.95,0:14:59.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你观看昨天的战争了吗？奇诺
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.79,0:15:02.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 看过了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.05,0:15:04.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这下木乃伊的谜底也解开了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.82,0:15:07.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是你们的「战争」吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.03,0:15:13.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我看来只是对塔塔达人的虐杀或是处刑罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.83,0:15:17.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但那就是我们的「战争」
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.68,0:15:32.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,以前的战争我还历历在目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.35,0:15:36.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在长年以来毫无厌倦的战争中
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.35,0:15:38.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,死去了无数的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.36,0:15:40.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无数的人…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.83,0:15:44.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我曾拥有家人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.30,0:15:46.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,丈夫与四个儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.86,0:15:48.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们是我的无价之宝
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.33,0:15:50.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.80,0:15:54.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在我的丈夫失去了上半身
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.61,0:16:00.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们立志要替父亲报仇
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.34,0:16:02.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,接二连三地志愿从军去了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.35,0:16:06.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最初是次子索德斯被狙击身亡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.58,0:16:10.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,隔日达德斯踩到地雷 被炸得粉身碎骨
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.89,0:16:13.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,长子乌德斯则是遭受了己方的炮击
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.62,0:16:14.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连同敌军一起被轰杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.96,0:16:17.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最后仅有四子由德斯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.73,0:16:23.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说一定会活着回来的他 在离乡后就一去不归了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.60,0:16:31.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我拼命思索着有无不打这种无谓之战的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.80,0:16:33.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,于是我作出了一个提案
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.81,0:16:37.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就是昨天的战争吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.55,0:16:38.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.24,0:16:41.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅主张「不要再争战了」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.09,0:16:43.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根本不会有任何改变
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.79,0:16:50.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为人类的竞争心、敌忾心、残忍心都是与生俱来的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.29,0:16:54.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以必须是一个能令其找到宣泄出口的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.37,0:16:56.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我发表这个提议时
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.97,0:17:01.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对方阵营也偶然有个女性跟我想着同样的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.25,0:17:12.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是距今15年前的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.68,0:17:16.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,之后两国缔结了条约
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.79,0:17:20.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,舍弃了杀伤力过强的兵器
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.79,0:17:24.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为即使将塔塔达人全灭也毫无意义
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.80,0:17:27.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,托此之福 国防经费得到了大幅的裁减
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.77,0:17:30.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.20,0:17:33.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这也是最为重要的一点
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.84,0:17:35.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,从那以后
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.27,0:17:40.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,两国间再也没发生过会让国民死亡的战争
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.79,0:17:52.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,历史博物馆之旅至此就告终了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.26,0:17:53.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.66,0:17:58.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以向你提一个问题吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.83,0:17:59.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请便
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.86,0:18:03.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被杀的塔塔达人又该如何是好？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.73,0:18:07.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想他们也都有自己的生活和自己的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.77,0:18:09.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,请您计算一下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.77,0:18:11.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,塔塔达人的牺牲人数
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.98,0:18:15.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,与以往我们的战争造成的牺牲人数相比
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.21,0:18:17.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根本就是少到不能再少了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.05,0:18:19.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.25,0:18:20.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.45,0:18:22.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,您还有其他的腹案吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.25,0:18:25.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,若有则望不吝赐教
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.23,0:18:29.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇诺
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.43,0:18:32.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和平是需要牺牲的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.76,0:18:37.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而所牺牲的人 绝不可以是我们的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.04,0:18:46.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢您的娓娓道来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.21,0:18:50.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哪里 不用客气
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.01,0:18:52.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.22,0:18:59.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,馆长 我无法了解
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.12,0:19:02.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,究竟是你现在的做法是错的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.26,0:19:05.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还是以前的人们才是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.91,0:19:16.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.87,0:19:18.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要是再上些岁数
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.98,0:19:21.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就能了解我的感受了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.95,0:19:24.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是如此吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.85,0:19:31.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当你怀着你的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.99,0:19:35.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在自己体内感知那个孩子的温暖时
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.30,0:19:41.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你一定会了解的……
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.97,0:19:50.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个馆长的家人被杀是很可怜没错
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.01,0:19:53.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过那种和平还是让人敬谢不敏呢 奇诺
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.15,0:19:59.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像有什么掉了哦 奇诺
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.92,0:20:08.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是旅人的行李
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.93,0:20:10.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,竟有这么多…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.09,0:20:12.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,奇诺
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.97,0:20:20.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们找我有事吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.37,0:20:27.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在要把你带到我们的村落
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.01,0:20:29.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后在大家的面前
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.25,0:20:32.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,将你大卸八块、折磨至死
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.28,0:20:33.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这又是为何呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.28,0:20:36.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们的复仇
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.09,0:20:40.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我…不是那个国家的人哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.59,0:20:42.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道 旅行者
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.79,0:20:44.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们憎恨着那个国家
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.36,0:20:47.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们被毫无意义地杀戮
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.20,0:20:51.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,连埋葬心爱之人都无法办到
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.97,0:20:54.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但就算我们战斗也无法获胜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.47,0:20:56.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以…无论是谁都无妨…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.27,0:21:01.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们会将恰巧经过此地的你 折磨至死
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.18,0:21:03.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就算只有一点点…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.55,0:21:05.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们也必须满足我们的复仇心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.15,0:21:09.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我深知你们的感受
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.52,0:21:12.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我还不想死
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.62,0:21:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也不会忘了你们
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.86,0:21:16.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么 恕我告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.35,0:21:45.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.46,0:22:22.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了 奇诺
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.29,0:22:24.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你不去邻国没关系吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.90,0:22:28.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有这个必要 艾尔梅斯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.25,0:23:51.25,NEXT,,0000,0000,0000,,下集预告
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.28,0:23:55.33,预告标题,,0000,0000,0000,,「温柔之国」
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.08,0:23:59.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在造访的国家中 奇诺最喜欢的是哪个？
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.93,0:24:01.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道哪个才是最喜欢的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.83,0:24:03.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但直接想到的就是那个国家
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.00,0:24:04.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个国家？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.47,0:24:09.78,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在那儿 接受了连同无数旅行者的份在内的温柔
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.33,0:24:11.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以无法忘怀
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.34,0:24:13.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人们的笑容
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.96,0:24:14.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,此外还有…
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.27,0:24:17.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那个以花为名的女孩…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.25,0:00:10.78,OP_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}空は果てしない 心の鏡だからね
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.63,0:00:20.04,OP_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}毎日色を変えてく 映し出すように
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.46,0:00:28.07,OP_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}白く はいた 煙 雲になって
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.30,0:00:32.77,OP_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}こぼれ そうな 涙 隠していて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.01,0:00:37.39,OP_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}信じる 物が 壊れてく時には
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.62,0:00:40.93,OP_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}目を閉じて願う
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.22,0:00:50.47,OP_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}一人きりで 眠れない 夜に落ちても
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.59,0:01:04.68,OP_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}闇の中に 瞳とじて 星の輝きに耳を澄ましてる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.93,0:01:13.96,OP_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}譲れないから 裸足でも 走り続ける
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.15,0:01:28.44,OP_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}蒼い空の 月のように 儚さ抱いて手を伸ばしたい
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.25,0:00:10.78,OP_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}天空广阔无垠 只因那是心之明镜吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.63,0:00:20.04,OP_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}每日都映照出与昔迥异的色彩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.46,0:00:28.07,OP_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}喷吐的白烟 化作云朵
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.30,0:00:32.77,OP_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}滑落的泪水 悄悄隐藏
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.01,0:00:37.39,OP_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}坚信的事物 崩溃之时
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.62,0:00:40.93,OP_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}轻闭双眼 默默乞愿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.22,0:00:50.47,OP_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}就算独自身临难以入眠的夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.59,0:01:04.68,OP_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}亦可于黑暗中阖上双眸 侧耳倾听群星的光辉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.93,0:01:13.96,OP_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}因为绝不退让 即便一无所有 也要继续前行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.15,0:01:28.44,OP_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}想要伸手怀抱青空中 那宛若月亮般的虚幻
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.13,0:22:51.30,ED_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}遠くで降りだした雨
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.77,0:23:02.26,ED_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}だれかが濡れながら そっと震える
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.81,0:23:07.48,ED_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}森に迷い 空に寄り添う
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.18,0:23:12.66,ED_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}国を訪ね 人と行き交い
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.88,0:23:21.23,ED_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,400)}そして旅は終わらない
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.35,0:23:27.49,ED_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}So the Beautiful World
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.74,0:23:34.24,ED_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}何処から来た 何処まで行く
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.47,0:23:38.19,ED_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,200)}So the Beautiful World
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.37,0:23:47.65,ED_JP,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(200,400)}流れるまま 世界を走る
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.13,0:22:51.30,ED_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}远方雨点洒落
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.77,0:23:02.26,ED_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}是谁淋着雨 悄悄颤抖
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.81,0:23:07.48,ED_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}迷失森林 靠近天空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.18,0:23:12.66,ED_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}寻访各色国度 与人交错相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.88,0:23:21.23,ED_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,400)}旅途将永无止境
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.35,0:23:27.49,ED_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}So the Beautiful World
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.74,0:23:34.24,ED_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}从何而来 又将从何而去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.47,0:23:38.19,ED_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,200)}So the Beautiful World
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.37,0:23:47.65,ED_CH,,0000,0000,0000,,{\an3\fad(200,400)}任之漂流 走遍世界
