[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub r6195M13 (development version, 2.1.9 codebase, SAPikachu)
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title:JoJo's Bizarre Adventure(2012) TV #23
Original Script:A.I.R.nesSub & MYSUB
Website:http://airu.us/
Website:http://www.manyv.com.cn/
Synch Point:0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000F0F0F,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,30,30,30,1
Style: Staff,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000F0F0F,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,5,5,5,1
Style: Comment,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF0F0F0F,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,30,1
Style: Title,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H000F0F0F,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,30,30,30,1
Style: OPJ,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,40,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OPC,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,40,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: EDE,WenQuanYi Micro Hei,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: insert,文泉驿微米黑,36,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&HC0000000,&H96000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,8,30,30,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Comment: 0,0:00:00.30,0:00:00.30,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,========Opening========
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.45,0:00:13.82,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,静寂の底から
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.46,0:00:20.85,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目覚めるその柱たち 時を越え
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.15,0:00:28.09,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深紅の血潮が
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.98,0:00:35.01,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立ち上がる勇気を 惹きあわせる
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.78,0:00:43.20,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受け継ぐ愛を 宿命と呼ぶなら
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.48,0:00:49.42,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,微笑む目で 次の手を
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:55.99,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暗を欺いて 刹那を躱して
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.27,0:00:59.55,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刃すり抜け 奴等の隙を突け
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.88,0:01:05.66,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,つらぬいた信念が 未来を拓く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.30,0:01:08.49,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Like a Bloody Storm
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.68,0:01:10.66,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熱く Like a Bloody Stone
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.91,0:01:14.16,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血脈に刻まれた因縁に
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.46,0:01:25.91,OPJ,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆を 握りしめて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.45,0:00:13.82,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自深邃的静寂中
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.46,0:00:20.85,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石柱们觉醒过来 超越时空
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.15,0:00:28.09,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深红的血潮
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.98,0:00:35.01,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与涌现的勇气相互吸引
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.78,0:00:43.20,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如承继的爱 可以称作宿命
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.48,0:00:49.42,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就用微笑的眼神 应对下一次挑战吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.52,0:00:55.99,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗过黑暗 刹那间闪过
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.27,0:00:59.55,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,避过利刃 找到他们的破绽
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.88,0:01:05.66,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,代代相承的精神将开拓未来
Comment: 0,0:01:07.30,0:01:08.49,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Like a Bloody Storm
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.68,0:01:10.66,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,热情 Like a Bloody Stone
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.91,0:01:14.16,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将从铭刻于血脉的因缘中
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.46,0:01:25.91,OPC,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浮现而出 那不灭而荣耀的羁绊 紧握于手中

Comment: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,========A Part========
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.50,0:01:35.49,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\pos(890,600)\be4}第23话 「随风而逝的战士」
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.73,0:01:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}风…怎么…被吸进瓦姆乌的管子里
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.20,0:01:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终流法——浑楔飒！
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.93,0:01:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这是风吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.39,0:01:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你在火坛边上
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.50,0:01:59.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo 我只能把握到你大概的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.28,0:02:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 现在你停止了波纹的呼吸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.00,0:02:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我逐厘米扫过去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.66,0:02:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一定能找到你的身体 切成两半
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.42,0:02:09.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浑楔飒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.92,0:02:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓦姆乌的最终流法
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.74,0:02:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不同于让身体透明的用法
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.60,0:02:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这招反其道行之 吸入大量的风
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.97,0:02:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在肺内部极度压缩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.11,0:02:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再从窄如剃刀的缝隙中
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.19,0:02:24.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以超高压强喷射出去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.77,0:02:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以说 是一道烈风之刃
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.26,0:02:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 风的高速压缩带来的摩擦和热力
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.99,0:02:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是瓦姆乌的肉体也无法承受
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.62,0:02:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会慢慢地遭到破坏
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.97,0:02:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 那凄惨的样子 实在太美了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.51,0:02:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胜利是属于你的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.09,0:02:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢下这场战斗 用人类的生命治愈自己的伤吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.80,0:02:47.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo！
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.01,0:02:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来…来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.75,0:02:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要想办法反抗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.91,0:02:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我称为 波纹油作战
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.20,0:03:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的体内 可以说是一个超浓缩的氧气瓶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.49,0:03:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要把这火焰瓶扔向他的管子
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.68,0:03:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就会把火吸进去 引起体内爆炸！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.39,0:03:11.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 这也是我的最终策略
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.73,0:03:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦失败就要完蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.92,0:03:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,NWWW 找到了 在那里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.80,0:03:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 吃招！瓦姆乌！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.26,0:03:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火焰瓶吗 没意思
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.12,0:03:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要离开火坛有一米距离
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.38,0:03:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就能感受到物体的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.16,0:03:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你已经束手无策了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.35,0:03:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你刚才的喊声 让我确定到你的位置了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.86,0:03:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上！浑楔飒！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.79,0:03:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西——撒——！靠你了！
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.14,0:03:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要丢火种吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.21,0:03:56.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你丢什么 在我1米范围内就能察觉到
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.59,0:04:02.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 我现在就把你切断 就分出胜负！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.38,0:04:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.25,0:04:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终…终于赢了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.53,0:04:14.58,insert,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\blur2}Ovunque tu vada
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.08,0:04:20.86,insert,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\blur2}Ovunque io vada
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.17,0:04:26.87,insert,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\blur2}C'é il mio amor nella tua vita,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.33,0:04:34.30,insert,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\blur2}c'é I'amor nella tua giornata
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.51,0:04:42.94,insert,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\blur2}Basta un tuo sorriso.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.94,0:04:49.54,insert,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\blur2}un tuo sol sorriso
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.58,0:04:58.08,insert,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\blur2}Non morirà I'alma mia. é immortal!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.76,0:05:14.00,insert,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\blur2}Non serve versar lacrime
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.65,0:04:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓦姆乌 刚才西撒的头带已经敲响了你的丧钟
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.01,0:04:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道火焰瓶是故意给你切的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.50,0:04:25.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的能力轻松地切断瓶子 才导致你的败北
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.62,0:04:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,油被吸进你体内成为雾状燃气
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.57,0:04:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而被你切碎的西撒的头带——
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.52,0:04:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火…火没有全灭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.87,0:04:38.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些火星也被吸进去了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.19,0:04:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓦姆乌 你是一个非常优秀的战士
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.74,0:04:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 我有西撒这个强大的同伴一直支持着我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.56,0:05:00.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,输…输了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.14,0:05:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,输了 瓦姆乌大人输了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.09,0:05:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo 即使炸成碎片 他依然能复活
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.45,0:05:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用从拳头释放出来的最强的波纹消灭他！
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.57,0:05:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终…终于分出胜负了啊 JoJo
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.40,0:05:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.91,0:05:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西撒大仇得报…了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.91,0:05:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.77,0:05:45.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 杀了我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.38,0:05:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好！
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.37,0:06:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.74,0:06:07.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些烟不是爆炸产生的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.95,0:06:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是波纹伤的烟
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.37,0:06:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来之前胸口和脚上中的波纹
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.86,0:06:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经蔓延到你全身了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.30,0:06:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道对你们来说 波纹有多么的痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.71,0:06:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经无法治愈了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.09,0:06:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少用我的血 让你去得没那么痛苦吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.64,0:06:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋 你要侮辱我瓦姆乌吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.05,0:06:32.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 我不需要敌人的施舍
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.20,0:06:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,施舍？你说“施舍”吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.40,0:06:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 为什么你会留下包着西撒的头带
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.37,0:06:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和这个蕴含着他的心意的解毒药戒指的泡泡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.92,0:06:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是出于施舍吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.48,0:06:52.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那个男人是一个高贵的战士
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.42,0:06:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我对一个战士的敬意
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.42,0:06:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你惊异地发现“难道JoJo你……”
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.44,0:07:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道JoJo你……
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.02,0:07:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 瓦姆乌
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.81,0:07:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战斗是一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.83,0:07:07.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西撒的死带来的悲伤又是一回事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.95,0:07:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不自觉地要向你表达敬意
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.40,0:07:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这点血是向你致敬
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.21,0:07:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼 我服了 JoJo
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.57,0:07:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你是一个比我更出色的战士
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.77,0:07:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了他！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.16,0:07:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手！你们要干什么！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.61,0:07:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这些小人！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.46,0:07:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓦姆乌！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.58,0:07:53.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为…为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.50,0:07:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我瓦姆乌直到最后一刻依然追随卡兹大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.66,0:08:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 不允许这些吸血鬼出手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.71,0:08:03.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也对着西撒说过
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.87,0:08:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不是我变得像人类般伤感
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.60,0:08:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我瓦姆乌看来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.19,0:08:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,强者才是真理
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.20,0:08:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胜利者才是正义 才值得我付出友情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.00,0:08:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是忠于自己的原则而已
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.09,0:08:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo 我瓦姆乌活了那么久
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.72,0:08:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不老不死对我来说无关紧要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.18,0:08:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要到生命的最后一刻 始终贯彻这条原则
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.20,0:08:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 在我面前吃下解毒药
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.80,0:08:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我消灭之前
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.62,0:08:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能感觉到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.06,0:08:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,触角 视力 话语都不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.18,0:08:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能感受到 只要有动作就足够了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.23,0:08:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下 死而无憾了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.75,0:09:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衷心的为你的成长而高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.39,0:09:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我是为了与你相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.20,0:09:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而在这个世界徘徊了一万几千年
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.31,0:09:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永…别…了…Jo…Jo…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.83,0:09:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓦姆乌化为风了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.07,0:09:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo在无意识下做出的 是一个敬礼的动作
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.00,0:09:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管没有眼泪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.15,0:09:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是耳边回响着无声的男人之间的歌声
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.21,0:09:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心中怀着一份奇妙的友情
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.12,0:09:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓦姆乌 杀了他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.99,0:09:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但…但是 卡兹大人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.71,0:09:57.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请恕我直言 那只是个少年
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.94,0:09:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少年 没错
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.31,0:10:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此更要杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.01,0:10:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波纹的少年战士成人后
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.33,0:10:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能会成为我们的强大天敌
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.30,0:10:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短短的时间内 人类就会成长
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.17,0:10:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做不到吗 瓦姆乌
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.87,0:10:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 既然你做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.28,0:10:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我就来做个示范
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.07,0:10:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下手 瓦姆乌！
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.39,0:10:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瓦姆乌 作为一个战士 他太过于纯粹了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.36,0:10:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那成为了他的弱点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.70,0:10:35.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 瓦姆乌那家伙输了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.89,0:10:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 太失望了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.84,0:10:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋 让他装逼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.38,0:10:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些家伙确实是一群人渣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.20,0:10:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听得我都要吐了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.23,0:10:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡兹大人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.18,0:10:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被…被吸干了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.18,0:10:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就剩下我卡兹一个人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.18,0:11:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 能站在顶点的 永远都只有一人
Comment: 0,0:00:00.75,0:00:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,========B Part========
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.61,0:11:12.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡兹大人他…噢噢…卡兹大人他…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.42,0:11:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进入战斗态势了！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.64,0:11:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 卡兹大人 没必要再举行一对一的决斗了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.98,0:11:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要讲规矩
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.07,0:11:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好就由我们将他们——
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.51,0:11:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碎尸万段！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.04,0:11:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们果然要来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.00,0:11:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.50,0:11:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赤…赤石！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.43,0:11:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,规则是卡兹和我一对一
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.25,0:11:44.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你们胆敢不守信用的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.53,0:11:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我宁为玉碎 不为瓦存！
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.42,0:11:50.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我守信用 一对一
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.75,0:11:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从来没有想过要悔约
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.40,0:11:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才摘下头巾露出触角
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.95,0:11:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些渣的行动是自把自为
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.48,0:12:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过他们已经死了 你满意了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.09,0:12:05.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡兹大人！
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.59,0:12:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的目的是那颗赤石
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.22,0:12:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是艾斯迪斯和瓦姆乌是一起走过一万多年的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.55,0:12:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对他们的死 对这场荣耀之战的心意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.35,0:12:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会贯彻到底
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.75,0:12:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我非常渴望亲手跟你们波纹战士
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.40,0:12:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,堂堂正正地来个了结
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.00,0:12:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 莉莎莉莎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.62,0:12:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你刚才的英姿 我已经不小看你一个女人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.04,0:12:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我卡兹 将使出所有能力来打倒你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.26,0:12:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟着来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.60,0:12:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个决斗场是那里——
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.87,0:12:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮兹·伯尔尼纳山神殿遗迹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.15,0:12:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在古代 下面的战车战角斗场的胜利者
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.30,0:12:53.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这所神殿喝下注入败者的血液的贡酒
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.48,0:12:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢上帝赐予的生命的喜悦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.64,0:12:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这里不是角斗场
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.14,0:13:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是可以享受一番立体式的战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.93,0:13:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉…莉莎莉莎老师
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.18,0:13:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管你很强 但依然是个女人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.04,0:13:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看起来比瓦姆乌要弱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.94,0:13:09.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这战让我来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.56,0:13:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必多言
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.45,0:13:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生没有那么柔弱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.91,0:13:19.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要区区一个20岁的小毛孩的同情和担心
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.35,0:13:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是50岁！
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.55,0:13:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有流法“辉彩滑刀”
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.85,0:13:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不让你拿武器
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.66,0:13:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会侮辱瓦姆乌骄傲的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.89,0:13:34.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挑你喜欢的武器吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.30,0:13:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己的这条围巾就足够
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.96,0:13:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 那么来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.47,0:13:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡…卡兹的这个架势…没有杀气
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.84,0:13:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能不散发出杀气战斗吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.15,0:13:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 不出招吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.59,0:14:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我先来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.56,0:14:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡兹在一阵光芒中消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.74,0:14:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.07,0:14:14.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡兹…这气息…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.79,0:14:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能会从上方攻击…也可能从下方来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.91,0:14:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流法“辉彩滑刀”！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.03,0:14:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从柱子的缝隙里出来！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.09,0:14:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs32\pos(615,625)}Snake Muffler
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.09,0:14:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛇首立带！
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.93,0:14:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这条围巾是用婆罗洲甲虫做成的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.35,0:14:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波纹传导率100%的线所织成的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.70,0:14:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既是波纹武器 也是生命反应雷达
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.98,0:14:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从后而来的攻击也能探知到
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.75,0:15:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成…成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.94,0:15:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师你果然很厉害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.46,0:15:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟瓦姆乌相比太没劲了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.57,0:15:07.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 越装腔作势的人越是不堪一击呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.02,0:15:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师的实力更胜我一筹呀
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.28,0:15:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡…卡兹大人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.99,0:15:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡…卡兹那家伙在后面
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.80,0:15:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面那个是…是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.90,0:15:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事…这究竟是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.28,0:15:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才战斗的不是卡兹
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.70,0:15:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是替身！
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.84,0:15:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无聊 什么一对一的决斗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.76,0:15:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我卡兹的目的仅仅是赤石
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.89,0:15:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅仅是成为终极生物
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.16,0:15:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既不想成为瓦姆乌那样的战士
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.35,0:15:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不爱浪漫
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.23,0:15:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管用什么手段
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.20,0:15:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要取得最终胜利不就行了！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.12,0:16:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难…难怪感受不到杀气
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.81,0:16:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始就没打算自己上场…啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.35,0:16:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一击！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.99,0:16:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jo…Jo
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.27,0:16:17.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赤石已经到手
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.44,0:16:22.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来 就由你们来收拾这个罗哩叭嗦的JoJo
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.94,0:16:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡…卡兹！不可饶恕！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.68,0:16:35.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡兹！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.76,0:16:37.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们给我滚开！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.65,0:16:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个个打爆你们的头 混蛋！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.87,0:16:42.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长臂拳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.86,0:16:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波纹没什么效果呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.30,0:16:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙不行…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.98,0:16:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波纹肘支疾走！
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.04,0:17:01.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你相当疲劳呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.13,0:17:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呼吸紊乱 波纹力量在减弱了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.57,0:17:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是拜莉莎莉莎为师练出来的波纹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.22,0:17:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这么多人的攻势下 撑得住吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.63,0:17:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撑得住吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.46,0:17:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo 撑得住…吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.48,0:17:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可…可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.82,0:17:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将他五马分尸
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.16,0:17:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟…糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.37,0:17:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这…这些光是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.46,0:17:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这张脸是…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.28,0:17:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恨的吸血鬼们
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.34,0:17:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我修特罗哈姆和德军精锐部队来做你们的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.71,0:17:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有我们史比特瓦根特别科学战斗队
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.11,0:17:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.71,0:17:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.82,0:18:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史…史比特瓦根老爷子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.53,0:18:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 你是…纽约的史摩基
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.53,0:18:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的右脚刚好痒痒了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.83,0:18:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的身体已经修复好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.93,0:18:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吃招吧 对付吸血鬼的新式武器——
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.72,0:18:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紫外线照射装置！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.71,0:18:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功小型化可是我们史比特瓦根财团的功劳呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.02,0:18:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个男人真够自恋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.11,0:18:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.45,0:18:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 卖弄小聪明的蝼蚁们
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.87,0:18:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo哪去了 看不到他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.11,0:18:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是那么神出鬼没呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.20,0:18:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微少看两眼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.35,0:18:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就会做出惊人的行动
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.76,0:19:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你越过了那条绝对不能越过的线
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.41,0:19:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你嘴上说着堂堂正正
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.25,0:19:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上却骗了莉莎莉莎 背信诺言
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.75,0:19:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且还背叛了你的同伴瓦姆乌的意志
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.47,0:19:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这蝼蚁…不要太激昂了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.34,0:19:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达成目的才是最重要的事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.01,0:19:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿到赤石就够了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.10,0:19:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽量不费功夫 将风险最小化
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.22,0:19:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,避免不可预料的赌博
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.61,0:19:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一步一步地驱使战场上的棋子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.76,0:19:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是“真正的战斗”
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.64,0:19:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在也慢慢地踏入我陷阱中送死
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.13,0:19:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…卡兹！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.45,0:19:47.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从来没有一个人像你这样让我深深地憎恨
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.14,0:19:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憎恨？那么就来报仇好了 JoJo！
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.92,0:19:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就是一对一
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.58,0:19:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最渴望的一对一的战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.56,0:20:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼哼 莉莎莉莎只剩一口气了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.07,0:20:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 还有一口气
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.24,0:20:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我故意留着她的命 留她一口气
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.61,0:20:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得为什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.06,0:20:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个女人是我的棋子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.32,0:20:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo 这是为了解决你的一个棋子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.57,0:20:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个混蛋…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.01,0:20:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我用绳子把两只脚串起来了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.47,0:20:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo 知道我为什么要这样做吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.01,0:20:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是——
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.34,0:20:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莎莉莎！
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.01,0:20:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢呀 掉下去就可当不成棋子了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.55,0:20:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不抓紧绳子的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.11,0:20:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就要撞上地面香消玉殒了 JoJo！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.67,0:21:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,Jo…JoJo！莉莎莉莎！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.69,0:21:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莎莉莎？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.47,0:21:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莎莉莎就是…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.11,0:21:14.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾莉娜奶奶说的轮船事故上救回来养育的婴儿？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.59,0:21:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那…那么她就是…JoJo的…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.25,0:21:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在已经无法走开一步
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.99,0:21:26.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是真正的战斗 JoJo
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.33,0:21:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我卡兹只需要一步步走过去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.22,0:21:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将不能行动的你斩杀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.43,0:21:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋…卡兹… 人渣！
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.81,0:21:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,JoJo不知道啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.55,0:21:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女人是他的母亲
Comment: 0,0:00:01.55,0:00:01.55,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,========Ending========
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.76,0:22:09.08,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}I'll be the roundabout
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.37,0:22:12.97,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}The words will make you out 'n' out
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.98,0:22:18.30,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}I spend the day your way
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.30,0:22:25.56,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}Call it morning driving thru the sound and in and out the valley
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.85,0:22:36.14,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}The music dance and sing
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.47,0:22:39.98,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}They make the children really ring
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.03,0:22:45.43,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}I spend the day your way
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.43,0:22:52.00,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}Call it morning driving thru the sound and in and out the valley
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.00,0:22:54.66,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}In and around the lake
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.71,0:22:59.82,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}Mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.79,0:23:06.58,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.21,0:23:13.01,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.70,0:23:22.25,EDE,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(400,400)\be1}Twenty four before my love you'll see I'll be there with you
Comment: 0,0:00:01.35,0:00:01.35,*Default,,0000,0000,0000,,========Trailer========
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.47,0:23:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,690)\fad(0,300)}还没解决完那些吸血鬼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.67,0:23:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,690)\fad(300,300)}我只想轻轻松松送你归西
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.26,0:23:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,690)\fad(300,300)}这把火就是一个赌注！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.54,0:23:36.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,690)\fad(300,300)}这孩子…唯有这个孩子…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.34,0:23:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,690)\fad(300,300)}住手 修特罗哈姆！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.53,0:23:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,690)\fad(300,300)}糟糕！
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.43,0:23:41.44,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\i1\be4\pos(640,560)}第24话 「连系JOJO的羁绊」