[Script Info]
; This is an Advanced Sub Station Alpha v4+ script.
; For Sub Station Alpha info and downloads,
; go to http://www.eswat.demon.co.uk/
; or email kotus@eswat.demon.co.uk
; 
; Advanced Sub Station Alpha script format developed by #Anime-Fansubs@EfNET
; http://www.anime-fansubs.org
; 
; For additional info and downloads go to http://vobsub.edensrising.com/
; or email gabest@freemail.hu
; 
; Note: This file was saved by Subresync.
; 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX:1920
PlayResY:1080
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Arial Unicode MS,90,&H00ffffff,&Hf0000000,&H00000000,&H40000000,-1,0,0,0,100,108,1,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,12,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.76,0:00:06.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,塔奇克馬式的日常生活
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.07,0:00:08.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什麼!?那個詹姆森社長
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.47,0:24:41.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,來反擊了?
