[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2014-12-28 22:45:52
; // 版本: 0.77
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title: TamakoMarket-MOVIE
Original Script:华盟字幕社
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:1280
PlayResY:720
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H001F1F1F,&H001F1F1F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,10,1
Style: zhushi,方正准圆_GBK,38,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,10,134
Style: Default2,方正准圆_GBK,42,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H001F1F1F,&H001F1F1F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,45,1
Style: ED_JP,DFPHSGothic-W5,33,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: OP_JP,DFPHSGothic-W5,36,&H00EFEFEF,&H000000FF,&H00233B5C,&H00000000,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,10,10,10,1
Style: title2,方正超粗黑_GBK,108,&H009F57E7,&H009F57E7,&H009F57E7,&H90000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,15,5,4,10,10,10,1
Style: title1,方正超粗黑_GBK,108,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H80000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,4,10,10,10,1
Style: Note,方正细珊瑚_GBK,45,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H001F1F1F,&H001F1F1F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,2,30,30,10,1
Style: title,方正宋黑_GBK,46,&H00EFEFEF,&H000000FF,&H009F57E7,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OP_CN,方正黑体_GBK,42,&H00EFEFEF,&H000000FF,&H00233B5C,&H00000000,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: ED_CN,方正黑体_GBK,40,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,3,0,2,10,10,8,1
Style: staff,微软雅黑,34,&H00FFFFFF,&HFF000000,&H20000000,&H00666666,0,0,0,0,100,105,0,0.00,1,3,0,8,30,30,2,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.63,0:00:41.21,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(1000,0)}南方小島的小蒂拉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.60,0:00:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡是某座南方小島
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.61,0:00:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村莊雖小  但物產頗豐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.04,0:00:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,720)}侍奉於正統王室的我  叫做蒂拉•莫奇馬茲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.78,0:00:56.45,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,590)}蒂拉•莫奇馬茲
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.41,0:00:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一隻能占善蔔  能說會道  廣受歡迎的蓋世神鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.72,0:00:59.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用力  敲下去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.98,0:01:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用力  敲下去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.13,0:01:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以稍微休息一下嗎  蒂拉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.92,0:01:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙就是從小受我照顧的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.02,0:01:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,720)}我國王子  梅查•莫奇馬茲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.13,0:01:11.45,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,590)}梅查•莫奇馬茲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.94,0:01:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是掌管我國占卜大業
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.83,0:01:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,720)}並且照顧著王子的  喬伊•莫奇馬茲 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.37,0:01:18.79,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,590)}喬伊•莫奇馬茲
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.16,0:01:22.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舂年糕還真是不輕鬆啊  蒂拉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.93,0:01:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王子你舂年糕的時候根本就沒有用上腰的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.35,0:01:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒂拉  你這樣對王子太無禮了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.20,0:01:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我失言了  喬伊大人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.74,0:01:33.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因為你總是懶懶散散地吃著年糕
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.05,0:01:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才會肥成這種傻樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.95,0:01:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這麼肥真是太抱歉了  喬伊大人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.08,0:01:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且舂好的年糕要記得分享給別人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.13,0:01:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟宮裡的各位也很期待呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.20,0:01:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王子  接下來換喬伊來舂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.48,0:01:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不必了  喬伊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.13,0:01:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  舂年糕是力氣活
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.40,0:01:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓王子做
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.53,0:01:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都說了  你對王子說話這是什麼態度
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.89,0:01:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  喬伊大人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.59,0:01:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必在意  喬伊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.46,0:02:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點口渴了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.46,0:02:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去拿點喝的來
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.33,0:02:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王子  讓喬伊拿來給您吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.86,0:02:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喬伊大人你得負責捏好年糕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.17,0:02:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別故作姿態指指點點
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.86,0:02:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,區區一隻小鳥  趕緊閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.17,0:02:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我一言  喬伊大人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.80,0:02:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能飛的鳥只是鳥而已  而能說話的鳥可是十分寶貴的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.36,0:02:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.71,0:02:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.27,0:02:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我去了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.95,0:02:25.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.20,0:02:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在  兔子山商店街的各位正寂寞著吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.08,0:02:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟我不在了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.82,0:02:44.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史織小姐她們也是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.22,0:02:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這麼聒噪的臭鳥終於離開了  他們大概也鬆了一口氣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.98,0:02:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實繼續在那家年糕店裡待一段時間也沒關係的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.80,0:02:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了尋找王子的後妃而踏上旅途的我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.80,0:03:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因機緣巧合而陷入麻煩的商店街年糕店
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.57,0:03:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那個地方  有一位名叫玉子的女孩…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.59,0:03:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「不要離開我  小蒂拉」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.57,0:03:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「姑娘  不要阻止我  我現在必須回去」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.81,0:03:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「諸位島民正在翹首企盼我的歸來啊」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.59,0:03:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「我明白了  小蒂拉  雖然有點寂寞  不過你要加油哦」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.74,0:03:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「這是長在最好的地方的羽毛」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.72,0:03:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「就把它當做是我  去做出好吃的年糕吧」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.06,0:03:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「謝謝你  我會珍藏它的  小蒂拉」
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.45,0:03:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然喬伊大人說她就是後妃人選的時候讓我吃了一驚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.22,0:03:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但其實是徹頭徹尾的估算錯誤
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.39,0:03:42.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給她添了麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.02,0:03:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望他們最近還好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.39,0:03:49.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來  捏年糕吧  蒂拉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.62,0:03:55.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老是做成一種形狀真是沒意思啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.38,0:03:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試著做一點帶有原創性的年糕…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.64,0:03:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喬伊大人  這種怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.55,0:04:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這算什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.78,0:04:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桃形年糕
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.35,0:04:05.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桃…桃？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.26,0:04:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喬伊大人  難道你原本以為這是臀部嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.66,0:04:10.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.77,0:04:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.16,0:04:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的如何
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.38,0:04:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我收斂一點
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.86,0:04:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒂拉  你在戲弄我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.82,0:04:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿來了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.37,0:04:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王子  您不能看
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.40,0:04:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王子  你看看這個怎麼樣
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.23,0:04:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.29,0:04:30.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢噢  真不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.53,0:04:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…錯？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.42,0:04:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個年糕？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.81,0:04:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜歡哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.43,0:04:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王子您也喜歡這種樣子的東西？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.91,0:04:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我很喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.35,0:04:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.72,0:04:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是蒂拉年糕吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.61,0:04:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.37,0:04:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別做這種容易招人誤會的玩意！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.85,0:04:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身為蓋世神鳥卻不知為何總是一副慘澹模樣的我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.80,0:05:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忍耐之後終能見藍天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.88,0:05:46.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想幹什麼  你這混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.09,0:05:55.68,title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(360,530)\fad(1000,0)}玉子愛情故事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.70,0:05:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你家的年糕太黏了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.66,0:06:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你家的明顯勁道不足啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.88,0:06:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.45,0:06:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爹在那邊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.52,0:06:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.89,0:06:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爹  你也住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.20,0:06:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴  我兒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.55,0:06:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我一定要和你決出勝負
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.04,0:06:11.17,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某座城市裡的商店街
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.84,0:06:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝惠顧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.11,0:06:13.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎光臨
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.28,0:06:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來嘗嘗吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.26,0:06:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這座雖然小  卻又不失熱鬧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.50,0:06:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像在舉辦祭典一樣的城市裡
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.52,0:06:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從出生開始就門當戶對
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.82,0:06:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同樣是年糕店的兒子和女兒
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.94,0:06:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.00,0:07:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我覺得大概誰都沒注意到
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.88,0:07:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對這位青梅竹馬的女孩子…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.66,0:07:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了份…戀意…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.22,0:07:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拿好了  餅藏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.62,0:07:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請講
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.38,0:09:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是這樣的話我說不出口
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.71,0:09:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我轉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.21,0:09:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.07,0:10:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.13,0:10:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道為什麼總是接不住東西
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.59,0:10:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是為什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.50,0:10:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要拼命去抓住它就能接住了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.81,0:10:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.46,0:10:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.58,0:10:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜讀完畢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.10,0:10:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打攪了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.77,0:10:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  那麼今天的練習就到此結束
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.88,0:10:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.92,0:10:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛苦了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.94,0:10:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.01,0:10:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神菜？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.26,0:10:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,STOP
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.01,0:10:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉遲到了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.38,0:10:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後  我有話說
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.68,0:10:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請講  牧野同學
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.23,0:10:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然事出突然  我有一個重大提案
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.24,0:10:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.11,0:11:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實我從很久以前就在心底埋藏了一個野心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.22,0:11:03.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神菜你該不會還想做社團社長吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.62,0:11:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那當然  能做自然想做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.20,0:11:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不是那件事情
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.57,0:11:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我掏我掏我掏
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.13,0:11:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想參加這個
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.49,0:11:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兔子山巡遊音樂節
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.57,0:11:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,申請的截止日期就是這個月底
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.18,0:11:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是突然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.84,0:11:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先我們什麼都沒準備
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.28,0:11:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我們也沒有能出場這種節日大賽的水準吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.72,0:11:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然好像很有趣  但很快就是商店街的祭典了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.66,0:11:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得做出新的糕餅才行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.31,0:11:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.68,0:11:36.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想創造回憶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.26,0:11:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回憶？
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.34,0:11:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夏天之前我們也要引退了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.88,0:11:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這之前  一起創造屬於我們舞棒社的回憶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.94,0:11:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  好高
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.65,0:11:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請給我這個社長…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.63,0:11:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留下回憶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.98,0:11:54.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神菜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.05,0:11:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是社長
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.37,0:12:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算就這麼捏著糕餅給自己的青春畫上句號嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.25,0:12:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.05,0:12:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.89,0:12:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糕餅你可以捏一輩子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.87,0:12:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們舞棒社的青春  只屬於當下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.96,0:12:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉  還有  小綠
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.79,0:12:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是有熱情啊…神菜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.15,0:12:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這也不錯  嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.84,0:12:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位如何
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.22,0:12:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.22,0:12:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想做
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.46,0:12:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社長
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.35,0:12:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.27,0:12:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就決定了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.91,0:12:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.76,0:12:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧無所謂了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.31,0:12:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  還有一個月
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.76,0:12:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位齊心協力一起奮鬥吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.54,0:12:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.67,0:12:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順帶一提  這是申請書
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.00,0:12:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠你能去把它交上去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.65,0:12:40.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.67,0:12:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子  你接棒這方面還要多多努力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.11,0:12:44.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.84,0:12:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得努力才行
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.11,0:12:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿咻
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.93,0:12:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.23,0:12:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你突然做些什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.69,0:13:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是有點太硬了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.16,0:13:01.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼硬
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.16,0:13:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在構思「屁屁年糕」
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.67,0:13:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子  你看看這種怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.51,0:13:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以摸嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.38,0:13:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.86,0:13:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神菜的好像很有口感的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.98,0:13:13.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為年糕你覺得怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.52,0:13:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠的你再給我摸一次
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.90,0:13:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.85,0:13:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  來嘛來嘛  真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.63,0:13:18.94,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位練習完了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.46,0:13:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史織  把你的屁屁朝著玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.74,0:13:22.76,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一次就好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.31,0:13:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？沾上了什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.89,0:13:23.41,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.99,0:13:25.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我摸摸嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.17,0:13:25.97,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.61,0:13:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能協助我家的變態糕餅妹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.40,0:13:28.47,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.89,0:13:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.47,0:13:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.37,0:13:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能用嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.88,0:14:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼說呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.41,0:14:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一句「怎麼說呢」是搞不懂你的意思的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.89,0:14:06.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真是閃閃發光
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.65,0:14:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是因為現在是春天吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.01,0:14:13.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.41,0:14:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大路  這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.12,0:14:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大學  我在考慮去那家大學的影視學專業
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.78,0:14:26.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的？
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.09,0:14:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是東京啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.66,0:14:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這樣就會和北白川同學分開了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.82,0:14:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.10,0:14:33.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不介意嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.39,0:14:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…正是因為這個我才下定決心的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.37,0:14:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決定什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.69,0:14:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒…沒什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.47,0:14:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位在畢業去向調查表上寫了什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.51,0:14:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我寫的是「玉屋」
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.13,0:14:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然準備繼承家業嗎  厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.80,0:14:57.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟玉子的腦袋裡全都是糕餅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.68,0:15:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知究竟糕餅就是她的人生  還是她的人生就是糕餅了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.69,0:15:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  將來會找個喜歡糕餅的人嗎？
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.65,0:15:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？那種事情我還沒考慮過
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.08,0:15:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史織你呢  果然是準備學英文專業嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.49,0:15:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  雖然我本來是這麼想的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.19,0:15:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但試著留學或許也不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.44,0:15:18.14,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(640,660)}Hi  Shiori,how  are  you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.80,0:15:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也不知道能不能適應那邊的生活…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.68,0:15:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史織  總之你先別無視我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.49,0:15:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  神菜
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.73,0:15:29.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,No  problem  沒問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.38,0:15:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神菜你是一心想去建築學專業的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.14,0:15:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.95,0:15:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是  畢竟家裡是做木匠活的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.76,0:15:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是其實我有點恐高
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.69,0:15:41.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.96,0:15:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事  會克服的  總有一天會的…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.61,0:15:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綠呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.16,0:15:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.14,0:15:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本來也是打算升學的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.44,0:15:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然完全沒考慮好去考哪所學校
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.39,0:15:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但大概  就在本地讀吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.76,0:16:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不繼承爺爺的玩具店嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.07,0:16:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種事情我完全不考慮啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.71,0:16:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.17,0:16:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但要是你繼承的話我們就能像以前一樣每天都能見面了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.97,0:16:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.06,0:16:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天再見
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.21,0:16:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.05,0:16:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.21,0:16:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都考慮了好多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.73,0:16:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.39,0:16:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.88,0:16:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.75,0:16:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加鹽烤著吃味道不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.00,0:16:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.01,0:16:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉  給我留十個豆沙大福
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.82,0:16:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝您的惠顧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.77,0:16:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子  歡迎回來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.09,0:16:35.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.42,0:16:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.28,0:16:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.20,0:16:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.81,0:16:50.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們舞棒社準備參加比賽了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.39,0:16:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠好像很有幹勁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.00,0:16:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎  那還真是不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.72,0:16:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薰先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.77,0:16:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.38,0:16:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請給我一束
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.76,0:16:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.04,0:17:11.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.14,0:17:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎光臨
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.03,0:17:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道小蒂拉現在過的好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.18,0:17:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知不覺
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.11,0:17:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我居然也到三年級了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.71,0:17:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺好像很多事情都在變化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.72,0:17:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日總會與昨日有所不同  因此今天才會如此美妙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.49,0:17:52.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也帶有些許寂寞
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.03,0:17:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這份寂寞將會一天天變得厚重
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.93,0:18:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咖啡也是一樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.82,0:18:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好苦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.76,0:18:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,牛奶
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.11,0:18:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏  歡迎回來
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.10,0:18:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.07,0:18:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.69,0:18:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.40,0:18:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為贈禮的永遠愛你糕  做八十個沒錯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.76,0:18:36.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  永遠愛你糕  八十個
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.59,0:18:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.86,0:18:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.58,0:18:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別在意  吾平過段時間也會放棄的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.71,0:18:53.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得這個決定不錯  去東京讀書
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.54,0:18:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更重要的是  你對玉子說了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.47,0:18:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼…我又不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.79,0:19:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好對她坦白比較好哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.83,0:19:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.32,0:19:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.23,0:19:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我也決定了要對她說的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.75,0:19:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.12,0:20:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.49,0:20:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,子…子…子…子…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.94,0:20:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.24,0:20:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少先告訴她  我要去東京的大學
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.30,0:20:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  要是玉子接住了紙杯電話的話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.48,0:20:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個時候  那個時候…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.34,0:20:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住了  明明一百次大概只能接住一次的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.70,0:20:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是厲害  玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.04,0:20:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉…玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.53,0:20:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…我…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.86,0:20:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.60,0:20:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.14,0:20:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大餅  我是餡兒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.24,0:20:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不是姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.57,0:20:42.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  為…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.53,0:20:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為為為為什麼餡兒你會在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.19,0:20:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請講
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.08,0:20:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在這裡也沒什麼吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.07,0:20:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自動鉛筆沒筆芯了  我過來拿的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.23,0:20:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都斷了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.23,0:20:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是  自動鉛筆的筆芯是很容易折斷的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.68,0:20:58.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.84,0:21:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  反正我的心也折了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.63,0:21:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏  吃飯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.84,0:21:23.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.89,0:21:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天早上去學校的時候  總之先把大學的事情說了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.92,0:21:25.30,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開動了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.91,0:21:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那時先打個招呼  告訴她我有話要說
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.03,0:21:34.20,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.05,0:21:42.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後果然還是用紙杯電話來…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.56,0:21:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.38,0:21:47.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子  你好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.42,0:21:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在做什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.67,0:21:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,據說你剛才把紙杯電話扔過來了？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.01,0:21:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.19,0:21:55.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也該用手機聯繫了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.24,0:22:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說  那個紙杯電話可是聯繫心與心的重要…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.33,0:22:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  餅藏
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.64,0:22:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.53,0:22:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天早上開始
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.47,0:22:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要開始舞棒的晨練了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.66,0:22:11.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們決定要出場下個月的節日大賽
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.66,0:22:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是厲害  加油
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.01,0:22:15.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.72,0:22:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要為我加油哦  餅藏
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.10,0:22:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不就是說早上搭不上話了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.82,0:22:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餡兒  進去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.50,0:22:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.26,0:22:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說  餡兒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.39,0:22:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.73,0:22:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我終於開始製作屁屁年糕了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.69,0:22:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那種怪年糕  反正肯定又會被爸爸否決掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.09,0:22:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.74,0:22:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我把年糕串成念珠的那種念珠年糕呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.93,0:22:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爺爺奶奶會不會開心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.42,0:22:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  姐姐你還真是姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.76,0:22:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先走了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.20,0:23:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餡子  你對我再溫柔一點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.19,0:23:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一點點就好  什麼的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.36,0:23:08.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還戴著隱形眼鏡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.53,0:23:10.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天一天沒問題的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.54,0:23:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.80,0:23:12.87,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.30,0:23:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波濤洶湧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.95,0:23:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年糕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.99,0:23:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餡子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.80,0:23:24.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.62,0:23:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做胸部年糕怎麼樣  會不會很受歡迎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.78,0:23:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.54,0:23:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  姐姐你在說什麼啦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.77,0:23:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餡兒  我可是認真的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.69,0:23:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用牛皮糖試著做做吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.15,0:23:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟做得軟一點會比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.08,0:23:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.17,0:23:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餡兒？你泡暖了沒
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.19,0:23:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給  餅藏
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.60,0:23:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.79,0:23:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.74,0:23:52.87,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別感冒咯
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.05,0:23:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是不好好告訴玉子的話  她是不會明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.61,0:24:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.73,0:24:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,節日大賽的參加手續已經完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.27,0:24:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先決定一下曲目吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.03,0:24:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把大家列出來的候補曲目都剪輯出來了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.21,0:24:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之先聽聽吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.71,0:24:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大路
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.55,0:24:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.48,0:24:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說  大路
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.27,0:24:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.15,0:24:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說了？
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.75,0:24:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼意思
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.98,0:24:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還沒嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.79,0:24:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.10,0:24:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.80,0:24:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以說  你們在說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.00,0:24:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事  什麼都沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.91,0:24:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  你們很吵
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.52,0:24:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.61,0:24:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.60,0:24:48.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常盤她真是可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.07,0:24:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是據說被常盤罵過的人有很多
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.78,0:24:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能理解
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.95,0:24:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是寶貴的經驗
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.20,0:24:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的  你們很吵耶
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.21,0:25:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.23,0:25:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲呵
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.22,0:25:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.83,0:25:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠  我去上個廁所
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.57,0:25:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,OK  我幫你拿東西
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.73,0:25:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.90,0:25:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.74,0:25:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正準備去練習？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.77,0:25:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大路啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.74,0:25:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還真是好懂
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.32,0:25:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼意思？
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.73,0:26:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概  玉子會為這種事情困擾的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.33,0:26:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.59,0:26:08.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今為止  玉子和大路一次都沒有同班過吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.65,0:26:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  我沒想到你居然會這麼誇張
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.59,0:26:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.51,0:26:17.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直在盯著玉子看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.64,0:26:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才沒有一直盯著呢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.49,0:26:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是偶爾掃一眼她正好走進我的視線而已
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.07,0:26:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有在看啊  盯得很厲害呢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.46,0:26:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過…
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.52,0:26:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也就是看看而已了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.24,0:26:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大路你就一直這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.18,0:26:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至今為止  從今往後也永遠只是在玉子周圍打轉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.90,0:26:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不會呢
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.26,0:26:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我準備去東京的大學
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.00,0:26:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我是打算好好和玉子說的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.69,0:26:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什麼  這和常盤你沒關係
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.17,0:26:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算什麼時候說
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.10,0:26:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包剪錘
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.51,0:26:57.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,輸了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.33,0:26:58.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼時候說
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.15,0:26:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在今天…
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.50,0:27:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常盤  你這傢伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.98,0:27:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算…今天說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.49,0:27:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這不是害我一口氣都說出來了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.71,0:27:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  這不是餅藏嗎  你怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.68,0:27:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒能來得及走進廁所嗎  真是可憐
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.49,0:27:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子  大路他有話對你說
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.33,0:27:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼  什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.51,0:27:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算送我點什麼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.99,0:27:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他說他打算今天說
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.67,0:27:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是說一定就在今天…
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.16,0:27:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才你這麼說了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.38,0:27:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常盤  你這個該死的河童頭
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.57,0:27:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼在練習結束以後再說行嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.50,0:27:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏你也有影視研究會的活動吧  結束以後一起回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.82,0:27:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  一起回
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.37,0:27:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  回頭見  餅藏
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.57,0:27:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  嗯  回頭見
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.29,0:27:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天…就是今天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.50,0:27:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.95,0:27:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點自我嫌惡
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.95,0:28:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺有點討厭自己
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.65,0:28:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.99,0:28:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是連著小綠那份一起喜歡小綠的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.61,0:28:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.38,0:28:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.37,0:28:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.19,0:28:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.50,0:28:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.00,0:28:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.14,0:28:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大路
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.42,0:28:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有沒有什麼能幫上忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.14,0:28:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是有什麼事的話  希望你隨時都能來找我們幫忙
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.45,0:28:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你們  我很開心
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.62,0:28:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們永遠都是同伴  不論是曾經  還是從今往後
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.12,0:28:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以小指發誓
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.07,0:28:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發誓
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.22,0:28:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開個玩笑  開個玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.20,0:28:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶不帶感  帶不帶感？
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.78,0:29:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超帶感的  很棒很棒
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.85,0:29:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛剛這個是不是應該錄下來的
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.56,0:29:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.76,0:29:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請進
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.56,0:29:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打擾了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.14,0:29:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉…玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.40,0:29:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北白川同學
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.94,0:29:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來接你了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.02,0:29:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像我這邊結束得比較早
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.54,0:29:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們好
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.46,0:29:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.06,0:29:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在外頭等著
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.08,0:29:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不論發生了什麼  明天都一定要來學校哦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.19,0:29:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.70,0:29:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什麼事要說  是關於商店街的事情嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.27,0:29:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  不是的…
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.72,0:29:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,店子的事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.55,0:29:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是…
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.25,0:29:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  糕餅的事情？
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.98,0:29:49.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是糕餅啦
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.85,0:29:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什麼  又要拍電影嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.61,0:29:57.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  也不算…不是糕餅
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.61,0:29:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實在要說也算是糕餅
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.26,0:30:01.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏？
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.40,0:30:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  就是餅藏的…我的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.36,0:30:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跳石啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.52,0:30:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小時候經常在上面跳來跳去
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.21,0:30:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏經常在那裡嚇唬我來著…
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.27,0:30:28.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  你要說什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.57,0:30:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.61,0:30:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要說餅藏的事情來著
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.60,0:30:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個不錯  胸部年糕就是這種感覺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.69,0:30:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽我說  之前我去澡堂的時候看見一個超大的胸部…
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.69,0:30:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該聊餅藏的事情來著  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.88,0:30:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…沒事…
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.42,0:31:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.66,0:31:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.59,0:31:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要說的事呢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.35,0:31:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經無所謂了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.07,0:31:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.11,0:31:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.16,0:31:23.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  你不過來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.96,0:31:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏  你覺得這塊石頭像不像我家的豆沙大福
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.48,0:31:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.69,0:31:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.91,0:31:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個  年糕這東西  雖然很小  但卻能讓很多人感到幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.67,0:31:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我長得比年糕大了這麼多倍  卻還完全比不上它
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.09,0:31:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼軟
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.47,0:31:58.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼白  那麼溫柔
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.52,0:32:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還很香
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.11,0:32:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又熱熱的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.31,0:32:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道自己能不能成為那樣的人
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.63,0:32:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得我行嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.66,0:32:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  好像總是在聊我自己的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.71,0:32:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.03,0:32:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要摔下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.22,0:32:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.56,0:32:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.00,0:32:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你  嚇死我了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.92,0:32:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏你拉了我一把呢  和小時候不一樣了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.75,0:33:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏？
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.43,0:33:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.54,0:33:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我啊  準備去東京的大學
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.34,0:33:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,東京…？
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.49,0:33:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在考慮  我想好好學學影像這方面的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.89,0:33:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  在這之前
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.34,0:33:24.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想先好好地說出  自己的心意
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.95,0:33:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.49,0:33:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.10,0:33:30.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  喜歡玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.81,0:33:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我特別喜歡玉子  所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.10,0:33:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  餅藏  你在說什…
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.68,0:33:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.26,0:33:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.00,0:33:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不勝感激
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.51,0:34:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不勝感激
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.89,0:34:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小女子先行告辭了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.10,0:34:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.35,0:34:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼來著
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.04,0:34:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才餅藏對我說了什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.02,0:34:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後我又回答了什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.65,0:34:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏他…說了…
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.95,0:34:42.91,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.94,0:34:45.24,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉  歡迎回來
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.44,0:34:46.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉？
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.71,0:34:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.05,0:34:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都濕透了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.11,0:34:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子  歡迎回…
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.20,0:35:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎麼了？
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.77,0:35:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  這不是濕透了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.97,0:35:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  餡兒  拿塊毛巾來
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.53,0:35:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去燒洗澡水  等下記得去洗哦
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.61,0:35:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不勝感激
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.47,0:35:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐你在說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.49,0:35:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在躲什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.15,0:35:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  隱形眼鏡弄丟了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.88,0:36:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐  鍋子燒焦了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.57,0:36:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是難以置信
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.81,0:36:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.84,0:36:31.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這算什麼菜  簡直難以置信
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.76,0:36:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這煮的是年糕吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.25,0:36:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.67,0:36:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說的是年糕啦
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.14,0:36:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說來  明天要送去吉田家一百個年糕
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.21,0:36:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一百個餅藏對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.70,0:36:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒？這傢伙在胡言亂語什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.21,0:36:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吃飽了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.38,0:36:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  餡兒你就吃飽了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.55,0:36:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要我去給你烤幾個餅藏
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.49,0:36:53.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常不想要
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.29,0:36:55.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.63,0:36:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爺爺  給我醬油
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.53,0:37:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿去
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.68,0:37:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.78,0:37:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請進
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.70,0:37:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餡兒  你去洗澡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.73,0:37:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.83,0:37:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦  書包為什麼會在這種地方
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.74,0:37:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好像是大餅拿來的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.20,0:37:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好疼
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.36,0:37:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說真的  你怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.54,0:37:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒了？你的臉好紅
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.50,0:37:33.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  或許是感冒了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.08,0:37:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天記得早點睡哦
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.67,0:37:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.68,0:38:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞砸了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.09,0:38:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿咻
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.88,0:38:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.06,0:38:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.25,0:38:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我睡迷糊了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.53,0:38:28.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是感冒了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.06,0:38:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去睡吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.24,0:38:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必了  我很健康
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.64,0:38:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要做幾個柏葉餅藏來著
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.79,0:38:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這噁心的糕餅算什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.90,0:38:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柏葉餅要做五十個
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.23,0:38:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祭典用的紅白餅藏也該開始做了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.89,0:38:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不吉利  你這傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.00,0:38:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.20,0:38:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把糕餅全都說成餅藏了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.21,0:39:03.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糕餅…
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.17,0:39:07.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我果然還是在感冒
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.54,0:39:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二  三  四  二  二  三  四  三  二  接著
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.72,0:39:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉身投棒
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.59,0:39:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.16,0:39:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.61,0:39:25.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後最後的最後用一個用魔術收場
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.75,0:39:27.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備表演魔術嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.19,0:39:28.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然要做
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.34,0:39:29.27,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉身投棒
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.47,0:39:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉身投棒
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.62,0:39:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉轉轉轉轉轉轉…
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.65,0:39:37.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看見了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.27,0:39:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我接
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.78,0:39:42.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是神菜  一接一個准
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.72,0:39:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是有在計算角度的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.17,0:39:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  真的嗎  好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.13,0:39:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神菜  抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.72,0:39:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.18,0:39:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有注意過平衡點嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.24,0:39:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是有吧…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.41,0:39:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我直言
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.39,0:40:03.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉接不住棒子應該和你平時甚少注意平衡點有關係
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.74,0:40:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它在棒底和棒頭的這個位置上
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.12,0:40:12.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後就是下落時的角度
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.95,0:40:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了　小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.64,0:40:18.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棒頭看上去好像是糕餅一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.74,0:40:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愧是變態糕餅妹
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.09,0:40:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能把這個看成糕餅的世上真的只有你一個了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.62,0:40:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好　多注意一下手型
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.12,0:40:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.40,0:40:32.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靈活的運用下手腕
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.04,0:40:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.62,0:40:35.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼放學見
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.06,0:40:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回見啊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.61,0:40:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.34,0:40:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.27,0:40:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.65,0:40:41.86,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.00,0:40:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好玩
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.48,0:40:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什麼啊　玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.47,0:40:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔  魔術的練習
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.43,0:40:52.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不要搞啦
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.74,0:40:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什麼啦你
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.00,0:41:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無聊之日，枯坐硯前，心中不由雜想紛呈　
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.00,0:41:05.31,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs-3\an8}摘自《徒然草》 卜部兼好  原文序段 つれずれなるままに、ひぐらし、すずりにむかいて、\Nこころにうつりゆくよしなしごとを、そこはかとなくかきつくれば
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.56,0:41:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天  有遇到什麼事了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.52,0:41:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼都沒有哦
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.96,0:41:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼都沒
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.86,0:41:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.75,0:41:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.04,0:41:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.42,0:41:37.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.58,0:41:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲呵
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.51,0:41:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺和平時不太一樣呢
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.08,0:41:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒！沒什麼不一樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.74,0:41:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從小玉的便當裡散發出的這股違和感
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.51,0:41:56.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎喲居然沒有糕餅
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.61,0:42:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說起來  玉子的便當平時都有放大福之類的在裡面呢
Dialogue: 0,0:42:01.58,0:42:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忘記放進去了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.28,0:42:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個變態糕餅妹居然會忘記把糕餅放裡面
Dialogue: 0,0:42:07.23,0:42:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是何等的大事 大事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:42:11.91,0:42:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微 對糕餅有些抵觸
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.65,0:42:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 經歷低谷了是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.11,0:42:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,低谷？
Dialogue: 0,0:42:19.28,0:42:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糕點低谷？
Dialogue: 0,0:42:20.72,0:42:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不說這個其實我遇到過釘子低谷
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.93,0:42:28.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小學的時候我練習釘釘子練過了頭
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.62,0:42:31.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,導致我對所有金屬的銅臭味產生了過敏
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.76,0:42:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吐
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.80,0:42:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事情做過頭都不好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.02,0:42:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子你是不是糕餅做得太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.96,0:42:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本來玉子對糕餅就不太喜歡呢
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.47,0:42:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.10,0:42:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小時候的事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:42:48.75,0:42:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:42:50.59,0:42:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年糕店的白雞蛋  北白川玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.83,0:42:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年糕店的白雞蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.00,0:42:57.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白雞蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:42:58.09,0:42:59.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是老套
Dialogue: 0,0:42:59.91,0:43:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩個人都好可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.08,0:43:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼那麼 是因為什麼才喜歡上糕餅的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.09,0:43:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 在我很沮喪的時候 糕餅說話了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.46,0:43:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要哭啦
Dialogue: 0,0:43:17.05,0:43:18.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多數是 我爸爸他
Dialogue: 0,0:43:19.57,0:43:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是個好故事
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.63,0:43:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是現在卻陷入了糕餅低谷
Dialogue: 0,0:43:24.12,0:43:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,低谷  這只有用堅強的心去克服了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.21,0:43:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒  也不至於到那種地步
Dialogue: 0,0:43:31.66,0:43:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是稍稍有點像感冒那種的
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.33,0:43:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒？
Dialogue: 0,0:43:35.50,0:43:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過些時候會好的
Dialogue: 0,0:43:37.20,0:43:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢
Dialogue: 0,0:43:38.37,0:43:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 不要太憋著
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.41,0:43:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:43:42.36,0:43:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順帶一提 我克服釘子低谷用得是反治法
Dialogue: 0,0:43:46.95,0:43:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天天把釘子帶在身上一直去聞那股味道
Dialogue: 0,0:43:49.64,0:43:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺飯都要變得有銅臭味了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.71,0:43:59.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這場獨立戰爭是圍繞處在奧斯曼帝國統治下的希臘展開的…
Dialogue: 0,0:44:01.37,0:44:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爺爺 為什麼我們家是做年糕的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:44:04.57,0:44:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為爺爺的爺爺就是年糕店啊
Dialogue: 0,0:44:08.49,0:44:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事情我知道啦
Dialogue: 0,0:44:11.11,0:44:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是為什麼會是年糕啊
Dialogue: 0,0:44:13.15,0:44:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼又在說這種莫名其妙的話了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:16.39,0:44:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了 玉子 在哭嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.71,0:44:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏欺負我
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.19,0:44:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為玉子小公主這麼的可愛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:44:29.35,0:44:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小可愛 小可愛 玉子小公主
Dialogue: 0,0:44:32.07,0:44:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為餅藏最喜歡玉子了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:44:35.92,0:44:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在雅克•拉菲特和路易•菲力浦等人領導下  發動了這場平民起義
Dialogue: 0,0:44:35.92,0:44:42.10,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}法國二月革命
Dialogue: 0,0:44:42.46,0:44:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有在七月…
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.92,0:44:47.24,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:45:03.20,0:45:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎光臨 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:45:04.76,0:45:06.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一會兒再過來
Dialogue: 0,0:45:07.59,0:45:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:45:09.08,0:45:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:11.59,0:45:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:45:12.72,0:45:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小百合姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:45:14.08,0:45:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉你好有精神 一直想見你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:45:16.84,0:45:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上我去「兔湯」看你
Dialogue: 0,0:45:18.18,0:45:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  一會兒見
Dialogue: 0,0:45:28.02,0:45:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉  歡迎回來
Dialogue: 0,0:45:35.00,0:45:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  玉子  送的這個  你要不要吃
Dialogue: 0,0:45:38.20,0:45:39.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  你等等
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.11,0:45:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有用堅強的心去克服了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:45.27,0:45:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心
Dialogue: 0,0:45:46.68,0:45:48.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用堅強的心去克服
Dialogue: 0,0:45:49.16,0:45:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用堅強的心去克服
Dialogue: 0,0:45:51.54,0:45:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 對不住啊餅藏 多謝
Dialogue: 0,0:45:56.97,0:45:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燙死啦這玩意兒
Dialogue: 0,0:45:58.50,0:46:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這東西真是百吃不厭啊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:00.70,0:46:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝啦 我還會再來的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:06.92,0:46:09.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏 再拿一塊去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:46:11.34,0:46:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒好了沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:46:12.82,0:46:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  靠毅力克服了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:15.35,0:46:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝 
Dialogue: 0,0:46:16.74,0:46:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安
Dialogue: 0,0:46:17.79,0:46:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多謝
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.00,0:46:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大爺 謝…啊 玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:46:21.64,0:46:22.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是大餅啊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:22.97,0:46:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲 你可安好 餅藏 我很好 再見啊
Dialogue: 0,0:47:24.95,0:47:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好 今天真早啊
Dialogue: 0,0:47:27.36,0:47:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:47:29.05,0:47:29.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:47:30.24,0:47:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:47:31.16,0:47:32.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你休息一會兒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:47:33.49,0:47:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身體還沒好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:47:35.28,0:47:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暫時不用幫店裡做事了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:38.46,0:47:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萬一受傷了也不好
Dialogue: 0,0:47:41.24,0:47:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你 在雛子…你媽去世之後還從來沒在這時候休息過吧
Dialogue: 0,0:47:47.50,0:47:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶爾歇一下也可以
Dialogue: 0,0:47:50.86,0:47:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就聽你的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:47:55.21,0:47:56.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你 爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:48:23.43,0:48:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:48:26.64,0:48:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:48:28.14,0:48:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起的挺早啊 出來散步嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.42,0:48:33.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦？ 小玉 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:48:34.79,0:48:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉 早上好 今天會是個好天哦
Dialogue: 0,0:48:41.36,0:48:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:48:43.18,0:48:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起的很早嘛 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:48:46.56,0:48:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:48:48.68,0:48:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早安
Dialogue: 0,0:48:50.58,0:48:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:48:54.95,0:48:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都和平時一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:48:57.11,0:48:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,beautiful day
Dialogue: 0,0:49:00.55,0:49:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和平時一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:49:06.02,0:49:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,平時的話…
Dialogue: 0,0:49:07.51,0:49:09.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子 早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:49:54.53,0:49:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1 2 3
Dialogue: 0,0:50:10.11,0:50:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠
Dialogue: 0,0:50:12.53,0:50:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還是不能好好的接住舞棒 還有…
Dialogue: 0,0:50:18.40,0:50:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大路？
Dialogue: 0,0:50:37.37,0:50:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠
Dialogue: 0,0:50:40.49,0:50:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能聽我說嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:50:45.96,0:50:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏 說要去東京的大學
Dialogue: 0,0:50:50.49,0:50:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:50:56.71,0:51:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前 餅藏說有事要找我談的那天
Dialogue: 0,0:51:01.69,0:51:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被餅藏 表白了
Dialogue: 0,0:51:05.68,0:51:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:51:08.04,0:51:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去和平時的他完全不一樣 我嚇了一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:51:14.29,0:51:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後來小綠你問起我的時候我又說什麼都沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:51:20.60,0:51:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:51:31.75,0:51:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後 玉子你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:51:35.84,0:51:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道 還跑開了
Dialogue: 0,0:51:41.73,0:51:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和餅藏打一出生就一直是鄰居
Dialogue: 0,0:51:46.63,0:51:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩家又都是糕點店
Dialogue: 0,0:51:49.27,0:51:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都 無論什麼時候都一直在對方的身邊
Dialogue: 0,0:51:58.18,0:52:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起看著對方長大 我還以為我們兩個永遠不會變的
Dialogue: 0,0:52:08.40,0:52:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 餅藏他卻有好好想著自己的將來
Dialogue: 0,0:52:17.12,0:52:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像他突然離我很遙遠一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:52:20.47,0:52:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一下變得有點不知所措
Dialogue: 0,0:52:25.82,0:52:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過…
Dialogue: 0,0:52:30.32,0:52:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是覺得他想了很多 真是很了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:52:36.70,0:52:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他房間的窗戶 老是關著
Dialogue: 0,0:52:42.78,0:52:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底該怎麼辦啊
Dialogue: 0,0:52:51.04,0:52:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:52:52.89,0:52:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:52:55.78,0:52:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 看著玉子這麼悶悶不樂的樣子 
Dialogue: 0,0:52:59.07,0:53:00.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不怎麼開心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:53:04.02,0:53:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:53:09.90,0:53:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在流感很猖獗 大家多注意一下身體
Dialogue: 0,0:53:16.61,0:53:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順帶一說 我家的太太每天早中晚都有好好洗手所以身體很好
Dialogue: 0,0:53:22.99,0:53:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也因此天天能吃到美味的飯菜所以非常幸福
Dialogue: 0,0:53:51.32,0:53:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 開始練習吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:54.00,0:53:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:53:57.06,0:53:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 疼疼疼
Dialogue: 0,0:53:57.79,0:53:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:59.17,0:53:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:54:00.43,0:54:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉 還是稍微休息一下的好
Dialogue: 0,0:54:03.18,0:54:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:54:04.05,0:54:06.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大會就快到了 這時候傷到腳可不好
Dialogue: 0,0:54:14.98,0:54:16.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 玉子
Dialogue: 0,0:54:16.33,0:54:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 史織
Dialogue: 0,0:54:19.92,0:54:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,練習完成了？
Dialogue: 0,0:54:21.20,0:54:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  就我暫時出來休整下
Dialogue: 0,0:54:24.78,0:54:28.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊 我一會兒也要去上英語課外輔導了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:28.83,0:54:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 暑假的時候我要去homestay
Dialogue: 0,0:54:34.11,0:54:36.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然還沒確定要住哪一家
Dialogue: 0,0:54:39.89,0:54:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我只是覺得好了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:54:46.13,0:54:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得比起煩惱要不要留學不如先去看看再說
Dialogue: 0,0:54:49.56,0:54:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然有些不安 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:54:52.08,0:54:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都說萬事開頭難嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:54:58.75,0:54:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子？
Dialogue: 0,0:55:01.26,0:55:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感冒 還沒好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:55:12.68,0:55:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 這個禮拜天要不要久違地去看下電影
Dialogue: 0,0:55:15.82,0:55:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 一起去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:18.16,0:55:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 小玉 歡迎回來
Dialogue: 0,0:55:20.42,0:55:21.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:21.64,0:55:22.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 
Dialogue: 0,0:55:23.85,0:55:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顏見世公演的票訂到了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:23.85,0:55:25.84,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}顏見世公演：介紹歌舞伎新班子的見面會表演
Dialogue: 0,0:55:25.96,0:55:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好厲害
Dialogue: 0,0:55:27.25,0:55:28.73,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 歡迎回來 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:55:29.31,0:55:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 能稍微放會兒風嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:55:31.80,0:55:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:36.58,0:55:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斷緣糕真的不行嗎 把它吃下去就斷掉這段緣分這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:41.60,0:55:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不能想些來緣分的點子嗎 吾平
Dialogue: 0,0:55:44.96,0:55:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼嘛 我還想讓餅藏那傢伙吃下去來著
Dialogue: 0,0:55:48.35,0:55:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 小玉
Dialogue: 0,0:55:50.07,0:55:50.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來
Dialogue: 0,0:55:51.23,0:55:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.95,0:56:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 回家也說一聲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:56:06.20,0:56:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,0:56:07.34,0:56:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:08.98,0:56:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想 其實大家也經歷了不少呢
Dialogue: 0,0:56:13.99,0:56:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家指哪些
Dialogue: 0,0:56:15.71,0:56:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是大家
Dialogue: 0,0:56:16.83,0:56:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全搞不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:56:55.23,0:56:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:56:57.45,0:57:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這首曲子 是爸爸寫的吧 在對媽媽表白的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:57:02.45,0:57:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:57:03.44,0:57:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼在聽這個啊
Dialogue: 0,0:57:04.96,0:57:08.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒 沒什麼 只是這個 那個
Dialogue: 0,0:57:10.18,0:57:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起 總之我就是想一個人聽啦
Dialogue: 0,0:57:16.55,0:57:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏 去買下豆腐
Dialogue: 0,0:57:19.71,0:57:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:57:56.81,0:57:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近 她有來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:58:00.54,0:58:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 最近沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:58:04.11,0:58:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:58:06.73,0:58:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:58:09.57,0:58:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有糖
Dialogue: 0,0:58:17.97,0:58:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是太倉促了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:58:21.40,0:58:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是這樣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:58:26.43,0:58:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年輕 便是性急
Dialogue: 0,0:58:29.76,0:58:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好比連一勺糖化開的時間都等不及那般
Dialogue: 0,0:58:39.74,0:58:43.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後悔的苦味 正是做出了結果的證明
Dialogue: 0,0:58:46.18,0:58:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一份 都有它各自的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:58:58.26,0:58:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好苦
Dialogue: 0,0:59:24.84,0:59:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爹 出什麼事了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:26.28,0:59:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那啥 福老爺子出了點事
Dialogue: 0,0:59:30.00,0:59:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說是吃年糕噎住了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:32.10,0:59:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 我和你沒話說來著
Dialogue: 0,0:59:35.40,0:59:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都什麼時候了你說的這什麼話
Dialogue: 0,0:59:37.26,0:59:38.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爺爺
Dialogue: 0,0:59:40.31,0:59:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豆大他人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:59:41.48,0:59:42.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還在給人送貨的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:59:42.99,0:59:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爺爺
Dialogue: 0,0:59:44.00,0:59:46.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉 不要擔心了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:46.69,0:59:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要一同前往的家人有哪些
Dialogue: 0,0:59:48.48,0:59:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:59:49.78,0:59:50.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏
Dialogue: 0,0:59:50.75,0:59:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個 我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:59:53.51,0:59:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們倆一會兒打車來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:59:55.68,0:59:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:59:56.87,0:59:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 走吧
Dialogue: 0,1:00:00.00,1:00:01.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我也要上車
Dialogue: 0,1:00:08.13,1:00:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 吃得有點急了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:00:13.18,1:00:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還想和糕餅同歸於盡嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:00:15.22,1:00:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少說兩句吧你
Dialogue: 0,1:00:16.61,1:00:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你們費心了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:18.12,1:00:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 哪裡 沒事才是最好的
Dialogue: 0,1:00:22.07,1:00:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸
Dialogue: 0,1:00:23.56,1:00:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喲
Dialogue: 0,1:00:27.64,1:00:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼呀 這不是活的好好的嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:00:30.92,1:00:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別隨便咒人死啊
Dialogue: 0,1:00:40.26,1:00:41.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你添麻煩了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:42.46,1:00:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡
Dialogue: 0,1:00:45.07,1:00:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真受不了老爺子他
Dialogue: 0,1:00:49.62,1:00:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 聽說你要去東京啊
Dialogue: 0,1:00:54.46,1:00:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都被吾平拉去灌了好幾次酒了
Dialogue: 0,1:00:58.18,1:01:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼辦啊 豆大 我家的兒子他…
Dialogue: 0,1:01:00.75,1:01:03.64,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好臭 好臭啊
Dialogue: 0,1:01:04.94,1:01:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實在抱歉
Dialogue: 0,1:01:08.46,1:01:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身為男人
Dialogue: 0,1:01:10.06,1:01:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是自己決定的事就這麼著了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:01:16.03,1:01:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,1:01:18.51,1:01:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過呢
Dialogue: 0,1:01:21.47,1:01:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可要回來啊
Dialogue: 0,1:01:25.09,1:01:28.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我先把入院的手續做完再回家
Dialogue: 0,1:01:28.42,1:01:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我們等你吧
Dialogue: 0,1:01:30.08,1:01:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事的 爸爸 你把大家送回去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:01:35.55,1:01:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行 那我們就先回去吧
Dialogue: 0,1:01:40.34,1:01:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏 你和小玉一起坐公交回去
Dialogue: 0,1:01:46.73,1:01:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…我留下
Dialogue: 0,1:01:48.55,1:01:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那誰來開車啊
Dialogue: 0,1:01:50.26,1:01:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肚子餓了 快點回家吧
Dialogue: 0,1:01:54.71,1:01:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂你們兩個 立刻馬就給我回家來
Dialogue: 0,1:01:57.90,1:02:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾平叔叔 道子阿姨 真的太謝謝你們了
Dialogue: 0,1:02:08.55,1:02:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個…
Dialogue: 0,1:02:10.64,1:02:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏 抱歉讓你受驚了  多謝了
Dialogue: 0,1:02:15.34,1:02:16.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不知道會變成什麼樣呢
Dialogue: 0,1:02:16.58,1:02:17.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那啥
Dialogue: 0,1:02:22.26,1:02:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前那事真是抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,1:02:24.69,1:02:25.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事
Dialogue: 0,1:02:27.05,1:02:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那件事 你可以當做沒發生過的
Dialogue: 0,1:02:34.47,1:02:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要那麼在意  像平常一樣就好
Dialogue: 0,1:02:37.68,1:02:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  像平常一樣
Dialogue: 0,1:02:43.05,1:02:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爺爺  不知道晚飯吃了沒有
Dialogue: 0,1:02:46.04,1:02:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了
Dialogue: 0,1:02:46.87,1:02:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醫院的飯菜是什麼樣的啊
Dialogue: 0,1:02:48.99,1:02:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天  去問問看吧
Dialogue: 0,1:02:50.76,1:02:53.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎  姐姐你也會去的吧
Dialogue: 0,1:02:55.22,1:02:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 
Dialogue: 0,1:02:57.34,1:02:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:02:58.48,1:03:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探病  去看爺爺
Dialogue: 0,1:03:01.23,1:03:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  嗯  去的
Dialogue: 0,1:03:03.65,1:03:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我社團活動結束了就去
Dialogue: 0,1:03:08.34,1:03:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 明天餡兒替你給店裡幫忙吧
Dialogue: 0,1:03:11.67,1:03:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝 抱歉了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:03:31.55,1:03:32.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,1:03:33.02,1:03:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早啊
Dialogue: 0,1:03:33.58,1:03:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早
Dialogue: 0,1:03:38.29,1:03:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起
Dialogue: 0,1:03:40.73,1:03:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯  沒事  再來一遍
Dialogue: 0,1:03:44.27,1:03:46.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  本來時間就很緊了
Dialogue: 0,1:03:47.50,1:03:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說你爺爺的事了  知道你現在有點難辦
Dialogue: 0,1:03:51.47,1:03:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 這下麻煩了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:03:54.21,1:03:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想到一個好點子
Dialogue: 0,1:03:56.09,1:03:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:03:56.80,1:03:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做一個裝有強力磁石的手套
Dialogue: 0,1:03:59.93,1:04:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棒子裡也裝一個
Dialogue: 0,1:04:02.21,1:04:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀真是不可思議 強力吸附的S級和N級
Dialogue: 0,1:04:05.66,1:04:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 史織
Dialogue: 0,1:04:10.06,1:04:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天也在做晨練？
Dialogue: 0,1:04:11.14,1:04:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你對S級和N級有什麼想法
Dialogue: 0,1:04:14.08,1:04:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒
Dialogue: 0,1:04:14.69,1:04:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩者情不自已地互相吸引
Dialogue: 0,1:04:17.42,1:04:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果把S級和S級湊一塊舞棒可就飛走了 這可要萬分小心
Dialogue: 0,1:04:24.75,1:04:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了小玉 磁石的話題如此讓你難受？
Dialogue: 0,1:04:29.25,1:04:29.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,1:04:29.96,1:04:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誒
Dialogue: 0,1:04:31.02,1:04:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你感冒了？
Dialogue: 0,1:04:32.32,1:04:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中招了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:33.31,1:04:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好遜
Dialogue: 0,1:04:34.65,1:04:38.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有人要收回之前說的話  一般是在哪種情況之下？
Dialogue: 0,1:04:40.50,1:04:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小史  前兩天你在橋上無視我了
Dialogue: 0,1:04:44.96,1:04:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  這事你就當沒發生過吧
Dialogue: 0,1:04:49.34,1:04:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是這樣的時候嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:04:50.94,1:04:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是搞得尷尬希望對方忘掉的這種
Dialogue: 0,1:04:55.09,1:04:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:04:56.25,1:04:58.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子  遇到什麼事了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:05:04.54,1:05:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大路同學好厲害  大路同學他
Dialogue: 0,1:05:07.16,1:05:10.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子  你對大路同學對你表白這件事受驚了是吧
Dialogue: 0,1:05:11.36,1:05:14.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以大路同學才會對你說當做沒發生過嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:05:15.88,1:05:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  玉子你又很寂寞
Dialogue: 0,1:05:19.16,1:05:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來是  喜歡的呢
Dialogue: 0,1:05:48.24,1:05:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要哭啦  又會被雛子姐姐笑話的
Dialogue: 0,1:05:53.36,1:05:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏
Dialogue: 0,1:06:03.99,1:06:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  很可愛呢
Dialogue: 0,1:06:05.62,1:06:07.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該是  這個樣子的
Dialogue: 0,1:06:07.67,1:06:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小外星人
Dialogue: 0,1:06:09.11,1:06:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然後  你準備怎麼辦
Dialogue: 0,1:06:11.91,1:06:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給不給大路一個答覆？
Dialogue: 0,1:06:14.93,1:06:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盡快給一個答覆比較好哦  盡快
Dialogue: 0,1:06:16.81,1:06:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎
Dialogue: 0,1:06:17.66,1:06:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然還是要選在走廊上撞見那種嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:06:20.73,1:06:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在走廊的轉角上等著
Dialogue: 0,1:06:22.63,1:06:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在斜45度方位見到大路同學後 
Dialogue: 0,1:06:25.79,1:06:28.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咚 啊 摔地 然後把他攔下 
Dialogue: 0,1:06:28.33,1:06:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以此為契機 
Dialogue: 0,1:06:30.14,1:06:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說之前那件事真是謝謝了 我很高興 下次有空幫我建個家吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:38.90,1:06:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和家沒關係吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:40.60,1:06:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我想這麼說而已
Dialogue: 0,1:06:42.34,1:06:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有神菜的作風
Dialogue: 0,1:06:44.27,1:06:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高興 這樣回復他就行了吧
Dialogue: 0,1:06:57.42,1:07:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏 之前真是謝謝了 我很高興 下次有空幫我建…
Dialogue: 0,1:07:02.83,1:07:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 哎？
Dialogue: 0,1:07:08.36,1:07:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借來一用
Dialogue: 0,1:07:09.60,1:07:10.72,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}為我建個家
Dialogue: 0,1:07:09.96,1:07:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神菜 不行啦
Dialogue: 0,1:07:18.00,1:07:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  大路
Dialogue: 0,1:07:20.56,1:07:21.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼事
Dialogue: 0,1:07:24.14,1:07:25.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還以為你不會說的
Dialogue: 0,1:07:26.54,1:07:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還以為你肯定不會說的
Dialogue: 0,1:07:36.39,1:07:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刮目相看了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:39.32,1:07:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僅此而已
Dialogue: 0,1:07:44.95,1:07:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久等了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:47.19,1:07:48.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開動了
Dialogue: 0,1:07:50.94,1:07:51.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠
Dialogue: 0,1:07:52.81,1:07:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騙你啦  沒事
Dialogue: 0,1:07:57.76,1:07:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,1:08:08.50,1:08:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還真是喜歡呢  這首曲子
Dialogue: 0,1:08:11.01,1:08:12.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不起  是不是太吵了
Dialogue: 0,1:08:12.91,1:08:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,1:08:14.84,1:08:17.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爺爺  沒事真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,1:08:17.86,1:08:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像明天就可以在店裡做事了
Dialogue: 0,1:08:24.52,1:08:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了  餡兒  穿穿看這個吧
Dialogue: 0,1:08:27.98,1:08:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明年餡兒也是中學生了呢
Dialogue: 0,1:08:32.52,1:08:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很合身哦  餡兒
Dialogue: 0,1:08:34.48,1:08:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎  我感覺稍微有點大呢
Dialogue: 0,1:08:40.64,1:08:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來這邊一下
Dialogue: 0,1:08:44.52,1:08:45.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了
Dialogue: 0,1:08:48.21,1:08:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餡兒不怕改變嗎？
Dialogue: 0,1:08:53.23,1:08:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼意思
Dialogue: 0,1:08:55.26,1:08:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然陷入和至今而止不一樣的世界裡的那種感覺
Dialogue: 0,1:08:59.28,1:09:00.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,致豆大
Dialogue: 0,1:09:01.57,1:09:02.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:09:02.70,1:09:06.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豆大獻給了我一首十分精彩的曲子
Dialogue: 0,1:09:07.18,1:09:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我也想為此回一份禮
Dialogue: 0,1:09:10.77,1:09:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  還有
Dialogue: 0,1:09:12.77,1:09:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關於之前我逃避的這件事真是萬分抱歉
Dialogue: 0,1:09:15.02,1:09:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是媽媽的聲音
Dialogue: 0,1:09:17.69,1:09:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼  我在此獻上一曲
Dialogue: 0,1:09:26.67,1:09:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽媽
Dialogue: 0,1:09:31.20,1:09:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌  唱的有點跑調呢
Dialogue: 0,1:09:35.73,1:09:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 
Dialogue: 0,1:09:54.26,1:09:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餡兒  我明天就能回店裡幫忙了
Dialogue: 0,1:09:58.68,1:09:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:10:05.79,1:10:06.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,1:10:09.20,1:10:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,1:10:10.91,1:10:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,50個豆沙大福哦
Dialogue: 0,1:10:16.24,1:10:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠
Dialogue: 0,1:10:19.64,1:10:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,1:10:20.70,1:10:21.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,1:10:22.59,1:10:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠 我感覺這次能夠好好接住了 在節日大賽上
Dialogue: 0,1:10:29.77,1:10:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉讓你費心了  餅藏那兒我也會好好給一個答覆的
Dialogue: 0,1:10:37.99,1:10:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是呢 走吧
Dialogue: 0,1:10:48.61,1:10:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盡情來一場沒有遺憾的表演吧
Dialogue: 0,1:10:51.41,1:10:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,1:10:53.09,1:10:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼我們上吧
Dialogue: 0,1:10:54.42,1:10:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家  一起喊自己喜歡的東西來加油吧
Dialogue: 0,1:10:56.58,1:10:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薄烤餅
Dialogue: 0,1:10:57.32,1:10:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炒雞蛋
Dialogue: 0,1:10:58.11,1:10:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仙貝
Dialogue: 0,1:10:58.98,1:10:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直角
Dialogue: 0,1:10:59.91,1:11:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熊
Dialogue: 0,1:11:02.31,1:11:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年糕
Dialogue: 0,1:11:05.10,1:11:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1 2
Dialogue: 0,1:11:06.59,1:11:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢
Dialogue: 0,1:11:09.11,1:11:11.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在有請下面一組
Dialogue: 0,1:11:11.89,1:11:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來自兔子山高中女子舞棒隊的表演
Dialogue: 0,1:12:58.25,1:12:59.79,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs-1}徹底刪除後 \N回收站內的資源\N將完全刪除。\N 需要完全刪除嗎？ \N取消 確定
Dialogue: 0,1:13:01.27,1:13:06.51,zhushi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fs-1}徹底刪除後 \N回收站內的資源\N將完全刪除。\N 需要完全刪除嗎？ \N取消 確定
Dialogue: 0,1:13:16.11,1:13:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休學？
Dialogue: 0,1:13:17.25,1:13:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對 好像是得流感的學生有很多
Dialogue: 0,1:13:21.35,1:13:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:22.84,1:13:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒通知到的就剩餅藏了 你幫忙聯繫一下他
Dialogue: 0,1:13:28.51,1:13:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北白川同學？
Dialogue: 0,1:13:30.32,1:13:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:13:35.01,1:13:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶 餡兒 如果有人沒接到通知的話會怎麼樣啊
Dialogue: 0,1:13:40.07,1:13:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼怎麼樣 沒有通知不就不知道了嘛
Dialogue: 0,1:13:45.22,1:13:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,1:13:46.90,1:13:47.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給
Dialogue: 0,1:13:47.72,1:13:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,1:13:49.78,1:13:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏他有沒有發現
Dialogue: 0,1:13:51.63,1:13:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有 現在他正和小吾看電視呢
Dialogue: 0,1:13:55.69,1:13:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過這樣就行了嗎
Dialogue: 0,1:13:57.60,1:13:58.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,1:13:58.85,1:14:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要再給你做一對新的
Dialogue: 0,1:14:00.46,1:14:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是要這個
Dialogue: 0,1:14:03.09,1:14:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你 道子阿姨
Dialogue: 0,1:14:34.42,1:14:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠
Dialogue: 0,1:14:37.74,1:14:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去玉子家裡的時候 聽說你來學校了
Dialogue: 0,1:14:41.93,1:14:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像還沒通知大路？
Dialogue: 0,1:14:45.37,1:14:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,1:14:46.73,1:14:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大路 不會來的哦
Dialogue: 0,1:14:50.64,1:14:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才我遇到餅藏了
Dialogue: 0,1:14:54.20,1:14:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他說要去東京
Dialogue: 0,1:14:57.10,1:14:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是突然決定下來的
Dialogue: 0,1:14:59.95,1:15:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是很果斷呢  他決定立刻就轉學
Dialogue: 0,1:15:05.23,1:15:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉學
Dialogue: 0,1:15:06.57,1:15:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過 要去考東京的大學話 的確是現在去比較好
Dialogue: 0,1:15:14.31,1:15:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他會坐9點多的新幹線
Dialogue: 0,1:15:18.63,1:15:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,動作快點的話還來得及
Dialogue: 0,1:15:26.14,1:15:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠 謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,1:15:34.72,1:15:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小綠
Dialogue: 0,1:15:38.05,1:15:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神菜
Dialogue: 0,1:15:40.00,1:15:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還想趁教室裡沒人來做一個架子來著
Dialogue: 0,1:15:44.52,1:15:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啊  那是
Dialogue: 0,1:15:45.89,1:15:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小玉碰上什麼事了 剛才見她急急忙忙的就跑出去了
Dialogue: 0,1:15:51.85,1:15:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我撒了個謊
Dialogue: 0,1:15:53.65,1:15:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:15:54.48,1:15:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騙她說大路要轉學
Dialogue: 0,1:15:57.02,1:16:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其實他只是去參觀一下要報考的大學而已
Dialogue: 0,1:16:01.77,1:16:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可真是老謀深算 不過我挺喜歡這樣的
Dialogue: 0,1:16:08.32,1:16:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 小綠
Dialogue: 0,1:16:12.50,1:16:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你現在的表情不錯啊
Dialogue: 0,1:16:18.51,1:16:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,thank you 神菜
Dialogue: 0,1:16:20.87,1:16:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吶 小綠 我要不要也試試登一下高呢
Dialogue: 0,1:16:28.41,1:16:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好寬敞啊
Dialogue: 0,1:16:31.31,1:16:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真寬敞啊
Dialogue: 0,1:16:50.83,1:16:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子
Dialogue: 0,1:16:59.40,1:17:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒂拉 有春天的味道呢
Dialogue: 0,1:17:03.33,1:17:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是玉子的風呢
Dialogue: 0,1:17:05.73,1:17:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喬伊 蒂拉 吃點心了
Dialogue: 0,1:17:07.95,1:17:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,王子
Dialogue: 0,1:17:21.25,1:17:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪裡 我搞不明白啦
Dialogue: 0,1:17:45.82,1:17:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上啊 神菜！
Dialogue: 0,1:18:24.55,1:18:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏 在哪裡？
Dialogue: 0,1:18:31.64,1:18:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏
Dialogue: 0,1:18:33.30,1:18:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏
Dialogue: 0,1:18:37.28,1:18:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏
Dialogue: 0,1:18:41.11,1:18:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子
Dialogue: 0,1:18:43.30,1:18:47.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等啊 等等啦
Dialogue: 0,1:18:52.24,1:18:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉子 為什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:18:52.88,1:18:53.66,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼
Dialogue: 0,1:18:53.83,1:18:56.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼  為什麼要去東京
Dialogue: 0,1:18:56.91,1:18:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很遠的 東京很遠的
Dialogue: 0,1:18:59.54,1:19:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 這個 但是 誒 為什麼玉子會在這裡
Dialogue: 0,1:19:03.23,1:19:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明一直都在身邊的 為什麼突然要離開
Dialogue: 0,1:19:09.24,1:19:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我還有話沒有對餅藏
Dialogue: 0,1:19:11.25,1:19:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,1:19:19.01,1:19:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 我搞錯了
Dialogue: 0,1:19:22.82,1:19:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 餅藏的 我的
Dialogue: 0,1:19:46.09,1:19:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我…
Dialogue: 0,1:19:52.53,1:19:56.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餅藏 我最喜歡你了 請講
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.53,0:08:16.59,OP_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}夕日が沈む　音楽室で
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.74,0:08:21.34,OP_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ピアノを奏でる　あなたの
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.71,0:08:28.88,OP_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}やわらかい　横顔に
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.21,0:08:35.36,OP_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}惹きつけられて　目が離せなくて
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.43,0:08:41.61,OP_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}あなたの家の　テレフォンナンバー
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.66,0:08:46.57,OP_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}くり返し　書いて　おぼえて
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.79,0:08:54.00,OP_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}受話器を　はずして
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.12,0:09:00.27,OP_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}ダイヤル回す　それだけなんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.03,0:09:12.14,OP_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}だけど　そんな勇気も出せないから
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.40,0:09:24.97,OP_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}せめて　この歌をあなたのためだけに歌う
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.05,0:09:30.72,OP_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}この歌はあなただけに聴いてほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------OPCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.53,0:08:16.59,OP_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}在夕陽西下的音樂室裡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.74,0:08:21.34,OP_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}不禁被演奏著鋼琴的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.71,0:08:28.88,OP_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你那清秀的側臉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.21,0:08:35.36,OP_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}所吸引  無法自拔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.43,0:08:41.61,OP_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}不停地寫著  記著
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.66,0:08:46.57,OP_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}你家的電話號碼
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.79,0:08:54.00,OP_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}拿起聽筒
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.12,0:09:00.27,OP_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}撥出號碼  僅僅如此
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.03,0:09:12.14,OP_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}但是我連這樣的勇氣都沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.40,0:09:24.97,OP_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}但至少讓這首歌只為你所唱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.05,0:09:30.72,OP_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(200,200)}希望這首歌只有你能聽到
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDJP-------------------
Dialogue: 0,1:20:24.54,1:20:29.18,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}夕\N日\Nが\N沈\Nむ\N　\N音\N楽\N室\Nで
Dialogue: 0,1:20:30.20,1:20:33.52,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}ピ\Nア\Nノ\Nを\N奏\Nで\Nる\N　\Nあ\Nな\Nた\Nの
Dialogue: 0,1:20:34.81,1:20:38.81,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}や\Nわ\Nら\Nか\Nい\N　\N横\N顔\Nに
Dialogue: 0,1:20:41.62,1:20:46.32,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}惹\Nき\Nつ\Nけ\Nら\Nれ\Nて\N　\N目\Nが\N離\Nせ\Nな\Nく\Nて
Dialogue: 0,1:20:47.39,1:20:51.99,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}あ\Nな\Nた\Nの\N家\Nの\N　\Nテ\Nレ\Nフ\Nォ\Nン\Nナ\Nン\Nバ\Nー
Dialogue: 0,1:20:53.08,1:20:56.40,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}く\Nり\N返\Nし\N　\N書\Nい\Nて\N　\Nお\Nぼ\Nえ\Nて\N
Dialogue: 0,1:20:57.75,1:21:01.65,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}受\N話\N器\Nを\N　\Nは\Nず\Nし\Nて
Dialogue: 0,1:21:04.48,1:21:09.12,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}ダ\Nイ\Nヤ\Nル\N回\Nす\N　\Nそ\Nれ\Nだ\Nけ\Nな\Nん\Nだ
Dialogue: 0,1:21:09.89,1:21:20.22,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}だ\Nけ\Nど\N　\Nそ\Nん\Nな\N勇\N気\Nも\N出\Nせ\Nな\Nい\Nか\Nら
Dialogue: 0,1:21:21.29,1:21:31.61,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}せ\Nめ\Nて\N　\Nこ\Nの\N歌\Nを\Nあ\Nな\Nた\Nの\Nた\Nめ\Nだ\Nけ\Nに\N歌\Nう
Dialogue: 0,1:21:31.99,1:21:37.32,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}こ\Nの\N歌\Nは\Nあ\Nな\Nた\Nだ\Nけ\Nに\N聴\Nい\Nて\Nほ\Nし\Nい
Dialogue: 0,1:22:17.44,1:22:21.38,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}無\N邪\N気\Nな\N笑\N顔\N　\N見\Nて\Nい\Nる\Nだ\Nけ\Nで
Dialogue: 0,1:22:21.50,1:22:26.17,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}延\N々\Nは\Nな\Nし\N尽\Nき\Nな\Nい\Nけ\Nど
Dialogue: 0,1:22:26.67,1:22:30.71,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}ふ\Nい\Nに\Nだ\Nま\Nっ\Nて\N　\N時\Nが\N止\Nま\Nる\Nと
Dialogue: 0,1:22:30.82,1:22:34.24,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}急\Nに\N大\N人\Nに\N見\Nえ\Nた\Nん\Nだ
Dialogue: 0,1:22:34.47,1:22:39.77,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}悲\Nし\Nい\Nわ\Nけ\Nじ\Nゃ\Nな\Nい\Nの\Nに
Dialogue: 0,1:22:39.92,1:22:45.97,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}泣\Nき\Nた\Nい\N気\N持\Nち\Nに\Nな\Nる\Nよ\N　\Nな\Nぜ\N？
Dialogue: 0,1:22:46.25,1:22:51.41,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}一\N言\Nで\Nも\N\N伝\Nえ\Nら\Nれ\Nる\Nの\Nな\Nら\Nば
Dialogue: 0,1:22:51.51,1:23:01.31,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}も\Nう\N変\Nわ\Nり\Nは\Nじ\Nめ\Nて\Nい\Nる\N　\Nあ\Nざ\Nや\Nか\Nな\N宇\N宙\Nが
Dialogue: 0,1:23:01.46,1:23:06.05,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}廻\Nり\N巡\Nっ\Nて\N　\N私\Nを\N呼\Nぶ\Nよ
Dialogue: 0,1:23:06.17,1:23:10.74,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}裸\N足\Nで\Nも\Nい\Nい\N　\N輝\Nく\N世\N界\Nへ
Dialogue: 0,1:23:10.87,1:23:17.30,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}星\Nが\Nほ\Nほ\Nえ\Nん\Nだ\Nら\N　\N手\Nを\Nの\Nば\Nし
Dialogue: 0,1:23:17.42,1:23:26.84,ED_JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(40,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}小\Nさ\Nく\N揺\Nれ\Nて\Nい\Nた\N心\Nを\Nた\Nだ\N　\N解\Nき\N放\Nつ\Nよ
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,----------------EDCN-------------------
Dialogue: 0,1:20:24.54,1:20:29.18,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}在\N夕\N陽\N西\N下\N的\N音\N樂\N室\N裡
Dialogue: 0,1:20:30.20,1:20:33.52,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}不\N禁\N被\N演\N奏\N著\N鋼\N琴\N的
Dialogue: 0,1:20:34.81,1:20:38.81,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}你\N那\N清\N秀\N的\N側\N臉
Dialogue: 0,1:20:41.62,1:20:46.32,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}所\N吸\N引\N  \N無\N法\N自\N拔
Dialogue: 0,1:20:47.39,1:20:51.99,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}不\N停\N地\N寫\N著\N \N記\N著
Dialogue: 0,1:20:53.08,1:20:56.40,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}你\N家\N的\N電\N話\N號\N碼
Dialogue: 0,1:20:57.75,1:21:01.65,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}拿\N起\N聽\N筒
Dialogue: 0,1:21:04.48,1:21:09.12,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}撥\N出\N號\N碼\N  \N僅\N僅\N如\N此
Dialogue: 0,1:21:09.89,1:21:20.22,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}但\N是\N我\N連\N這\N樣\N的\N勇\N氣\N都\N沒\N有
Dialogue: 0,1:21:21.29,1:21:31.61,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}但\N至\N少\N讓\N這\N首\N歌\N只\N為\N你\N所\N唱
Dialogue: 0,1:21:31.99,1:21:37.32,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}希\N望\N這\N首\N歌\N只\N有\N你\N能\N聽\N到
Dialogue: 0,1:22:17.44,1:22:21.38,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}只\N是\N看\N著\N那\N純\N正\N無\N邪\N的\N笑\N容
Dialogue: 0,1:22:21.50,1:22:26.17,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}雖\N然\N有\N說\N不\N完\N的\N話
Dialogue: 0,1:22:26.67,1:22:30.71,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}不\N小\N心\N沉\N默\N一\N下\N  \N就\N感\N覺\N時\N間\N停\N了\N下\N來
Dialogue: 0,1:22:30.82,1:22:34.24,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}一\N下\N子\N宛\N如\N大\N人\N一\N般
Dialogue: 0,1:22:34.47,1:22:39.77,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}明\N明\N一\N點\N都\N不\N悲\N傷
Dialogue: 0,1:22:39.92,1:22:45.97,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}卻\N有\N想\N哭\N的\N心\N情\N  \N這\N是\N為\N何\N？
Dialogue: 0,1:22:46.25,1:22:51.41,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}如\N果\N一\N句\N話\N就\N能\N說\N清\N的\N話
Dialogue: 0,1:22:51.51,1:23:01.31,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}平\N穩\N的\N宇\N宙\N已\N經\N開\N始\N了\N變\N化
Dialogue: 0,1:23:01.46,1:23:06.05,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}時\N光\N輪\N轉\N \N喚\N我\N前\N往
Dialogue: 0,1:23:06.17,1:23:10.74,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}即\N使\N光\N著\N腳\N \N也\N要\N前\N往\N這\N光\N輝\N的\N世\N界
Dialogue: 0,1:23:10.87,1:23:17.30,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}對\N著\N微\N笑\N的\N星\N星\N伸\N出\N手
Dialogue: 0,1:23:17.42,1:23:26.84,ED_CN,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\pos(1240,360)\fad(200,200)\be70}解\N放\N這\N搖\N擺\N不\N定\N的\N小\N小\N心\N靈\N吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
