[Script Info]
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:848
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default2,MS UI Gothic,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,2,8,10,10,10,0
Style: Default,方正准圆_GBK,32,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00145CD6,&H804182ED,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,30,30,12,134
Style: Comment,方正准圆_GBK,25,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00145CD6,&H804182ED,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,8,30,30,12,134
Style: biaoti,DFPGirlW5-B5,45,&H00FFB5FF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H00FFFFFF,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,3,30,30,10,136
Style: biaoti1,ＤＦ教科書体W3,45,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,3,30,30,10,128
Style: biaoti2,DFPGirlW5-B5,45,&H00000000,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,3,30,30,10,136
Style: biaozhi,方正准圆_GBK,30,&H60FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H75464646,&H000F0F0F,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: mianze,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H20FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H20000000,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,8,30,30,10,134
Style: OP1,ＤＦ教科書体W3,27,&H009A35FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,7,30,30,10,128
Style: OP2,DFPGirlW5-B5,27,&H009A35FF,&HF0000000,&H00FFFFFF,&H00FFFFFF,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,0,3,30,30,10,136
Style: ED1,HGMaruGothicMPRO,23,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00765932,&H00FFFFFF,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,7,30,30,10,128
Style: ED2,方正准圆_GBK,26,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00765932,&H00FFFFFF,1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,3,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.20,0:11:05.20,biaozhi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(82,40)}{\move(490,30,490,45,0,2000)}{\t(0,2000,\fry360)}{\fade(500,500)}{\t(0,2000,\fs28)}動漫國字幕組
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.20,0:11:05.20,biaozhi,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(82,54)}{\t(0,2000,\fs20)}{\fade(500,500)}bbs . dmguo . com
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.22,0:21:35.47,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}本字幕由動漫國字幕組製作(bbs.dmguo.com)\N僅供試看,若您喜歡本作品,請支持購買正版音像製品
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.47,0:21:39.20,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)} 翻譯:時の楔&KKK  時間:タママ  後期:小白  MKV：nuomi 協力:dongs
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.57,0:21:45.44,mianze,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(500,500)}9000G永不過期,同步連載的動漫下載站  http://x.dmguo.com
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.24,0:01:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久很久以前 某個地方住著一位老爺爺跟老奶奶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.98,0:01:43.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日真是好天氣唄
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.64,0:01:45.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,櫻老奶奶去河邊洗衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.36,0:01:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸村老爺爺去山上砍柴…
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.45,0:01:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果沒去 被迫幫著洗衣服
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.50,0:01:54.88,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浮浮沉沉 浮浮沉沉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.60,0:01:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.18,0:01:56.78,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,浮浮沉沉 浮浮沉沉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.56,0:01:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這時 有個很大的桃子漂過來
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.21,0:01:58.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.91,0:02:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 我最愛桃子啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.27,0:02:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老太婆啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.63,0:02:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爺爺和老奶奶把桃子帶回家
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.27,0:02:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閃光
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.33,0:02:10.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,準備吃了它 就在那時…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.20,0:02:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從桃子裡面蹦出個…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.15,0:02:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鐺鐺鐺
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.70,0:02:26.71,biaoti,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(650,165)}連桃太郎都是女僕大人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.20,0:02:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在 在下…要去討伐惡鬼…是也
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.54,0:02:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老 老太婆啊 桃子裡冒出個人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.26,0:02:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嚼 嚼
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.59,0:02:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不是吃桃子的時候啦
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.73,0:02:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近是不是有惡鬼擄走年輕姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.86,0:02:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓村人都很害怕的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.28,0:02:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉呀 生出個了不起的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.62,0:02:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可饒恕那殘暴的惡鬼 是也
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.60,0:02:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了 桃太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.72,0:03:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放輕鬆一點也沒關係啦 放輕鬆點
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.76,0:03:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.79,0:03:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老太婆呀 何時取了名字
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.53,0:03:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼爺爺奶奶 我出發了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.30,0:03:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 看你好帥氣的樣子 這個特地送你唄
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.04,0:03:17.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多吃點黍糰子哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.23,0:03:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你 奶奶
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.36,0:03:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保重
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.02,0:03:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油唄
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.33,0:03:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.61,0:03:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 來吃桃子唄
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.49,0:03:34.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣 為討伐惡鬼而踏上旅程的桃太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.41,0:03:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到了狗 猴子 山雞
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.99,0:03:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼我們要遭這種罪啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.65,0:03:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是狗你的錯 居然被那種人騙了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.16,0:03:45.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猴子你不也被騙了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.89,0:03:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是山雞沒發覺的錯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.52,0:03:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有說過不可信啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.89,0:03:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們在幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.99,0:03:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊萍水相逢的路人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.45,0:03:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請救我們
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.29,0:03:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們被壞人拐騙來 快被殺了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.06,0:04:05.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們說「肯救我們的話 就什麼都聽你的」
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.23,0:04:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,於是桃太郎救了他們三個
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.39,0:04:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但因為他們想搶黍糰子 又小小的教訓了一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.88,0:04:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才抓他們的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.12,0:04:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壞人出現了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.29,0:04:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會被殺掉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.65,0:04:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什麼人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.17,0:04:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是碓冰
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.79,0:04:35.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三笨蛋大馬戲團的團長
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.30,0:04:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些是我的團員
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.56,0:04:37.91,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(430,160)}那些
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.10,0:04:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好假
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.34,0:04:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 好不容易建了個馬戲團的說
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.78,0:04:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果這些傢伙完全派不上用場
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.20,0:04:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才想乾脆吃掉好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.00,0:04:49.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.51,0:04:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當做食物而殺生 也沒辦法啦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.39,0:04:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會是沒辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.91,0:04:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為之前一直在做排練 食物也被吃光了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.88,0:05:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼排練 只是你滿臉歡喜地隨意鞭打我們吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.78,0:05:02.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.72,0:05:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從誰開始呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.40,0:05:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很難吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.54,0:05:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很好吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.62,0:05:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先吃他先吃他
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.76,0:05:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.02,0:05:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是最好吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.67,0:05:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以說這傢伙比較好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.44,0:05:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.56,0:05:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然會救我們…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.32,0:05:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被吃掉之前有事問你們
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.73,0:05:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來不是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.67,0:05:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道惡鬼的住處嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.69,0:05:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.34,0:05:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.67,0:05:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰 猶豫的話我推薦做什錦火鍋
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.43,0:05:29.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告辭了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.97,0:05:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請等一下等一下等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.65,0:05:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不知道惡鬼的住處
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.06,0:05:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是最近出現惡鬼的村子我們知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.56,0:05:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那村子大多是年輕人 惡鬼突然出現
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.24,0:05:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隔天 村裡所有姑娘都不見了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.63,0:05:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們說的是哪個村子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.25,0:05:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救我們就帶你去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.37,0:05:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.27,0:05:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.83,0:05:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.24,0:06:02.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要給我黍糰子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.60,0:06:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣 桃太郎跟狗 猴子 山雞
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.83,0:06:10.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及可疑的馬戲團團長一起出發去找惡鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.85,0:06:12.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們那份黍糰子呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.92,0:06:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.01,0:06:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼！？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.29,0:06:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但 但是這種感覺不錯呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.05,0:06:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是勇者率領的小隊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.51,0:06:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,party？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.18,0:06:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開什麼玩笑 你這傢伙以為是辦宴會嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.99,0:06:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可不是為了好玩的旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.01,0:06:30.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是指那個party啦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.75,0:06:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是給我們五人的總稱…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.64,0:06:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要那種東西嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.61,0:06:40.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼就叫 「討伐惡鬼會」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.63,0:06:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡稱「伐鬼會」
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.62,0:06:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是個好名字 沒意見吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.70,0:06:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 出發吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.48,0:06:55.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這裡啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.38,0:06:59.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被惡鬼擄走姑娘的村子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.45,0:07:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是荒涼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.87,0:07:05.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,豈止是姑娘 根本感覺不到一點人氣
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.85,0:07:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說了那個是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.73,0:07:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要跟我搶嗎你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.26,0:07:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我田裡的最後一根啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.53,0:07:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是 那是我的田
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.11,0:07:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 那個
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.70,0:07:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要幹嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.48,0:07:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿走囉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.16,0:07:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.10,0:07:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這慘狀是 被惡鬼害的？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.34,0:07:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好臭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.13,0:07:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.37,0:07:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像說突然變很臭 受不了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.34,0:07:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙是狗 鼻子很靈嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.78,0:07:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這點氣味就縮掉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.37,0:07:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看你們還是趁早離開這個村子才好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.71,0:07:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼這麼說
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.19,0:07:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡已經不是正常人住的村子…了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.12,0:07:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 怎麼了 沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.71,0:08:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些傢伙終於也撐不住了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.11,0:08:02.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能給我解釋一下嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.99,0:08:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以說 就是完全沒洗澡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.65,0:08:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村裡姑娘都不見了之後
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.41,0:08:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,洗衣打掃之類的都變得一團糟
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.93,0:08:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人們都過著野外生存一樣的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.09,0:08:16.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說是村子 不如說是戰場啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.22,0:08:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,簡直是弱肉強食
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.30,0:08:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是意外的很有趣哦 生存戰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.69,0:08:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充滿刺激呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.75,0:08:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,村子變成這樣 姑娘們回來的時候會很為難吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.73,0:08:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 不會回來了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.04,0:08:35.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對方是惡鬼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.75,0:08:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打不贏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.27,0:08:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.15,0:08:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.43,0:08:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別開玩笑了 我們去救回那些姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.03,0:08:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快告訴我惡鬼的住處
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.81,0:08:49.30,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此時的幸村老爺爺和櫻老奶奶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.15,0:08:49.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真太平唄
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.15,0:08:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這片海的對面 就有個惡鬼島
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.30,0:08:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只看見水平線
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.81,0:09:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信村裡那些傢伙說的沒問題嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.17,0:09:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說得好含糊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.77,0:09:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定不是想幫我們
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.89,0:09:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滿臉寫著不情願呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.18,0:09:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別去了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.33,0:09:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天就別去了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.14,0:09:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去別的村子說不定能打聽到新消息
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.40,0:09:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.75,0:09:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出發
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.09,0:09:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本不聽
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.82,0:09:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這隻烏龜怎麼回事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.31,0:09:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把它翻過來好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.78,0:09:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點翻快點翻
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.29,0:09:26.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你們在幹什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.28,0:09:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.18,0:09:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.11,0:09:29.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救了烏龜
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.52,0:09:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這難道會是那個
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.50,0:09:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個是？
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.15,0:09:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽過這樣一個故事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.84,0:09:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救了烏龜的話 它為報恩就會背著你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.84,0:09:39.53,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,童話：浦島太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.73,0:09:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶你去海底的龍宮
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.12,0:09:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龍宮？是什麼樣的地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.37,0:09:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又漂亮又有些性感的龍宮仙女
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.71,0:09:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會送上好多鯛魚比目魚鮪魚之類的新鮮海料理款待你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.77,0:09:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且還能讓你帶禮物回來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.56,0:09:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎 快點讓它帶我們去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.81,0:10:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是要小心那個叫玉匣的禮物
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.66,0:10:05.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打開的話裡面會冒出煙霧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.98,0:10:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞬間你就變成老人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.19,0:10:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼給這種危險的禮物啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.42,0:10:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烏龜難道是恩將仇報嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.41,0:10:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下 不開那個玉匣不就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.77,0:10:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯 只要不打開玉匣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.45,0:10:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能吃美食 還能跟漂亮又有點性感的龍宮仙女作伴
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.94,0:10:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們 從剛剛開始在說什麼悄悄話
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.15,0:10:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驚
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.54,0:10:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什 什麼事都沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.62,0:10:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們搭在這隻烏龜背上去惡鬼島
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.34,0:10:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先走一步去探探情況
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.52,0:10:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去去就回
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.56,0:10:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不覺得有點穿越嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.13,0:10:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.58,0:10:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能呼吸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.82,0:10:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想殺了我們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.87,0:10:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鳥不會游泳啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.53,0:10:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.77,0:11:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種破船沒問題嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.80,0:11:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遇難的話怎麼辦啊 也沒有食物
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.18,0:11:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到時候就吃了你們
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.61,0:11:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,果然
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.98,0:11:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山雞 你飛到天上去找出惡鬼島的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.95,0:11:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.61,0:11:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不到陸地
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.09,0:11:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山雞也沒回來
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.92,0:11:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是逃了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.94,0:11:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的羈絆是很深的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.03,0:11:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快被吃掉的時候還在互相推託來的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.12,0:11:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.64,0:11:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼會
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.35,0:11:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然自己逃了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.34,0:11:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肚子餓了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.46,0:11:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.88,0:11:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這裡居然還剩一個
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.36,0:11:43.76,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黍糰子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.02,0:11:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.13,0:11:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.85,0:11:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放開
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.48,0:12:06.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們掉下去的是這個普通的黍糰子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.48,0:12:06.13,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,童話：金斧銀斧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.54,0:12:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是這邊一疊黍糰子1年份中獎明信片
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.27,0:12:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是這邊的最高等堪察加擬石蟹 海膽 鮭魚子 扇貝
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.63,0:12:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北海道珍饈海味的中獎明信片呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.40,0:12:23.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那個普通的黍糰子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.28,0:12:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎 嗯 你是個誠實的人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.09,0:12:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作為獎勵 就把這個北海道珍饈海味的中獎明信片送給你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.19,0:12:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信箱呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.36,0:12:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西北偏北方向30公里處的一個海濱村莊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.89,0:12:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼時候能拿到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.51,0:12:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抽獎日在一個月以後 中獎公佈將會發送…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.48,0:12:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃走了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.09,0:12:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還我黍糰子
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.31,0:12:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在吃什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.48,0:12:59.79,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(430,20)}家就在隔壁
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.48,0:12:59.79,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(800,20)}此\N刻\N的\N幸\N村\N老\N爺\N爺\N和\N櫻\N老\N奶\N奶
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.55,0:12:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靜子婆婆
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.96,0:12:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃桃子唄
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.62,0:13:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長 睏了？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.84,0:13:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微睡會吧 我會替你守著…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.11,0:13:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,…的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.44,0:13:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別碰我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.20,0:13:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然順其自然和你們一起旅行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.89,0:13:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我並不信任你們
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.02,0:13:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,特別是碓冰你 太可疑了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.87,0:13:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外表也好 內心也好 一切的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.11,0:13:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就隨便你了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.95,0:13:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.87,0:13:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是山雞嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.68,0:13:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.02,0:13:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊 救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.67,0:14:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼感覺山雞下面拖著像繩子一樣的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.64,0:14:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.29,0:14:08.39,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅之丘
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.05,0:14:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命啊 我會被殺掉的 救命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.46,0:14:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那個吧 撿回一艘被遺棄的船
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.31,0:14:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那傢伙真周到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.12,0:14:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼呀 你說的夥伴就是這艘破船啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.13,0:14:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太讓我失望了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.83,0:14:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看著也不覺得能撈到點什麼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.92,0:14:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少讓我高興高興吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.51,0:14:36.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之 就給我跪下求饒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.62,0:14:39.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山雞你個笨蛋 幹嘛被海盜抓到啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.60,0:14:40.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要死你自己死
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.72,0:14:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷血鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.50,0:14:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難道是 剛才的烏龜
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.93,0:14:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是說 來報恩了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.82,0:14:59.08,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日本童話：白鶴的報恩
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.82,0:14:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能保證絕對不偷看嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.88,0:15:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能偷看 一定是在給我們準備很厲害的武器
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.98,0:15:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎麼感覺又在穿越了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.11,0:15:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.98,0:15:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在幹什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.85,0:15:30.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,躺著一個不認識的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.48,0:15:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這傢伙誰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.44,0:15:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我死出去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.82,0:15:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們幾個 演的什麼破爛短劇啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.91,0:15:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我適可而止點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.87,0:15:42.01,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此刻的幸村老爺爺和櫻老奶奶
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.18,0:15:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊啦啦 是桃子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.34,0:15:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有很多很多呢 多吃點吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.16,0:15:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老 老太婆啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.60,0:15:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受不了你們
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.58,0:15:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用刀把子彈劈開了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.52,0:16:02.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣 你過來一下
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.74,0:16:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我上來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.48,0:16:13.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真沒辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.89,0:16:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀呀 太亂來了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.68,0:16:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之把耳朵堵起來比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.05,0:16:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這艘船容易著火啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.23,0:16:36.27,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好燙 好燙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.21,0:16:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估計 離遠點會比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.27,0:16:39.55,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點來救我啊 我說 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.57,0:16:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊…
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.58,0:16:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是群有趣的傢伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.21,0:16:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝…謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.10,0:16:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舉手之勞
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.93,0:16:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過天都亮了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.68,0:17:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真累人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.88,0:17:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看那邊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.66,0:17:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,終於出現了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.79,0:17:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惡鬼島
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.95,0:17:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 就憑我們贏得了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.45,0:17:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們連武器都沒帶哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.75,0:17:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了 這個時候就要用那個辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.18,0:17:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個辦法是什麼辦法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.03,0:17:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鐺鐺鐺
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.28,0:17:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稻草？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.28,0:17:34.12,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日本童話：稻草富翁
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.32,0:17:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用這個去逐一換到各式各樣的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.59,0:17:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣的話 雖然開始只是一般的稻草
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.31,0:17:40.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,換到最後會變成超厲害的武器的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.20,0:17:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.24,0:17:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之 有沒有什麼可以交換的東西啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.42,0:17:45.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鏘鏘鏘
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.84,0:17:45.94,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餐巾紙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.60,0:17:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 下一個
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.62,0:17:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鏘鏘鏘
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.13,0:17:50.11,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壞掉的犬笛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.56,0:17:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 下一個
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.59,0:17:53.90,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鏘鏘鏘
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.64,0:17:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器什麼的 有這把刀就足夠
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.58,0:17:55.57,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 下一個
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.92,0:17:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從正面突破
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.51,0:17:59.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長會長 來看看這個
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.11,0:18:01.52,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惡鬼島制服 想成為夥伴的人請穿上這個 *尺寸有3種
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.48,0:18:02.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原來如此
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.37,0:18:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佯裝成想成為夥伴的人 從而潛入內部的方法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.77,0:18:08.63,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是夠奇怪的服裝袋啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.18,0:18:11.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起激烈的戰鬥 這樣也許可以不用傷到姑娘們
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.01,0:18:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然有可能這本身就是個陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.49,0:18:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿上去賭一把吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.68,0:18:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我們就變成真實版去探探情況
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.96,0:18:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裝成野生動物
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.32,0:18:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果感覺沒勝算的話就偷偷回去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.72,0:18:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會是什麼情況呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.60,0:18:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.84,0:18:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是天堂嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.70,0:18:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女僕後宮啊~~~~~~！
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.05,0:18:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別忘了我們的目的 三笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.98,0:18:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點帶這些姑娘去安全的地方避難
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.30,0:18:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呀 發生什麼事了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.23,0:18:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新來的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.73,0:19:02.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會 會長原來是女的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.44,0:19:05.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無視這些傢伙算了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.84,0:19:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可惡 碓冰到哪裡去了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.11,0:19:09.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在這裡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.15,0:19:17.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歡迎回來 主人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.93,0:19:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰 你…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.87,0:19:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直都在騙我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.53,0:19:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 我沒說過我是鬼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.90,0:19:41.75,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.43,0:19:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我的確是三笨蛋馬戲團的團長哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.13,0:19:43.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真囉嗦 那個不用再說了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.93,0:19:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拐走這些姑娘的也是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.12,0:19:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覺悟吧 你這個變態色鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.47,0:19:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說你 在誤會些什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.99,0:19:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可是自願在這裡生活的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.09,0:20:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多受夠那種生活了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.34,0:20:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人們又髒 又自說自話
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.77,0:20:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到一個帥哥就跟來了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.26,0:20:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果這座島住起來感覺還不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.32,0:20:10.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又輕鬆 又養眼
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.50,0:20:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很充實啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.84,0:20:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,綜上所述 我家被侵佔了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.05,0:20:18.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可憐的我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.14,0:20:22.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以說
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.20,0:20:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我交往吧 會長
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.08,0:20:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離開這座島嶼 一起去尋找快樂的地方吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.75,0:20:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說什麼呢 為什麼我要和你…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.51,0:20:38.37,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,討厭 萌萌花啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.88,0:20:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,問為什麼…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.92,0:20:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為和會長在一起 我會很亢奮
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.37,0:20:49.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣 兩人冰釋前嫌成為了情侶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.75,0:20:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 等一下 我還沒…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.88,0:20:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話說回來 會長 多麼誘人的打扮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.36,0:20:57.52,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之 我才不想和你這樣的變態
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.78,0:20:58.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在誘惑我嗎 大腿露那麼多
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.71,0:21:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 準備要戰鬥了 把裙子剪掉了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.01,0:21:02.87,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.28,0:21:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恩恩愛愛地踏上了新的旅途
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.17,0:21:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過那又是另說了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.68,0:21:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可喜可賀可喜可賀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.75,0:21:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的 住手 變態
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.72,0:21:22.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碓冰同學 從剛才開始一直在給會長聽什麼呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.96,0:21:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她呻吟得很厲害啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.10,0:21:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我特製的童話故事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.30,0:21:27.14,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忙碌的會長小睡中
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.30,0:21:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順便說一下 三笨蛋也一起成為了他們倆的食物
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.51,0:21:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也是另說了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.44,0:21:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們最後還是被當成食物
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.80,0:21:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什麼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.98,0:21:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好過分
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.00,0:21:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那麼這樣 三笨蛋都各自活了下去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.12,0:21:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狗被取名為波奇 成了開花爺爺的寵物
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.12,0:21:50.62,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,童話：開花爺爺
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.07,0:21:57.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山雞擅自偷吃了婆婆的漿糊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.07,0:21:57.02,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,童話：剪舌的麻雀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.22,0:22:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猴子騙了螃蟹 搶了它的飯糰 
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.22,0:22:03.22,Comment,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,童話：猴子與螃蟹
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.93,0:22:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別殺了我們啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.00,0:22:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可喜可賀可喜可賀
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.99,0:23:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然被碓冰操縱了我的夢境 感覺真不爽
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.45,0:23:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會長愛冒險嘛 是不是很愉快啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.11,0:23:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什麼時候說過我喜歡冒險了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.89,0:23:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美咲 來下來下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.73,0:23:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼啦 小櫻 比平時還興奮
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.87,0:23:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有個超帥的樂隊呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.87,0:23:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靜子也是這麼認為的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.86,0:24:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒 我完全沒有興趣
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.38,0:24:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不要搞個美妙的聚會啊
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.98,0:24:04.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像是要和樂隊男開茶會
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.11,0:24:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什麼 樂隊男
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.83,0:24:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樂隊男這稱呼 最近反而有點新鮮感呢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.12,0:24:10.73,biaoti2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(700,357)}{\c&H509EF5&}{\fad(300,0)}小 櫻 的 地 下 戀
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.53,0:00:07.22,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}どうか Please  can you keep my secret
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.06,0:00:23.95,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}キラキラと輝くミラー
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.37,0:00:29.83,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}私はどんなふうに映っているの
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.49,0:00:34.49,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}ホラホラと手招く未来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.67,0:00:39.65,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}これからどんなことが起こるの
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.39,0:00:50.73,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}目に見えているものがすべてではないから
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.78,0:00:53.48,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}無我夢中でThat's all right
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.53,0:00:56.12,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}迷わないで I want now try
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.17,0:01:01.03,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}自分の気持ちにまっすぐでいたい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.08,0:01:03.92,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}だけど一つや二つぐらい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.97,0:01:06.38,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}誰にもばれたくない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.43,0:01:11.39,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}内緒ってあるものだから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.69,0:01:17.22,OP1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}胸がちょっと痛い　my secret
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.53,0:00:07.22,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}求求你 Please  can you keep my secret
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.06,0:00:23.95,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}閃爍光芒的鏡子裡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.37,0:00:29.83,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}我究竟是什麼模樣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.49,0:00:34.49,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}快樂招手的未來裡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.67,0:00:39.65,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}又將會發生些什麼事
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.39,0:00:50.73,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}因為所見並非一切
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.78,0:00:53.48,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}心醉神迷 That's all right
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.53,0:00:56.12,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}不要迷茫 I want now try
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.17,0:01:01.03,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}想真心面對自己的感情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.08,0:01:03.92,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}但哪怕只是一兩件事
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.97,0:01:06.38,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}也不想透露給任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.43,0:01:11.39,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}因為那是我心中的秘密
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.69,0:01:17.22,OP2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}心口隱隱作痛　my secret
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.30,0:22:31.49,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}ほんの少しでも　吐き出してほしい
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.75,0:22:36.70,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}この手で受け止めるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.75,0:22:42.20,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}とても強がりな君のことだから
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.25,0:22:49.96,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}また何かを隠そうとして　ねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.01,0:22:57.82,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}確かな予感つかんだその手を握りしめて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.87,0:23:03.32,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}走り出した　行くあてもなく
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.37,0:23:08.45,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}ただ僕の心の中にいて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.50,0:23:13.34,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}いつもそばで　見守るから
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.01,0:23:18.96,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}どんな時も離れはしないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.01,0:23:24.46,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}立ち留まらず　怖がらないで
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.51,0:23:29.62,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}君がもしも振り向いた時は
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.67,0:23:36.55,ED1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}僕らきっと笑い合おう
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.30,0:22:31.49,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}哪怕一點點 也希望你吐露真心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.75,0:22:36.70,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}我會親手接受
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.75,0:22:42.20,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}我了解你的逞強
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.25,0:22:49.96,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}一定又想隱瞞什麼 對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.01,0:22:57.82,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}緊握那雙抓住明確預感的手
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.87,0:23:03.32,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}開始奔跑 沒有目標
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.37,0:23:08.45,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}只停留在我心中
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.50,0:23:13.34,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}因為我守候在身邊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.01,0:23:18.96,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}永遠不會離開
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.01,0:23:24.46,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}不要駐足 不要害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.51,0:23:29.62,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}當你有天回首時
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.67,0:23:36.55,ED2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fade(200,200)}我們一定能相視而笑
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default2,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,
