[Script Info]
Title:犬夜叉完结篇
Original Script:四魂制作组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Chinese,SIMHEI,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00804000,&H004D2600,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,5,5,10,134
Style: Staff,SIMHEI,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00353535,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,5,5,10,134
Style: Title,SIMHEI,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H002F2F2F,&H001F1F1F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134
Style: OP-JP,Microsoft YaHei,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H004F4F4F,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,Microsoft YaHei,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H004F4F4F,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OP-Ch,Microsoft YaHei,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H004F4F4F,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-Ch,Microsoft YaHei,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H004F4F4F,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.69,0:00:03.76,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(130,130)}「没有你的未来」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.06,0:00:15.86,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}守るべきものなんて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:25.21,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}悩むまでもなく一つしかなかった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.58,0:00:29.36,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}叫び声のこだま
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.38,0:00:38.63,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}むなしく響いた 深い森の奥に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.30,0:00:45.21,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}涙をこらえられた理由は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.16,0:00:51.75,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}重ねた指のぬくもりのせい
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:55.00,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}君がいない未来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.01,0:00:58.11,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}意味などない未来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.83,0:01:04.17,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}二度と離したりはしないから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.89,0:01:08.74,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}君と臨む世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.79,0:01:11.45,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}見たことない世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.48,0:01:18.87,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}時空を越えて はるか旅する僕等
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.06,0:00:15.86,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}必须要守护的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:25.21,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}根本不用费心思考 本来就只有一个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.58,0:00:29.36,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}呐喊的回音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.38,0:00:38.63,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}在幽深的森林深处 空虚地回荡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.30,0:00:45.21,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}能够忍住眼泪的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.16,0:00:51.75,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}是与你十指相扣的温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:55.00,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}没有你的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.01,0:00:58.11,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}毫无意义的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.83,0:01:04.17,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}我不会再远你而去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.89,0:01:08.74,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}与你共赴的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.79,0:01:11.45,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}未曾见过的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.48,0:01:18.87,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}穿越时空 我们继续漫长的旅途
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.45,0:22:11.50,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}I'll take you to the higher stage
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.88,0:22:13.52,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Now you got blazin'
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.72,0:22:18.39,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}I'll take you to the higher stage
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.98,0:22:20.59,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Now you got blazin'
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.95,0:22:30.54,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}涙を隠した 強がりな君の笑顔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.74,0:22:38.06,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}肩を抱くことさえ 素直には出来なくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.14,0:22:44.77,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}夜明けの向こうに どんな未来があっても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.95,0:22:51.17,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}信じることでしか変えられない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.08,0:22:59.45,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}見失っていた魂(こころ)のカケラ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.41,0:23:06.95,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}二人で探し当てた 瞬間 きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.18,0:23:10.26,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}壊して 追いかけて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.66,0:23:14.13,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}切り開いたあの空で
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.28,0:23:15.31,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Seeking my way
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.88,0:23:21.32,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}一筋の光になる with you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.45,0:22:11.50,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}I'll take you to the higher stage
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.88,0:22:13.52,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Now you got blazin'
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.72,0:22:18.39,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}I'll take you to the higher stage
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.98,0:22:20.59,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Now you got blazin'
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.95,0:22:30.54,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}隐藏起泪水 你故作坚强的笑颜
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.74,0:22:38.06,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}我却连安慰的拥抱 都没法直率地做到
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.14,0:22:44.77,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}在黎明的彼岸 不论未来会遇到什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.95,0:22:51.17,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}我们都只能选择坚信
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.08,0:22:59.45,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}失落的心之碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.41,0:23:06.95,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}两人找到的瞬间 必将
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.18,0:23:10.26,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}破坏吧 追逐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.66,0:23:14.13,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}在我们开辟的那片天空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.28,0:23:15.31,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Seeking my way
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.88,0:23:21.32,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}化身为一线光明 with you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.35,0:01:24.25,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,300)}本字幕由四魂制作组(bbs.4hun.net)制作\N仅供交流试看 如喜欢本作品请支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.00,0:01:34.57,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,300)}翻译：婲吣囡囡、圈圈、聽見風聲；校对：聽見風聲\N时间：dorakeiko、零；润色：C=C
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.43,0:01:43.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手啦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.87,0:01:49.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要走了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.28,0:01:52.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 已经够了 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.96,0:02:02.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.89,0:02:04.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有何贵干
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.15,0:02:07.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么想都觉得不对劲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.36,0:02:08.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是斗鬼神没了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.93,0:02:10.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便没有剑
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.92,0:02:13.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这利爪也足以把你撕裂成碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.48,0:02:15.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话不是这么说的嘛 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.17,0:02:17.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是没办法才来的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.09,0:02:19.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不是天生牙在叫我…
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.46,0:02:21.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天生牙？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.12,0:02:25.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装傻了 你应该也觉察到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.65,0:02:28.04,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天生牙在蠢蠢欲动
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.12,0:02:35.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照这么看来 你心中原本缺少的东西如今出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.29,0:02:36.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,缺少的东西是啥
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.71,0:02:38.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀生丸大人的心灵是完美无缺的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.14,0:02:40.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既强悍又温柔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.21,0:02:43.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么就没有感觉到温柔呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.38,0:02:44.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪见大人 不要哭了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.00,0:02:48.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天生牙感应到了你内心的变化
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.89,0:02:51.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕不是为了自己
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.63,0:02:54.58,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是因为某个人而产生的悲悯之心
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.04,0:02:57.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先不说了 把天生牙给我
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.73,0:02:58.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.71,0:03:01.99,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要重铸其身 使之作为武器
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.83,0:03:05.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重铸天生牙？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.81,0:03:13.42,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}冥道残月破
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.49,0:03:18.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这样啊 姐姐取出了翠子的死魂
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.17,0:03:20.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琥珀也不知去向
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.49,0:03:24.48,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珊瑚很是担心 一直打不起精神呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.73,0:03:28.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我总是一副阴沉的脸
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.19,0:03:30.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珊瑚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.85,0:03:32.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出去放松一下也没关系哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.99,0:03:34.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要不是去别的女人那里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.08,0:03:38.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珊瑚 正是这种时候我才想要留在你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.08,0:03:41.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎能丢下你自己去逍遥呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.22,0:03:44.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法师大人 真温柔呢 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.68,0:03:46.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.84,0:03:48.96,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在想你是不是七宝假扮的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.06,0:03:51.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是本人 真高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.94,0:03:53.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在怀疑我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.95,0:03:56.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不 她是在怀疑法师大人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.19,0:03:59.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 事情变得难办了呐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.27,0:04:01.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然目的不同
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.72,0:04:03.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是在集齐四魂之玉这件事上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.28,0:04:05.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈落和翠子巫女都是一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.94,0:04:07.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照犬夜叉所说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.34,0:04:11.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当奈落得到完整的四魂之玉时
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.28,0:04:15.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞄准那个瞬间 将玉与奈落一起净化
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.16,0:04:18.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仅靠蛮力 是无法打倒奈落的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.96,0:04:22.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桔梗大人好像是这么说的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.94,0:04:28.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是集齐四魂之玉也就是说要牺牲琥珀的性命
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.08,0:04:30.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琥珀也希望如此吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.93,0:04:33.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么想 珊瑚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.70,0:04:35.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你希望琥珀死去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.33,0:04:37.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.42,0:04:42.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说谎了 你脸上明明写着不愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.24,0:04:42.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.39,0:04:45.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在放弃是不是还太早了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.19,0:04:46.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.63,0:04:50.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果奈落想要集合四魂之玉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.45,0:04:53.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这之前打倒奈落就行了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.13,0:04:54.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法师大人 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.16,0:04:59.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珊瑚 我们需要的就是齐心合力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.01,0:05:01.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你也不要迷惘了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.40,0:05:04.48,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.70,0:05:07.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你先走啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.18,0:05:08.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要 别推我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.54,0:05:12.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咨询志愿的填报吗 在那里哟
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.46,0:05:14.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 非常感谢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.20,0:05:17.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真期待穿上那身制服啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.81,0:05:20.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 好紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.97,0:05:22.96,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真想快点考试啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.16,0:05:24.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么呢 你很有把握？
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.91,0:05:26.04,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戈薇 你没问题的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.35,0:05:29.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为生病 落下很多课吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.68,0:05:33.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油哦 大家一定要考上同一个学校
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.15,0:05:34.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.51,0:05:37.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惨了 真的惨大了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.06,0:05:44.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊呀 咱家的神社能保佑考试合格吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.80,0:05:47.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有了这个 合格是一定没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.82,0:05:49.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个四魂之玉的护身符
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.79,0:05:51.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管什么愿望都能实现
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.15,0:05:56.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盯上玉的妖怪和巫女之间展开了持续的战斗…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.48,0:05:59.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 在那边已经体验到腻了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.78,0:06:02.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来 当最后得到四魂之玉的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.90,0:06:05.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选择了唯一正确的愿望时
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.34,0:06:09.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玉就会被净化 继而消失于世间
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.46,0:06:11.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么 正确的愿望又是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.18,0:06:13.23,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个没有流传下来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.63,0:06:15.92,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这倒是头一次听说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.14,0:06:17.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不是你每次都不听我说到最后
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.93,0:06:18.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 爷爷
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.24,0:06:22.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才说的 和考试没什么关系吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.77,0:06:24.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种事…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.09,0:06:26.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来是没关系呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.56,0:06:29.46,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚不把公式背下来的话…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.78,0:06:34.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好棒 不断记到脑子里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.06,0:06:36.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然有点冷 但是真的太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.40,0:06:40.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冷 好棒 好冷
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.04,0:06:41.46,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.56,0:06:45.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会感冒的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.88,0:06:46.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬夜叉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.68,0:06:49.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候 我到底什么时候睡着的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.19,0:06:51.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梦？全部是梦？
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.76,0:06:54.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没记住啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.89,0:07:01.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 学习很不顺利是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.71,0:07:04.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再稍微放慢点步调来就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.45,0:07:07.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么说呢 总是有很多事要操心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.16,0:07:09.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本无心学习
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.17,0:07:12.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是犬夜叉持续的骚扰造成的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.84,0:07:17.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是狐火
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.32,0:07:20.92,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七宝
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.79,0:07:22.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.47,0:07:22.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.23,0:07:28.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要抢夺的目标就是那把妖刀了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.35,0:07:31.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旅店？
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.45,0:07:34.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个肯定是妖怪的宅子
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.38,0:07:37.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 是客人哟 欢迎光顾
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.12,0:07:38.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们住这儿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.74,0:07:39.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈啊？！
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.03,0:07:40.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除妖吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.46,0:07:42.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.08,0:07:45.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇啊 客人是法师大人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.20,0:07:47.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如所见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.20,0:07:49.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 真棒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.85,0:07:51.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底想干什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.14,0:07:54.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 符咒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.02,0:07:56.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一口气升了三级
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.46,0:07:57.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺是正八位下了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.84,0:07:59.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,俺也是从八位上了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.66,0:08:01.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.41,0:08:04.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.02,0:08:07.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说是被妖怪耍了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.55,0:08:08.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 七宝呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.55,0:08:11.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是睡觉的时候吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.14,0:08:12.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,振作点 七十七号
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.91,0:08:14.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七十…七号
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.86,0:08:18.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静 我要冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.99,0:08:21.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不会输给你们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.20,0:08:23.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么啊 七十七号
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.99,0:08:26.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓唬同胞是拿不到分数的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.89,0:08:28.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖狐升级考试？
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.17,0:08:30.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是拿着准考证吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.16,0:08:34.47,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准考证？是指这片叶子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.89,0:08:37.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狐妖的等级共分为三十个位阶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.94,0:08:40.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从最高的正一位开始
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.44,0:08:42.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从一位 正二位 从二位
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.01,0:08:45.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到从八位下 然后
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.91,0:08:47.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来是大初位上 大初位下 
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.83,0:08:50.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少初位上 少初位下共三十个位阶
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.82,0:08:54.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,升到正一位的话至少也要修行个上百年
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.10,0:08:58.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天晚上的客人有法师 除妖师和妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.57,0:09:01.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好地捉弄他们 就能拿高分了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.51,0:09:04.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他们 不知道这里是考试会场就住了下来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.03,0:09:07.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他们尝尝吓得要死的滋味吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.73,0:09:10.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七宝 你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.31,0:09:10.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戈薇
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.05,0:09:14.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看她拿着破魔之箭 难道是个巫女
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.22,0:09:16.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是能进展顺利的话 会拿到更高的分数
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.75,0:09:17.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.15,0:09:20.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 等等 你们
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.38,0:09:23.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能为了考试而让同伴身处险境…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.51,0:09:25.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 七宝你这家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.24,0:09:26.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在到处乱晃什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.09,0:09:29.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开我 现在没时间和你唠叨
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.42,0:09:31.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 你那是什么口气
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.94,0:09:33.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.14,0:09:33.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戈薇
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.77,0:09:39.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七宝 你在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.66,0:09:44.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐惧吧 哭泣吧 尖叫吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.44,0:09:46.59,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七宝 你这混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.33,0:09:48.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干…干吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.53,0:09:49.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认错人了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.53,0:09:50.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.35,0:09:52.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么差劲的变身除了他还能有谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.39,0:09:56.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不合格
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.74,0:09:58.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我记住
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.51,0:09:59.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得和七宝很像
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.95,0:10:02.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为是他的朋友来着
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.24,0:10:03.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会有那么粗暴的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.06,0:10:06.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连那个女孩也在嘲笑我们
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.94,0:10:08.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 请问一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.64,0:10:14.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 第一次考试就拿到从八位上
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.31,0:10:16.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一下子升了五个位阶吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.42,0:10:17.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很厉害吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.03,0:10:20.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七十七号老兄 你到底是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.61,0:10:22.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是因为刚才捉弄了犬夜叉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.53,0:10:27.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说只要捉弄犬夜叉就能升阶了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.34,0:10:32.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是七十七号老兄 你和那帮人好像是认识的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.44,0:10:34.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把同伴当笨蛋耍不觉得难过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.67,0:10:36.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难过啊 我好难过啊 但是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.21,0:10:39.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考试比什么都重要
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.54,0:10:40.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好冷酷的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.85,0:10:44.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看看七十七号能升到哪个地步
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.34,0:10:46.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能再弄亮一点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.68,0:10:49.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 七宝好慢啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.03,0:10:50.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去找他？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.12,0:10:53.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心 他在和同伴玩啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.11,0:10:54.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同伴？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.35,0:10:57.58,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 少说也有上百只
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.74,0:10:59.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.23,0:11:02.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬夜叉 你已经被完全包围了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.64,0:11:04.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就只针对我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.31,0:11:07.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可怜呢 你就当我的垫脚石吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.95,0:11:09.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那儿吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.48,0:11:11.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上当了 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.97,0:11:13.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.44,0:11:17.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是从八位上 为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.92,0:11:19.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么没有升阶
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.89,0:11:21.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有晋级哦七十七号老兄
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.11,0:11:23.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看 这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.32,0:11:25.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个变成正正得到十分后才会进阶一级
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.04,0:11:28.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要更上一阶是非常困难的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.61,0:11:31.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.53,0:11:33.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的台词
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.41,0:11:35.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇啊 我们明明什么都没有做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.74,0:11:36.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬夜叉 坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.75,0:11:41.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 稍微手下留情嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.64,0:11:42.99,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇啊 分数上升了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.17,0:11:45.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假哭术大成功啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.44,0:11:46.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.59,0:11:47.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈 再靠过来点嘛 哈哈哈
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.66,0:11:48.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀 讨厌
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.92,0:11:49.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 升级了 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.69,0:11:50.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.39,0:11:54.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜哇 除妖的臭丸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.35,0:11:57.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬夜叉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.36,0:11:59.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说怎么一直没看到人影
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.53,0:12:00.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.28,0:12:03.59,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖狐术的升级考试？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.85,0:12:06.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖狐的世界也很严厉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.82,0:12:09.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以就让他们变成女人来供你取乐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.63,0:12:11.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想协助他们而已嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.58,0:12:15.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬夜叉昏倒了 要修理他就趁现在
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.35,0:12:17.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一 二
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.26,0:12:22.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼…我要宰了你们

Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.46,0:12:25.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我滚出来七宝
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.65,0:12:31.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可怜 他们变得很像了的说
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.84,0:12:33.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法师大人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.13,0:12:37.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饭团 我们开动咯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.27,0:12:40.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呜哇 身体麻痹了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.72,0:12:44.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就那么担心我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.32,0:12:46.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.92,0:12:48.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法…法师大人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.01,0:12:51.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可爱好可爱…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.28,0:12:54.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了 升级了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.09,0:12:56.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们可真是够努力的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.43,0:12:58.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七宝 不要鬼鬼祟祟躲躲藏藏了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.98,0:13:00.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我既没逃也没躲
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.84,0:13:04.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这种人 我要用妖狐术把你压扁
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.62,0:13:06.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有趣 有本事就试试看…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.98,0:13:08.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（不要拉）
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.92,0:13:12.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（笨蛋才会拉）
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.22,0:13:15.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好厉害 多么巧妙的妖术啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.03,0:13:17.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也算妖术？
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.53,0:13:23.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差两下就升阶啦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.20,0:13:26.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖狐术 必杀陀螺
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.44,0:13:28.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.70,0:13:30.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看招
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.75,0:13:41.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七十七号老兄 马上要天亮了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.43,0:13:42.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考试要结束了哟
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.39,0:13:44.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪能那么轻易放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.22,0:13:47.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道具用光了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.90,0:13:48.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.95,0:13:51.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还想再打的话 我继续奉陪哦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.07,0:13:54.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明只要再拿两分就好了…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.07,0:13:56.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 这是报应吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.89,0:13:59.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被考试成绩迷昏了头
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.56,0:14:03.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤害了重要的伙伴犬夜叉而遭到报应
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.18,0:14:04.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七宝
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.47,0:14:06.47,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得自己好可耻
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.96,0:14:08.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没脸再和你们在一起了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.15,0:14:11.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬夜叉 去跟他和好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.68,0:14:12.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.81,0:14:14.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 七…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.23,0:14:18.33,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.83,0:14:20.23,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 升阶了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.40,0:14:22.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厉害 升到正八位下了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.32,0:14:25.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别开玩笑了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.58,0:14:29.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家 再会了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.85,0:14:31.99,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见 七十七号老兄
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.14,0:14:33.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传说中的妖术使用家
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.96,0:14:35.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会好好地告诉大家你的事迹的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.48,0:14:39.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七宝 去哪里了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.21,0:14:43.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我出来 从刚才起就知道你在那里了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.88,0:14:45.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了犬夜叉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.24,0:14:47.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有回答的打算吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.57,0:14:49.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么只好动手把你请出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.59,0:14:51.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风之伤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.05,0:15:00.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃走了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.39,0:15:03.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬夜叉你这混蛋 想杀了我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.26,0:15:05.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你…你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.57,0:15:11.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是小貉 你是那个半妖的同伴吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.12,0:15:17.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那里吗 风之伤
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.76,0:15:23.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,铁碎牙的妖力被什么东西吸收了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.18,0:15:25.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐上来 快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.10,0:15:32.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 多亏你 才能吸收到那把妖刀的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.42,0:15:37.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 小貉 你为什么那么想要让那把刀变强呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.06,0:15:42.04,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一个人吗 你父亲怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.31,0:15:44.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么提到我爹的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.52,0:15:46.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从你身上闻到父亲的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.09,0:15:50.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爹死了 被坏妖怪杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.75,0:15:53.47,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么说是为了给父亲报仇才要把刀变强
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.68,0:15:57.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这么一回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.44,0:15:59.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貉和我是一样的遭遇吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.22,0:16:02.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一场战斗已经不是私怨了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.94,0:16:04.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是为了大义的战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.48,0:16:05.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,（犬夜叉是个白痴）
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.72,0:16:07.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开什么玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.55,0:16:11.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖力又被吸走了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.54,0:16:14.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 你们的位置可是一目了然
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.84,0:16:17.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风之伤发不出来
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.22,0:16:21.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬夜叉 感觉怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.42,0:16:23.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七宝 你这个臭小子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.27,0:16:27.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是大义 我为了大义要助小貉一臂之力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.56,0:16:29.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退下 七宝 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.37,0:16:31.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底吸收了多少妖力了呢 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.32,0:16:33.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要拿这个半妖来试刀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.46,0:16:35.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戈薇 离我远些
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.04,0:16:38.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风之伤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.60,0:16:42.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬…犬夜叉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.43,0:16:46.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是不错的威力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.28,0:16:48.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个半妖也该断气了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.77,0:16:49.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.97,0:16:53.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是只要从铁碎牙上夺取妖力就可以了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.45,0:16:55.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不记得有答应你那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.12,0:17:01.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 为了夺取天下是不需要两个强者同存的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.36,0:17:04.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啥 你不是要为了父亲报仇的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.86,0:17:09.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我老爹都死了几百年了 死于食物中毒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.73,0:17:12.48,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被欺骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.67,0:17:16.04,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不原谅你 就算是女孩子也要…揍你！
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.53,0:17:19.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这拳是为了惨死的犬夜叉…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.71,0:17:22.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭小子 谁惨死了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.35,0:17:26.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬夜叉 你没死？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.43,0:17:27.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.62,0:17:29.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了风之伤为什么还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.82,0:17:32.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 那你就再砍一刀试试啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.00,0:17:35.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你既然这么说了 风之伤
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.90,0:17:38.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手法迟钝风速也慢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.51,0:17:43.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你吸了多少妖力我是不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.68,0:17:45.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但使用者的技术太烂了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.02,0:17:47.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办 七宝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.35,0:17:49.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被这家伙骗了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.14,0:17:50.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要杀了她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.45,0:17:52.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算被杀我也无话可说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.69,0:17:55.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我利用了七宝的温柔善良
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.55,0:17:57.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小貉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.86,0:17:59.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然时间很短暂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.67,0:18:01.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过和你在一起真的很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.40,0:18:03.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 犬夜叉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.04,0:18:05.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是想砍小貉的话就连我一起砍了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.59,0:18:10.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃吧 这里我来应付
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.55,0:18:12.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 七宝
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.25,0:18:14.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这流下的泪水
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.28,0:18:15.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能让我原谅她所做的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.73,0:18:16.99,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走吧 小貉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.44,0:18:21.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半妖 要是心疼这小子的小命的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.33,0:18:22.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就乖乖交出你那把妖刀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.42,0:18:24.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.98,0:18:26.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于显出本性来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.86,0:18:34.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的 你竟然能看穿我的真面目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.60,0:18:37.96,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吵死了 从一开始我就闻出你身上的大叔臭味了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.13,0:18:39.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔臭味…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.70,0:18:43.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 我还以为是父亲的气味
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.16,0:18:45.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是他本人的…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.63,0:18:47.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 怎么办七宝
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.15,0:18:49.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样都无所谓了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.68,0:18:50.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.50,0:18:54.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢蛋 你那把妖刀上的妖力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.83,0:18:56.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经被我的「夺鬼」给…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.76,0:19:00.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我滚
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.31,0:19:01.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.62,0:19:07.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 妖气回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.09,0:19:08.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这把铁碎牙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.20,0:19:11.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是能通过斩杀来吸收对方妖气的刀子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.43,0:19:13.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对…对不起 犬夜叉
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.48,0:19:15.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我不好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.77,0:19:18.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦七宝 我根本没放在心上
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.03,0:19:23.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 虽然你说的和做的是两回事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.03,0:19:26.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来这把叫「夺鬼」的刀子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.77,0:19:28.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能吸收妖气的力量可不能小看
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.77,0:19:31.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有调查看看的价值
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.18,0:19:37.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挥刀吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.49,0:19:45.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.79,0:19:48.33,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我见识你的本事吧 杀生丸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.14,0:19:53.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天生牙应该能引导你找出刀子的轨道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.86,0:20:05.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有砍断 这不是和以前没什么两样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.29,0:20:09.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪见大人 那是什么 鬼的身后
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.56,0:20:12.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冥道被打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.65,0:20:14.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冥道？
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.35,0:20:24.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到…到底发生了什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.22,0:20:26.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如所见
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.40,0:20:28.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鬼的身体被送到彼世去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.82,0:20:32.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斩开冥道的招式吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.17,0:20:36.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天生牙本来就是连结此世和彼世的妖刀啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.92,0:20:41.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正因如此 天生牙的持有者可以看见彼世的使者
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.35,0:20:46.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斩杀他们来让死者复活回到这个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.73,0:20:47.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎？是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.50,0:20:50.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不就是因此复活的第一号吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.89,0:20:52.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反过来 当它斩开通往彼世之道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.66,0:20:54.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是冥道的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.27,0:20:57.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会将敌人从那里送往彼世
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.77,0:20:59.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是天生牙的战法
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.27,0:21:02.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你刚才所使用的便是
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.88,0:21:04.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冥道残月破
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.93,0:21:09.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来 这家伙竟然一下子就运用自如了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.24,0:21:12.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是那副死样子 一点也不可爱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.31,0:21:16.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过没办法 天生牙都承认他是主人了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.97,0:21:23.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个笨女人 简直是白白送死
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.49,0:21:26.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少最后 见到了你…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.19,0:21:31.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死得有没有价值 由我杀生丸来决定
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.66,0:21:36.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刀刀斋 战斗用的天生牙我就收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.51,0:21:43.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.82,0:21:46.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.19,0:21:50.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帅呆了

