[Script Info]
Title:犬夜叉完结篇
Original Script:四魂制作组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:360
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Chinese,SIMHEI,23,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00804000,&H004D2600,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,5,5,10,134
Style: Staff,SIMHEI,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H00353535,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,5,5,10,134
Style: Title,SIMHEI,30,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H002F2F2F,&H001F1F1F,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,2,2,30,30,30,134
Style: OP-JP,Microsoft YaHei,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H004F4F4F,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-JP,Microsoft YaHei,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H004F4F4F,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,2,30,30,10,134
Style: OP-Ch,Microsoft YaHei,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H004F4F4F,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,30,30,10,134
Style: ED-Ch,Microsoft YaHei,21,&H00FFFFFF,&H00000000,&H004F4F4F,&H000F0F0F,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,1,8,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.69,0:00:03.76,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(130,130)}「没有你的未来」
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.06,0:00:15.86,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}守るべきものなんて
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:25.21,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}悩むまでもなく一つしかなかった
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.58,0:00:29.36,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}叫び声のこだま
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.38,0:00:38.63,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}むなしく響いた 深い森の奥に
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.30,0:00:45.21,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}涙をこらえられた理由は
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.16,0:00:51.75,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}重ねた指のぬくもりのせい
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:55.00,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}君がいない未来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.01,0:00:58.11,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}意味などない未来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.83,0:01:04.17,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}二度と離したりはしないから
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.89,0:01:08.74,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}君と臨む世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.79,0:01:11.45,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}見たことない世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.48,0:01:18.87,OP-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}時空を越えて はるか旅する僕等
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.06,0:00:15.86,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}必须要守护的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:25.21,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}根本不用费心思考 本来就只有一个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.58,0:00:29.36,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}呐喊的回音
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.38,0:00:38.63,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}在幽深的森林深处 空虚地回荡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.30,0:00:45.21,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}能够忍住眼泪的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.16,0:00:51.75,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}是与你十指相扣的温暖
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.08,0:00:55.00,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}没有你的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.01,0:00:58.11,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}毫无意义的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.83,0:01:04.17,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}我不会再远你而去
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.89,0:01:08.74,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}与你共赴的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.79,0:01:11.45,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}未曾见过的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.48,0:01:18.87,OP-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}穿越时空 我们继续漫长的旅途
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.45,0:22:11.50,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}I'll take you to the higher stage
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.88,0:22:13.52,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Now you got blazin'
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.72,0:22:18.39,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}I'll take you to the higher stage
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.98,0:22:20.59,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Now you got blazin'
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.95,0:22:30.54,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}涙を隠した 強がりな君の笑顔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.74,0:22:38.06,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}肩を抱くことさえ 素直には出来なくて
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.14,0:22:44.77,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}夜明けの向こうに どんな未来があっても
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.95,0:22:51.17,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}信じることでしか変えられない
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.08,0:22:59.45,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}見失っていた魂(こころ)のカケラ
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.41,0:23:06.95,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}二人で探し当てた 瞬間 きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.18,0:23:10.26,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}壊して 追いかけて
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.66,0:23:14.13,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}切り開いたあの空で
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.28,0:23:15.31,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Seeking my way
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.88,0:23:21.32,ED-JP,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}一筋の光になる with you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.45,0:22:11.50,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}I'll take you to the higher stage
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.88,0:22:13.52,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Now you got blazin'
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.72,0:22:18.39,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}I'll take you to the higher stage
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.98,0:22:20.59,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Now you got blazin'
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.95,0:22:30.54,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}隐藏起泪水 你故作坚强的笑颜
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.74,0:22:38.06,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}我却连安慰的拥抱 都没法直率地做到
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.14,0:22:44.77,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}在黎明的彼岸 不论未来会遇到什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.95,0:22:51.17,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}我们都只能选择坚信
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.08,0:22:59.45,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}失落的心之碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.41,0:23:06.95,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}两人找到的瞬间 必将
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.18,0:23:10.26,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}破坏吧 追逐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.66,0:23:14.13,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}在我们开辟的那片天空
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.28,0:23:15.31,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}Seeking my way
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.88,0:23:21.32,ED-Ch,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}化身为一线光明 with you
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.35,0:01:24.25,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,300)}本字幕由四魂制作组(bbs.4hun.net)制作\N仅供交流试看 如喜欢本作品请支持正版
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.00,0:01:34.57,Staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,300)}翻译：婲吣囡囡、PSIKYO、圈圈、聽見風聲；校对：聽見風聲\N时间：零、木子Lee、铁碎牙；润色：C=C
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.12,0:01:41.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾心空荒芜 浊世苟残喘
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.89,0:01:45.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜半月孤寒 惟此可流连
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.23,0:01:49.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不能让他逃走啊 神乐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.50,0:02:17.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,竟然吸收了妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.87,0:02:18.71,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 御灵丸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.05,0:02:20.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底是何方神圣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.64,0:02:22.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么奈落要把你关在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.15,0:02:25.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你若想知道就把他放出来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.49,0:02:28.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白童子？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.78,0:02:31.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 一到紧要关头就害怕起奈落吗 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.86,0:02:34.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 那你敢背叛奈落？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.22,0:02:36.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选择吧 神乐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.25,0:02:39.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就那样被奈落束缚直至死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.08,0:02:43.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是和我一起逃出这里获得自由
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.83,0:02:46.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自由？
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.68,0:02:47.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 自由
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.53,0:02:50.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果想完全从奈落手中逃脱出来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.00,0:02:52.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只有杀死他
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.99,0:02:53.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.72,0:02:55.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来 这些家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.04,0:02:58.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是奈落在白灵山时分离出来的心脏
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.83,0:03:02.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来被奇怪的和尚劈成了两半
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.64,0:03:04.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成了白童子和婴儿
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.41,0:03:06.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 神乐 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.90,0:03:07.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真能迎来那时刻
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.37,0:03:11.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会在奈落死之前拿回你的心脏
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.80,0:03:17.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这样 释放了御灵丸之后 我还要做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.93,0:03:20.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们的实力还不足以消灭奈落
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.04,0:03:22.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以一定要得到那个力量
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.13,0:03:23.92,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.27,0:03:26.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四魂碎片吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.77,0:03:34.02,Title,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(130,130)}奈落的心脏
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.65,0:03:39.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就可以了吗 弥勒 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.16,0:03:41.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 做得不错啊 七宝
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.69,0:03:44.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 怎么看都是另一个我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.13,0:03:47.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这个样子 在珊瑚身边待着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.35,0:03:51.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬夜叉去戈薇家的期间都一直这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.66,0:03:52.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.80,0:03:54.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就先稍微去放松放松
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.42,0:03:58.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这绝对不关我的事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.90,0:03:59.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都明白
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.20,0:04:09.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不明白 已经彻底不明白哪里不明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.35,0:04:11.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戈薇一个人补习吗 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.11,0:04:13.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为最近总是请假吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.49,0:04:16.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考试马上就到了 不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.33,0:04:19.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 是你们啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.39,0:04:21.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静下来 好好想想
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.97,0:04:24.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这绝对是参考书上有的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.83,0:04:26.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的 我一定可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.07,0:04:29.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦 是来接戈薇的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.45,0:04:30.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真体贴啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.58,0:04:31.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好说好说 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.57,0:04:33.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集中精神！还差一点就解出来了！
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.24,0:04:39.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才有什么扑哧的一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.90,0:04:41.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是集中力断裂的声音吧 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.33,0:04:43.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时不时的会有呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.90,0:04:44.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.50,0:04:48.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戈薇 你干吗又这么干
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.91,0:04:51.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了 不是说了要你在家里等吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.79,0:04:53.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不是因为你这么慢嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.64,0:04:56.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我在为早点回去努力啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.65,0:04:59.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 都是因为你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.42,0:05:02.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好不容易才想出来的公式全忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.94,0:05:04.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可怕 戈薇好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.95,0:05:07.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道以恐怖的高压占主导的是戈薇
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.91,0:05:09.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 全部都错了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.71,0:05:11.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照这样 要考你志愿的学校很难啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.21,0:05:16.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 戈薇
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.81,0:05:18.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.83,0:05:22.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈 怎么样 幸好有我来了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.56,0:05:23.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真甜蜜啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.15,0:05:26.59,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不打搅你们 我们就在这里闪人了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.98,0:05:27.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.74,0:05:29.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等下…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.40,0:05:33.47,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎 算啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.76,0:05:35.48,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.96,0:05:37.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来 戈薇…咦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.31,0:05:41.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 现在就走吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.98,0:05:43.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是老样子 匆匆忙忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.90,0:05:45.48,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边也能准备考试
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.17,0:05:47.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走啦 戈薇
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.36,0:05:47.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.05,0:05:49.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路顺风
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.59,0:05:51.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要加油哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.24,0:05:53.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 戈薇 
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.32,0:05:56.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论是那个志愿学校还是什么考试的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.84,0:05:58.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都给你摆平吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.06,0:06:00.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必了 那是绝对没可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.05,0:06:03.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 反正都是些杂碎妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.54,0:06:04.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考试也好邪见也好 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.39,0:06:06.58,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听上去都是弱了吧唧的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.29,0:06:11.33,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪见大人 感冒吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.53,0:06:12.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.30,0:06:15.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道是谁在背后说我坏话吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.90,0:06:19.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邪见 结晶没什么变化吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.74,0:06:22.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在妖气还没有消失
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.47,0:06:29.20,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 奈落用来隐藏心脏妖气的不妖璧并不在这附近
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.38,0:06:32.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀哎呀 到底在哪里呀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.86,0:06:31.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}邪见大人 邪见大人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.28,0:06:33.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}要把你丢下咯…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.28,0:06:35.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 杀生丸大人等等…
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.60,0:06:45.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.95,0:06:48.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唉 塞太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.15,0:06:51.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是的 你怎么回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.54,0:06:53.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别光看着 赶紧来帮忙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.55,0:06:56.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最猛胜
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.56,0:06:57.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是…奈落吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:01.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 真是好久不见了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.54,0:07:05.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么长时间没见你们 还让我很担心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.64,0:07:07.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.76,0:07:09.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戈薇
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.25,0:07:13.59,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四魂碎片被抢走了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.32,0:07:16.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戈薇小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.58,0:07:19.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要打开风穴 法师大人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.91,0:07:21.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会被最猛胜的毒腐蚀的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.91,0:07:23.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四魂之玉的碎片也会被吸进去的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.90,0:07:28.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要拿到这个 就不用和你们浪费时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.66,0:07:31.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别想跑 风之伤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.09,0:07:35.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 犬夜叉
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.46,0:07:36.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 被他逃了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.31,0:07:39.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 四魂之玉的气息还没消失 
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.12,0:07:40.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能追上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.88,0:07:44.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下啦 钢牙
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.38,0:07:45.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.08,0:07:47.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那么急干吗啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.93,0:07:50.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠得很近了 味道越来越臭了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.42,0:07:54.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈 来了呀 四魂碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.78,0:08:27.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琥珀 去狩猎厉害的妖怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.96,0:08:36.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 那就是妖怪的真面目吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.38,0:08:42.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.76,0:08:49.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 太一
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.59,0:08:50.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爹
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.23,0:08:55.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个…你的手臂没关系吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.71,0:09:01.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伤口还在疼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.24,0:09:03.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不疼 已经没问题了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.28,0:09:07.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.54,0:09:08.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.29,0:09:11.59,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被妖怪附身了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.90,0:09:15.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 太一
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.19,0:09:16.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 等等啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.27,0:09:22.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父…父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.40,0:09:25.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.58,0:09:26.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太一 为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.97,0:09:29.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在被操纵了 只是被操纵了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.54,0:09:32.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太一
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.14,0:09:34.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 我一定能救他的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.62,0:09:39.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的悲剧 不能再重演了 
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.18,0:09:41.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.34,0:09:49.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风刃之舞
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.07,0:09:53.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哟
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.87,0:09:54.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神乐
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.41,0:09:57.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道奈落的心脏所在了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.02,0:09:58.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.15,0:09:59.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.11,0:10:00.96,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 琥珀 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.66,0:10:03.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈落他不是你能打败的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.83,0:10:06.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 你就死在这里吧

Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.18,0:10:14.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次一定
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.98,0:10:15.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.20,0:10:18.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 无论多少次都会再生 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.73,0:10:20.95,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直就和奈落一样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.64,0:10:24.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 难怪总觉得可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.55,0:10:26.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是和奈落一伙的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.46,0:10:28.11,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的话 你又打算怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.33,0:10:30.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宰了你 为我的族人报仇
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.68,0:10:38.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈 我要将你和四魂碎片一起吞噬 
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.85,0:10:43.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.46,0:10:48.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人来碍事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.66,0:10:51.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这笔账我一定会和你算清的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.85,0:10:53.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才的是破魔之箭？
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.81,0:10:55.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说那是戈薇大姐吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.76,0:10:56.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.84,0:11:03.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到只是一击 灵力就下降了那么多
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.16,0:11:06.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是那个叫做魍魉丸的妖怪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.03,0:11:08.99,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和以前见过的印象完全不同了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.57,0:11:12.18,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直像有了灵魂一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.09,0:11:19.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道心脏下落的话 就告诉我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.50,0:11:22.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这之前我必须拿到你的四魂碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.71,0:11:26.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取出碎片后你就丧命了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.96,0:11:29.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少让你在这里死得痛快点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.59,0:11:35.68,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已无处可逃了 做好觉悟了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.08,0:11:38.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是觉悟的话 我很早以前就有了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.33,0:11:39.75,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我没打算在这里丧命
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.60,0:11:44.90,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要碎片的话 这样把我带回去就可以
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.35,0:11:48.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时我就能给奈落的心脏狠狠的一刀 
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.95,0:11:50.12,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使以我的生命为赌注
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.34,0:11:55.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神乐你不也是为了这个才把结晶给我的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.97,0:11:58.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算是被奈落操纵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.09,0:12:01.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是亲手杀了父亲和大家
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.56,0:12:04.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那边 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.55,0:12:06.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事 白童子还没有走太远
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.25,0:12:09.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.61,0:12:11.46,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉到另一块四魂碎片的气息
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.70,0:12:12.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一块碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.58,0:12:13.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钢牙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.58,0:12:15.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不是他的感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.31,0:12:17.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么是琥珀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.38,0:12:21.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我服从奈落的命令 不断地造孽
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.52,0:12:25.13,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就连我唯一的姐姐也一再被我伤透了心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.44,0:12:28.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便如此我也苟活到了今天
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.12,0:12:30.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了报仇…吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.50,0:12:32.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的使命
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.04,0:12:34.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不完成这个使命的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.65,0:12:39.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便是死去 我也没有脸面去给父亲和大家道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.16,0:12:42.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没用的 琥珀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.89,0:12:45.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道你下了多大的决心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.36,0:12:47.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是就算你狠狠地砍中 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.19,0:12:50.64,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对奈落 婴儿 白童子他们来说也是白费
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.76,0:12:54.33,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终你的四魂碎片还是会被取走
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.46,0:12:57.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 说得没错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.66,0:12:59.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神乐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.42,0:13:01.26,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的结果也只不过是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.74,0:13:04.06,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从奈落变到婴儿 换了个主人而已
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.84,0:13:06.41,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根本谈不上什么真正的自由
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.05,0:13:09.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了神乐 带我去奈落的心脏那里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.79,0:13:11.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然的话 就算是孤身一人 我也要…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.62,0:13:15.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖气的结晶被…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.84,0:13:19.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样你就失去了寻找心脏的线索
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.72,0:13:20.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神乐 你到底…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.20,0:13:22.04,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别废话了 快逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.85,0:13:25.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的碎片被抢走的话 会更麻烦的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.00,0:13:27.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是个不可信任的女人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.31,0:13:32.05,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背叛奈落之后 还要背叛我们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.86,0:13:33.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快逃 琥珀
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.52,0:13:34.03,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.83,0:13:35.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫你快逃
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.65,0:13:40.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琥珀 怎么下来就自己想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.95,0:13:42.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神乐
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.64,0:13:44.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃不掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.04,0:13:45.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙蛇之舞
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.65,0:13:54.52,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呵呵 神乐 偶尔也尝尝吧 自己的风刃
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.65,0:13:58.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风之伤
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.35,0:14:03.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犬夜叉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.27,0:14:05.22,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事 神乐 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.82,0:14:07.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么会和白童子打起来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.22,0:14:10.16,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烦死了 没空和你解释
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.47,0:14:12.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,珊瑚 你去追琥珀
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.54,0:14:14.33,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 走吧云母
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.38,0:14:17.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接招 金刚枪破
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.00,0:14:22.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碎片的气息还没走远 应该就在附近
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.51,0:14:26.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样好吗 轻率地背对着敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.00,0:14:29.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是敢轻举妄动 我照劈不误
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.95,0:14:33.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你知道的事情都坦白出来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.48,0:14:37.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白童子那混蛋好像不杀掉你就不打算走了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.05,0:14:41.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他大概是不想让我泄露奈落心脏的下落吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.16,0:14:45.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.54,0:14:48.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是御灵丸 他还活着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.61,0:14:51.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个伤 是被谁弄的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.88,0:14:53.42,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种事无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.37,0:15:05.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快把四魂碎片交出来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.96,0:15:07.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,御灵丸就是魍魉丸吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.12,0:15:08.98,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用上它
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.59,0:15:10.49,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四魂的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.32,0:15:13.56,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.15,0:15:15.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去追另一块碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.72,0:15:18.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会让你走的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.46,0:15:26.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白童子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.23,0:15:29.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幻…幻影
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.02,0:15:33.93,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背叛者 只有你 我是绝对不会放过的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.42,0:15:36.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白童子 你这个混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.50,0:15:39.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 再用你的招术攻过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.78,0:15:40.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连着神乐一起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.59,0:15:44.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不动手吗 真是个幼稚的小子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.33,0:15:48.47,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真意外啊 你也能用来做挡箭牌
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.65,0:15:49.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笨蛋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.11,0:15:52.30,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了犬夜叉 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.56,0:15:56.23,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈落心脏化的婴儿就在魍魉丸的体内
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.37,0:15:57.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.41,0:16:01.69,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,白童子和婴儿想靠加强魍魉丸打倒奈落以取代他
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.28,0:16:04.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你猜得不错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.46,0:16:08.99,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那天 奈落把心脏分离出来是个错误
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.98,0:16:13.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈落为了保护心脏 把不妖璧给了婴儿
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.99,0:16:15.97,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥有不妖璧就能隐藏妖气
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.90,0:16:20.51,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后婴儿就想制造一个坚硬的铠甲
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.12,0:16:23.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是吞噬御灵丸后的魍魉丸
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.28,0:16:27.36,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样做的同时我们发现了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.16,0:16:30.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有心脏的奈落只是个空壳
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.31,0:16:32.92,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们才是正体
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.64,0:16:35.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们迟早会取代奈落的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.84,0:16:39.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种伎俩奈落早就看穿了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.13,0:16:40.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.33,0:16:44.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过有空担心我 还是先担心你自己吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.49,0:16:49.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然同样是叛徒 但你的心脏却还在奈落手里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.38,0:16:51.65,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死心吧 神乐
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.12,0:16:54.24,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到哪里都无法拥有自由
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.30,0:16:54.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗嗦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.81,0:16:58.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砍多少次都一样 我是不会死的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.42,0:17:02.86,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来多少人也杀不死我 就算是奈落…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.90,0:17:05.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.53,0:17:11.02,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在 风之伤
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.83,0:17:14.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.88,0:17:15.85,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要使用风穴吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.58,0:17:17.08,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休想得逞
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.31,0:17:21.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 为什么不保护我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.01,0:17:26.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来被奈落先抛弃的 是你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.82,0:17:28.60,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住嘴 我是不会死的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.07,0:17:31.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是瘴气
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.07,0:17:32.59,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来净化
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.84,0:17:36.07,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和神乐不同
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.46,0:17:38.77,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不是像她这样 是任凭奈落操纵的道具
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.08,0:17:40.25,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快躲开 神乐
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.20,0:17:41.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.01,0:17:42.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风穴
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.69,0:17:46.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.76,0:17:49.72,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本尊…
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.90,0:17:56.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉真恶心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.33,0:17:56.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.68,0:17:59.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,简直就像是被奈落利用了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.08,0:18:01.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.67,0:18:05.50,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈落那个混蛋 竟然让我们了结白童子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.53,0:18:11.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神乐 今后你要怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.98,0:18:13.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐 如果可以的话 和我们一起…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.06,0:18:16.91,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用了 事到如今我怎么可能和你们一起
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.78,0:18:19.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起这个 你们动作一定要快
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.00,0:18:22.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魍魉丸的目标是琥珀的碎片
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.96,0:18:23.89,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 戈薇
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.21,0:18:25.37,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧 戈薇小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.08,0:18:26.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.73,0:18:28.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 神乐
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.04,0:18:31.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被奈落捏着的心脏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.53,0:18:32.70,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也会顺便替你夺回来的 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.73,0:18:33.46,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.06,0:18:36.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么漂亮话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.31,0:18:41.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 在那之前可别先死掉啊 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.85,0:18:42.55,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.40,0:18:47.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要你说我也会活下去的 无论是去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.68,0:18:51.29,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琥珀…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.19,0:18:54.35,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐 就那样 不要过来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.23,0:19:02.33,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼哼 看见你内心了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.06,0:19:07.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为杀死了父亲和同伴 决心以死赎罪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.97,0:19:09.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是很好的决心
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.93,0:19:13.09,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么为了你那个姐姐去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.69,0:19:17.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弟弟杀死父亲的事 那个女人是不会忘记的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.18,0:19:18.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琥珀…
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.82,0:19:23.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你还活着 你们姐弟的痛苦就不会结束
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.61,0:19:24.45,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.57,0:19:27.27,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞来骨
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.74,0:19:33.15,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不…不要过来 姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.52,0:19:35.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琥珀 你的记忆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.46,0:19:37.00,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,垂死挣扎就到此为止
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.43,0:19:40.73,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,垂死挣扎的是你 魍魉丸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.13,0:19:42.87,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对 奈落的心脏
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.33,0:19:47.63,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然看穿了你的本体 就更不能放过你了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.86,0:19:50.76,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉悟吧 金刚枪破
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.51,0:19:53.67,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋 想逃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.40,0:19:55.32,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 犬夜叉 
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.80,0:19:59.46,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那把刀的妖力 我迟早会吞噬掉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.09,0:20:02.83,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃哪里去了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.34,0:20:06.34,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碎片的气息消失了 好像被他逃了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.76,0:20:07.54,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好可惜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.47,0:20:12.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琥珀 你认得我了吧 想起来了对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.91,0:20:16.21,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想起来了 所有的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.82,0:20:21.79,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有那一天的事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.41,0:20:26.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我注定无法和姐姐在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.61,0:20:28.33,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琥珀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.82,0:20:30.66,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么 好不容易才重逢的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.00,0:20:34.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琥珀 你一个人能做什么 只是去送死吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.91,0:20:35.62,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.39,0:20:37.57,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一起的话会痛苦吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.52,0:20:40.14,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戈薇小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.25,0:20:43.39,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能留在珊瑚的身边吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.25,0:20:49.78,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有任何人 能代替琥珀的哦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.72,0:20:53.53,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.21,0:20:56.19,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琥珀
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.31,0:21:01.82,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便是弥勒 也无法抚平珊瑚的寂寞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.57,0:21:05.28,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说在前头 也没有人能代替我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.91,0:21:11.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桔梗大人 很痛吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.63,0:21:14.94,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心 这点程度的伤 
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.11,0:21:18.40,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,师…师傅
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.99,0:21:19.61,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妖怪？
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.84,0:21:21.31,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看…看向这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.88,0:21:23.88,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们能看到我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.84,0:21:26.74,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别过来 恶灵退散
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.84,0:21:28.81,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烫烫…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.83,0:21:31.84,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很可惜 驱邪的符咒对我没用的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.91,0:21:34.10,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对…对不起…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.12,0:21:36.38,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两人居然能穿过桔梗大人的结界
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.67,0:21:38.44,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么做到的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.32,0:21:41.01,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,桔梗大人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.15,0:21:45.43,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再这样下去 打倒奈落之前就…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.43,0:21:50.17,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吾心空荒芜 浊世苟残喘
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.78,0:21:53.80,Chinese,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜半月孤寒 惟此可流连




